<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<bugs>
	<bug>
		<id>242</id>
		<title>2ch.hk recaptcha2 центровка</title>
		<body>при попытке загрузить капчу происходит развертка области капчи за рамками экрана. Android 10, 423 dp, 1080x2400 При перевороте андроида в полноэкранный режим капча масштабируется нормально. https://imgur.com/a/AKOEOeR</body>
		<created>2020-09-18 12:41:36</created>
		<closed>2020-09-19 21:51:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>235</id>
		<title>4chan keeps telling me that the captcha is not supported </title>
		<body>Reinstalled it a couple times and tried 2 different extensions Unclicked "use Java script" still tells me the same thing  ![Screenshot_2019-12-20-09-36-26](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/59096315/71278402-5d4b0a00-230c-11ea-988d-32fa56645807.png) </body>
		<created>2019-12-20 17:37:45</created>
		<closed>2020-09-20 16:04:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>229</id>
		<title>Капча</title>
		<body>После ввода капчи ничего не происходит, появляется сообщение неправильная капча, с чем в корне не согласен, попадалась капча с четко нарисованными цифрами, все ввел, перепроверил, исход тот же. телеф oukitel k10000pro</body>
		<created>2019-07-16 10:46:52</created>
		<closed>2019-07-18 07:50:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>227</id>
		<title>Whatanime has changed their domain name -needs to be fixed</title>
		<body>Searching images on whatanime doesn't work anymore because they've changed their domain name to trace.moe </body>
		<created>2019-06-27 15:19:14</created>
		<closed>2020-09-18 02:28:13</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>215</id>
		<title>Не загружаются картинки </title>
		<body>Ни с двача ни с форчана уже несколько дней не удается загрузить картинки, статус всегда "не загружено". </body>
		<created>2018-12-07 00:01:56</created>
		<closed>2018-12-07 00:22:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>213</id>
		<title>Капча на форче</title>
		<body>Капча просто убийственно долгая, тупит невозможно. По двадцать раз приходится выбирать светофоры, и все равно ничего не происходит. </body>
		<created>2018-12-04 22:22:37</created>
		<closed>2020-09-18 02:29:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>212</id>
		<title>Search Image [whatanime.ga] doesn't work</title>
		<body>Basically whatanime.ga moved to trace.moe, ergo this function doesn't work.</body>
		<created>2018-12-03 20:07:59</created>
		<closed>2020-09-18 02:29:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>208</id>
		<title>Captchas not working in latest release.</title>
		<body>In the latest release (2.10.4), the captchas are not working, at least for 4chan. Steps to reproduce: 1) Install latest version with 4chan and webm support. 2) Try to post, load the captcha. 3) Complete the captcha successfully and post. 4) Try to post again. When you try to post again, the captcha will disappear every time you select a "square" of it, only to reappear again with the same problem. This happens a couple times more until it gives up and keeps trying to load the post to no avail. The weird thing is, the first time you try to post the captcha works fine, however every time after that it won't work at all. The captcha is working fine on 2.10.3. Cheers.</body>
		<created>2018-11-08 03:15:53</created>
		<closed>2020-09-18 02:29:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>194</id>
		<title>"No extensions installed" error</title>
		<body>After upgrading to Android Oreo, dashchan has intermittently been losing contact with the 8ch and 4chan extensions on launch and only loads the menu. Clearing cache, wiping data, or even uninstalling the app does not fix it. The extensions link back up seemingly at random and then the app functions as it should.</body>
		<created>2018-03-22 02:54:01</created>
		<closed>2020-09-18 02:40:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>186</id>
		<title>Вылетает при попытке поделиться файлом</title>
		<body>Система: Android 8.0 При попытке поделиться любым файлом, будь то изображение или вебм, вылетает дашчан. Прикрепляю лог ниже. [error-1515008297425.txt](https://github.com/Mishiranu/Dashchan/files/1601487/error-1515008297425.txt) </body>
		<created>2018-01-03 19:43:20</created>
		<closed>2018-01-06 19:35:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>185</id>
		<title>Recaprcha v2 dvach</title>
		<body>Рекапча с "машинами" и "дорожными знаками", а может быть и ещё , что-то, не отображает текст " нажмите на картинки с машинами/дорожными знаками", а просто картинки без надписи сверху, в то время как с "мостами", " автобусами" и "домами" всё в порядке, и над картинками висит надпись "select all images with an bus/appartament building/bridges".</body>
		<created>2017-12-31 00:53:40</created>
		<closed>2017-12-31 11:18:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>183</id>
		<title>Плагин 2ch не работает</title>
		<body>Тут это... 2ч отвалился</body>
		<created>2017-12-26 19:50:37</created>
		<closed>2017-12-26 20:52:02</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>176</id>
		<title>New bug</title>
		<body>На днях обновил телефон до android 7.0 NRD90M, Miui 9.1.1.0. После этого пропали надписи на экране (captions), которые при открытии тредов выскакивали с кол-вом новых сообщений и кнопкой "к новым постам" - это самая офигенная фича и она отвалилась. Можно это починить? Версия сброки 2.10.3, если что.</body>
		<created>2017-11-15 12:36:50</created>
		<closed>2017-11-15 12:47:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>175</id>
		<title>Wizchan</title>
		<body>Most thumbnail pics on Wizchan aren showing up as triangles with exclamation marks in them. Any way to fix it?</body>
		<created>2017-10-20 07:29:49</created>
		<closed>2017-10-29 12:21:33</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>173</id>
		<title>"Load nearest image" not working properly</title>
		<body>I have it set to "Always" but when I swipe to the next image it shows the thumbnail while the full resolution version loads. To confirm this I set the option "Load thumbnails" to "Never" then I get a blank space while the image loads.</body>
		<created>2017-10-11 01:13:01</created>
		<closed>2017-10-11 09:40:44</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>156</id>
		<title> 8ch Images don't load</title>
		<body>I think that 8ch has changed the location where images are stored, so all images are now broken, except for cached images and thumbnails.</body>
		<created>2017-07-24 11:56:37</created>
		<closed>2017-07-25 00:11:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>149</id>
		<title>Модули не устанавливаются в среде Samsung My Knox</title>
		<body>При попытке установить любой модуль в среде My Knox, моментально выходит ошибка "Приложение несовместимо с вашим устройством".  Прошу извинить за "индивидуальную" просьбу, но можете ли вы, Mishiranu, собрать один apk из Dashchan, модуля Двача и webm-кодеков?</body>
		<created>2017-07-06 08:07:19</created>
		<closed>2017-07-10 21:44:04</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>148</id>
		<title>Lainchan.org module doesn't work</title>
		<body>As title say. They remade the site while ago, maybe something changed and broken the module.</body>
		<created>2017-06-27 06:33:30</created>
		<closed>2018-01-17 10:30:43</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>146</id>
		<title>picture overview bug</title>
		<body> [If a thread has a lot of images and you try to do the picture overview, it will just crash](https://youtu.be/xZt855FqNFc)  https://endchan.xyz/pol/res/34243.html Try this thread for example. Also can you make it so we can change the direction the picture overview works?</body>
		<created>2017-06-17 05:04:28</created>
		<closed>2017-06-17 20:00:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>144</id>
		<title>endchan error</title>
		<body>![screenshot_20170615-004639](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/18385494/27165777-d2b0102a-5185-11e7-904c-06877e38bc8f.png)  Clicking the post number puts you to a different thread rather then the post itself.</body>
		<created>2017-06-15 04:49:02</created>
		<closed>2017-06-16 20:48:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>142</id>
		<title>endchan bug</title>
		<body>Sometimes I make a mistake trying to post a thread, but when i fix it i get a captcha error. Happens on /pol/.</body>
		<created>2017-06-11 03:46:09</created>
		<closed>2017-06-14 14:52:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>136</id>
		<title>Глюк гуя</title>
		<body>Если быстро два раза нажать на ссылку на ответ пока он открывается, то он откроется 2 раза. Поставь и проверяй флаг, что ли.</body>
		<created>2017-05-30 19:27:08</created>
		<closed>2017-06-03 12:47:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>129</id>
		<title>Archivers won't load threads? </title>
		<body>4plebs.org:------When I load the catalog at /HR/ for example I'm able to load it, and clicking on the preview works, but when i click at a post it displays nothing except for "this thread doesn't exist".  This happens the same for other archives but they wont even load the catalog like asia.rbt</body>
		<created>2017-05-03 00:00:23</created>
		<closed>2017-05-03 00:31:29</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>126</id>
		<title>"Unable to download data" after solving captcha</title>
		<body>I can't post on 4chan. After resolving captcha I get the abovementioned notification.  I was wandering if it's due to using cerberus</body>
		<created>2017-04-18 07:43:17</created>
		<closed>2017-04-22 23:40:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>122</id>
		<title>8chan extension 403 Forbidden</title>
		<body>Unable to access 8chan. Maybe due to the security fixes recently implemented? Visiting results in 403 Forbidden.</body>
		<created>2017-04-05 00:23:34</created>
		<closed>2017-05-03 00:17:29</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>119</id>
		<title>Issue in posting in 4chan using reCAPTCHA v2</title>
		<body>I noticed a few days ago that I was having issues with the captcha.  I was using reCAPTCHA v2 but kept getting the "invalid captcha error" even though I already **unchecked** the  "Use Javascript for reCAPTCHA".  The only way I was able to post again was to change the CAPTCHA to v1.   Am I missing something to not be able to use reCAPTCHA v2 properly?</body>
		<created>2017-04-02 10:14:20</created>
		<closed>2017-04-22 23:40:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>118</id>
		<title>Unable to create posts in 4chan</title>
		<body>If I use the old captcha, no matter how many times I input it, it tells me "Captcha is not valid", and when I use Captcha 2 (Where you have to click squares), most of the time it doesn't even load.</body>
		<created>2017-03-14 10:07:23</created>
		<closed>2017-04-02 18:55:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>117</id>
		<title>Lainchan submissions are always spoilered</title>
		<body>Hey, I found a small issue with the Lainchan extension.    Scenario:  1. Make post with image  2. Submit  Result:  Image is spoilered no matter what.   Device: HTC 10, Android 7.0, Dashchan v2.9.0, Extension v1.3  Regardless, thanks for working on this great app!</body>
		<created>2017-03-13 02:31:38</created>
		<closed>2017-03-15 14:42:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>113</id>
		<title>can't upload any files for 8ch.net</title>
		<body>  Every time I try attaching an image/video to a post, a message just pops up, reading "invalid server response". There are no other connection issues, I can make text only posts, I can attach files to posts on other extensions, and I tried changing image settings. It only happened after getting the latest patch.  I'm on a motorola xoom.  </body>
		<created>2017-02-06 01:18:54</created>
		<closed>2017-02-06 06:31:53</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>112</id>
		<title>Highlighting the bottom post of a threads crashes the app</title>
		<body>Device: HTC 10, Android 7.0  If I try to double tap the bottom/last post of a thread to select its text, the app crashes sometimes. </body>
		<created>2017-01-30 01:58:04</created>
		<closed>2017-04-02 18:56:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>110</id>
		<title>7chan board /eh/ doesn't load</title>
		<body>It just shows a text saying "Invalid server response".</body>
		<created>2017-01-09 17:48:50</created>
		<closed>2017-01-14 19:59:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>108</id>
		<title>Captchas don't work if JavaScript versions are enabled</title>
		<body>If the option to use JavaScript for captchas is enabled, they don't seem to work. `Failed to download data`  Android 7.1.1</body>
		<created>2016-12-25 21:25:45</created>
		<closed>2016-12-31 14:15:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>104</id>
		<title>Blank thumbnails in most threads</title>
		<body>I'm on 2.9.0 running Android 7.1 and I can't see almost any thumbnail, happening in 4chan, lainchan and 420chan (possible to affect all of them). Am I doing something wrong?  Screenshots: https://my.mixtape.moe/xnqpzg.png https://my.mixtape.moe/nrgidz.png https://my.mixtape.moe/cbmigu.png https://my.mixtape.moe/gsvbge.png</body>
		<created>2016-12-05 14:44:49</created>
		<closed>2016-12-09 01:00:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>102</id>
		<title>[2ch] Ошибка расширения вместо 404?</title>
		<body>При попытке обновить страницу которая судя по всему была удалена показывается "ошибка расширения"</body>
		<created>2016-12-02 05:30:48</created>
		<closed>2016-12-03 03:07:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>95</id>
		<title>u18chan post count is wrong.</title>
		<body>While browsing threads it always shows a really low post number even if there's more.</body>
		<created>2016-10-31 08:44:15</created>
		<closed>2016-11-05 11:39:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>92</id>
		<title>Pop-ups not closing</title>
		<body>When you click the bottom for replies, a pop-up shows up showing the replies. Sometimes this pop-up doesn't close. Not all the time.  May be related to the new update for mathjax? </body>
		<created>2016-10-20 18:57:36</created>
		<closed>2016-10-22 22:35:16</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>91</id>
		<title>Some images or videos won't load (8chan)</title>
		<body>Some images / videos from 8ch wont load and shows a 404 message. Tried /pol/, /tech,/ /v/ so it pretty much happens to every board.  This started the other day. </body>
		<created>2016-10-19 02:27:13</created>
		<closed>2016-10-19 14:14:51</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>88</id>
		<title>8chan captcha "no need to enter captcha"</title>
		<body>8cha ext doesnt want me to enter captcha </body>
		<created>2016-10-03 02:47:38</created>
		<closed>2016-10-06 03:23:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>81</id>
		<title>Can't access some parts of u18chan.</title>
		<body>Any board under the section labelled "The Basement" gives an invalid server response. </body>
		<created>2016-09-04 13:08:15</created>
		<closed>2016-09-04 14:27:45</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>79</id>
		<title>Поиск изображения</title>
		<body>Поиск изображения на дваче не работает с тех пор, как они добавили сраную проверку флеры (хотя им постили ссылку на модуль который эту проверку обходит). Как минимум не работает tineye. </body>
		<created>2016-08-23 18:53:30</created>
		<closed>2016-09-19 16:42:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>73</id>
		<title>Автосохранение набранного текста</title>
		<body>Если набрать текст, переключиться на другое приложение, после этого из-за нехватки памяти прогу прибьют, то текст тоже пропадет. </body>
		<created>2016-08-18 19:54:17</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 20:04:25</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>69</id>
		<title>404 для капчи (2ch)</title>
		<body>Вместо капчи показывается 404, соответственно, отправка не работает. </body>
		<created>2016-08-17 14:02:51</created>
		<closed>2016-08-23 19:02:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>68</id>
		<title>webm playback jerks</title>
		<body>When playing Webms, the video and sound jerks and stutters. I'm on a Nexus 6P. </body>
		<created>2016-08-16 20:57:33</created>
		<closed>2016-08-28 16:12:43</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>66</id>
		<title>4chan Captcha Problem </title>
		<body>Sometimes when I go to post something on 4chan and I'm trying to do the Captcha I click a picture and it closes and opens up a new window with a new Captcha. You have to close the app and reopen for it to work sometimes.  I'm running Android 6.0 on a Motorola G3 </body>
		<created>2016-08-05 01:09:01</created>
		<closed>2016-08-06 06:11:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>58</id>
		<title>Desustorage moved to http://desuarchive.org/</title>
		<body>Title. </body>
		<created>2016-06-30 05:36:03</created>
		<closed>2016-06-30 18:53:02</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>52</id>
		<title>Crash while updating</title>
		<body>What do you need for fix this? Logs, screens etc. </body>
		<created>2016-06-07 10:37:58</created>
		<closed>2016-06-08 13:43:44</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>51</id>
		<title>Webm player shows unknown address</title>
		<body>After updating to the latest dashchan webm plugin, attempting to play a webm shows an error: "unknown address".  </body>
		<created>2016-05-29 04:26:01</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 18:32:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>49</id>
		<title>Webm</title>
		<body>При открытии вебм,на очень малое время включается звук и выключается,получается писк и похоже что на всю громкость Zenfone 2 551ml 5.0 </body>
		<created>2016-05-19 19:23:36</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 18:49:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>45</id>
		<title>App aways starting with burichan light theme enabled. </title>
		<body>I have to change manually everytime when I start the app.  This theme is like battery acid on my eyes. Is this a bug?  </body>
		<created>2016-04-02 08:03:37</created>
		<closed>2016-04-16 04:22:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>44</id>
		<title>Small typo in settings-info (Portuguese) </title>
		<body>I'm Brazilian, and the word "licensa " doesn't exist.  Please fix it writing "licença"   The two texts are currently written  "licensas open source" "detalhes da licensa open source" change licensa to licença  </body>
		<created>2016-03-13 04:22:54</created>
		<closed>2016-03-23 02:44:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>43</id>
		<title>0chan.cc</title>
		<body>У нульчана заблокировали домен,сделай чтобы с его айпи 31.220.3.61 зайти можно было </body>
		<created>2016-03-11 08:18:09</created>
		<closed>2016-03-12 20:30:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>41</id>
		<title>Thumbnails don't load in local host (and suggestions related to local host) </title>
		<body>In the previous version thumbnails was loading without problems, but now they aren't loading. I tried everything except cleaning app data (I have many favorites saved and I don't want lost)   You remember the suggestion about archiving threads with their original names? Since this isn't possible I have other idea, and at same time  a question.   When you save an image and the dialog prompt ask to save file and choose the location, the app asks to save with their original names and detailed names, in this process what your app do?   It renames the original filename (according to server name with details/or original filenames?  If any of my thoughts are correct..  My request is, in local host, when you save files in the localhost gallery or individually, the app rename the file to their original filenames or detailed (user choice) using the same method above.  And other request, is it possible to make a custom directory setting when saving files in local host (in the folder called localhost/null and the threads) like I requested In the past.   Thank you so much.  </body>
		<created>2016-03-10 01:51:15</created>
		<closed>2016-08-23 19:03:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>38</id>
		<title>Ponychan Doesn't Work</title>
		<body>Opening a Ponychan thread just says "Invalid server response". </body>
		<created>2016-02-09 16:36:16</created>
		<closed>2016-02-10 14:44:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>34</id>
		<title>Captchas not rendering properly.</title>
		<body>When I try to reply, I load the captcha and this is how it appears:  http://i.imgur.com/Kgkbn1z.png  I can't see nor click the images. Don't mind the red hue, it's just Twilight. </body>
		<created>2016-01-26 16:25:11</created>
		<closed>2016-02-03 15:50:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>33</id>
		<title>Can't tap to read spoilers of an OP without opening the thread.</title>
		<body>e.g.: http://a.pomf.cat/smmqdy.mp4 </body>
		<created>2016-01-26 05:13:05</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 18:33:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>32</id>
		<title>Clean installed and can't do much.</title>
		<body>I clean installed the Main .apk, 4chan apk, and the WebM apk.  Now, I can't change the theme or open any images. Latest versions installed as of this moment. </body>
		<created>2016-01-25 23:43:51</created>
		<closed>2016-01-26 00:06:22</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>31</id>
		<title>Make it harder to swipe to next image.</title>
		<body>A constant problem that I have is that when I'm zooming into images, it's way too easy to swipe to the next image.  An easy solution is to not swipe to the next image when zoomed in. </body>
		<created>2016-01-17 21:06:18</created>
		<closed>2016-01-26 00:17:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>27</id>
		<title>Клиент падает при попытку скопироватб или цитировать.</title>
		<body>Началось пару мажорных апдейиов назад уже несколько месяцев. Одинаково как на планшете с Android 5.0.2 (не обновлял с апреля) так и на телефоне со свежим 6.0.1 и factory reset. Как повторить - виделить любой текст и нажать кнопку копировать или цитировать и приложение сразу падает. Каждый раз. Приаттачил лог креша [error-1450555480286.txt](https://github.com/Mishiranu/Dashchan/files/67593/error-1450555480286.txt) </body>
		<created>2015-12-19 20:12:06</created>
		<closed>2015-12-20 15:29:33</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>26</id>
		<title>Can't write to SD card (external) even allowing the app to write </title>
		<body>Phone model: Galaxy S4 GT-i9505 - ROM JDCT ROM 6.0. </body>
		<created>2015-12-16 15:20:24</created>
		<closed>2015-12-19 03:45:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>23</id>
		<title>Small Typo in Settings</title>
		<body>Preferences &gt; Contents &gt; Clear cache, thumbnails is spelt "thumnails". </body>
		<created>2015-12-02 07:45:01</created>
		<closed>2015-12-13 18:31:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>22</id>
		<title>Invalid server response (error) when browsing 8ch.net </title>
		<body>Happens when I'm swiping to reach at page 2, after this a toast notification says "invalid server response."   Reloading board doesn't works.  </body>
		<created>2015-11-22 04:37:06</created>
		<closed>2015-11-22 16:55:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>20</id>
		<title>captcha expired</title>
		<body>help, it's impossible to post because it keeps saying captcha expired </body>
		<created>2015-11-20 09:31:14</created>
		<closed>2015-11-23 17:46:35</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>19</id>
		<title>Rbt.asia thumbnails</title>
		<body>Can you make it so rbt.asia can actually open up images? On the site I can open the full image but on the app all pictures are thumbnails. </body>
		<created>2015-11-19 06:31:05</created>
		<closed>2015-11-20 16:43:18</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>17</id>
		<title>"No access to memory" error on Nexus 7 (2013, Wi-Fi), Android 6.0</title>
		<body>After updating to 6.0 I can no longer open attached media, always getting the "No access to memory error". Thumbnails display fine. </body>
		<created>2015-11-09 01:08:11</created>
		<closed>2015-11-09 21:11:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>12</id>
		<title>App crashes if gallery opened before thread loaded</title>
		<body>Version: App: 2.2.0 (03.09.2015) 4chan extension: 1.1  STEPS_TO_REPRODUCE: 1. Открыть тред. 2. Открыть галерею до того как содержимое треда загрузится. 3. В приложении "Dashchan" произошла ошибка.  Воспроизводится стабильно, желательно открывать большой тред. </body>
		<created>2015-09-05 19:05:09</created>
		<closed>2015-09-20 10:59:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>11</id>
		<title>Crashes when clicking a youtube thumbnail from an Opening Post</title>
		<body>If you spot a thread where the Opening Post contains a youtube thumbnail instead of a conventional image, and click on it, the app will crash. This happens on 8ch. I haven't tried to reproduce this problem on other imageboards tho. </body>
		<created>2015-09-01 05:23:08</created>
		<closed>2015-09-21 20:13:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>5</id>
		<title>Theme not applied when starting up</title>
		<body>http://i.imgur.com/3FC5SWk.png  http://i.imgur.com/Jjqz5GZ.png </body>
		<created>2015-08-17 02:20:38</created>
		<closed>2015-08-20 06:51:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1</id>
		<title>Issue with links</title>
		<body>The embedded links always cut off letters at the end. Please fix it. Thank you. </body>
		<created>2015-07-13 20:38:04</created>
		<closed>2015-10-05 20:29:33</closed>
	</bug>
</bugs>
