<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<bugs>
	<bug>
		<id>2950</id>
		<title>UI issue -- Need a refresh after pushing Profiles</title>
		<body>This is a known issue, I just want to make sure is captured. After pushing to  GVT,  at the Test Execution panel trying to to load a sample message, I get the following:  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/46209624-5184b980-c2fc-11e8-8811-211f61e21697.png)   It works fine after doing a refresh.</body>
		<created>2018-09-28 12:57:50</created>
		<closed>2018-10-11 16:38:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2943</id>
		<title>Can't build CS: Undefined value</title>
		<body>Issue reported by user:                  I was trying to do something simpler, I was trying to make a Conformance Statement for OBX-4 that states that the value of OBX-4 must be greater than Zero. For some reason when I add a conformance statement that should say, “The value of OBX-4 SHALL be greater than 0” it is replacing 0 with the word undefined? Below are screen shots of what I am trying.  1)Created a Custom Flavor of OBX-Observation/Result   2)Clicked on the Conformance Statements Tab   3) Added the following conformance statement    4)When I hit Add this is what displays, how is 0 being equated to Undefined?    </body>
		<created>2018-09-20 16:44:56</created>
		<closed>2018-10-11 16:46:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2942</id>
		<title>Can't add entry to User's Guide</title>
		<body>Moving sections in the User's Guide was implemented and it is working, but now I can't add entries in the User's Guide. I click the + sign, when I tried to enter a title nothing happens:   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/45832024-cc335080-bcce-11e8-94bd-8beac6b06d58.png) </body>
		<created>2018-09-20 16:15:21</created>
		<closed>2018-10-11 16:42:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2935</id>
		<title>Can't delete a document from Documentation sub-categories.</title>
		<body>Can't delete a document from Documentation sub-categories. Just the message is displayed no action button.</body>
		<created>2018-09-06 14:06:39</created>
		<closed>2018-09-20 16:17:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2930</id>
		<title>Profile Component is not applied for some profiles and some locations </title>
		<body>from @robnist  When I create a PC by selecting a Segment Level element and then change the usage of a field to R from O and then create a composite profile, the definition of the composite profile does not include the change. ![image1](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/16800878/43289933-76d023e8-90fa-11e8-8f9b-805d106c6520.jpg) ![image2](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/16800878/43289950-7ebf71bc-90fa-11e8-8acf-817ddd43e549.jpg) </body>
		<created>2018-07-26 21:37:35</created>
		<closed>2018-09-06 14:05:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2921</id>
		<title>Custom tables are duplicated in the export</title>
		<body>Many (but not all) tables are present multiple times in the export  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/42781103-d2c9743a-890a-11e8-95de-4f959623d8ed.png) </body>
		<created>2018-07-16 20:13:56</created>
		<closed>2018-07-17 12:23:18</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2917</id>
		<title>Export is showing value set intended for composite profile element in the core profile elem.</title>
		<body>1. A profile component was created adding a value set to PID_IZ-11.9.  2. Exported the IG not including the generated flavors for the composite profile.      =&gt;The export shows the  main flavor PID_Iz-11.9  (core profile flavor) with  the value set that was intended for the created profile component.   Maxence, this is the issue we discussed yesterday, you mention it might be related to an id issue. </body>
		<created>2018-07-03 11:18:44</created>
		<closed>2018-07-19 15:21:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2916</id>
		<title>Profile Configuration Reset Default configuration</title>
		<body>Restore default configuration is not working. </body>
		<created>2018-07-03 11:11:16</created>
		<closed>2018-07-19 15:22:56</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2907</id>
		<title>Creating a Tool Scope from IGAMT is not working</title>
		<body>The drop down to select a Tool Scope is working, but create Tool Scope is not. </body>
		<created>2018-06-21 20:37:53</created>
		<closed>2018-07-19 15:29:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2880</id>
		<title>Profile errors when Pushing to GVT</title>
		<body>This is for, HL7 Version 2.6 Implementation Guide: Vital Records Birth and Fetal Death Reporting, Release 1 STU Release 2- Copy  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/39440375-b822d514-4c78-11e8-90b3-850078f31f98.png)  </body>
		<created>2018-04-30 17:16:42</created>
		<closed>2018-05-30 22:22:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2874</id>
		<title>Create profile verification module</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2018-04-16 17:32:08</created>
		<closed>2018-06-05 17:58:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2848</id>
		<title>Color coding incorrect</title>
		<body>The color coding to identify field, components is not correct  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/37734701-51a7a686-2d22-11e8-89b9-3cbcbc963e7f.png)  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/37734796-9a2b8044-2d22-11e8-8538-e98380040305.png)  </body>
		<created>2018-03-21 20:12:29</created>
		<closed>2018-03-23 13:55:48</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2842</id>
		<title>User Dynamic Mapping - Reference Values</title>
		<body>The user Dynamic Mapping is allowing datatypes that are not in the  0125 value set.  There need to be a link to this value set.  Also, we  need to rename the "Reference Values" column title. Rob approved the first requirement, We need Rob to give us title name. </body>
		<created>2018-03-16 21:07:33</created>
		<closed>2018-03-23 14:47:43</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2838</id>
		<title>Value Set Binding - single code -- not working </title>
		<body>1. Once in the Value Set/Single Code Bindings panel - Selecting "Single Code" ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36869038-4b2da78e-1d68-11e8-84bf-5b0be4078e47.png) 2. Selected a value set with codes 3.Did not choose a code, but clicked the box under "Action" column for the value set selected.  (BTW this is not clear - it looks like unselects the value set) 4. Tried to choose a different v/s and here the tool does not respond. I am not longer able to select a v.s </body>
		<created>2018-03-01 20:59:39</created>
		<closed>2018-03-23 14:30:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2835</id>
		<title>Profile Update </title>
		<body>This issue was reported by Sheryl:  I tried to update My Profile in IGAMT – wanted to correct the spelling of my last name. IGAMT rejected the update. 1.I found where my name is in My Profile – Taylor is mis-spelled Tayor ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36817717-30f351d8-1cb0-11e8-9434-bdb892d93f41.png)  2.I changed Tayor to Taylor; the UPDATE ACCOUNT button activated, but when I clicked on it… ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36817749-544e9b4c-1cb0-11e8-8e1c-f56bf10a3c09.png)  …IGAMT rejected the update and this message displayed: ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36817767-68313700-1cb0-11e8-8d80-64aea538e360.png)  Also:  At the bottom of the My Profile screen is a function that allows the user to Disable their User Account. A message warns the user that if they disable their account they won’t be able to reuse their username if they create a new account – but it doesn’t say anything about the impact on the email address associated with the disabled account.  Rob is going to check with Harold to see if disabling a User Account affects being able to create a new account using the same email address as before.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36817853-ace072c6-1cb0-11e8-8d34-f75097d8608e.png)  </body>
		<created>2018-02-28 22:59:13</created>
		<closed>2018-03-23 13:58:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2827</id>
		<title>Value Set/Single code delete button is not working</title>
		<body> ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36616894-725c5904-18b3-11e8-95a9-67a947afeb66.png) </body>
		<created>2018-02-23 21:06:40</created>
		<closed>2018-03-23 14:39:37</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2822</id>
		<title>GVT error when saving a profile </title>
		<body>GVT is generating an error when I am trying to save a profile to a new group. No clue on what is the error.  ![image.png](https://images.zenhubusercontent.com/56097b10638e718c995d604c/f2bf06a8-3fe4-4ea8-9dfd-1e6e500230c3)</body>
		<created>2018-02-20 19:09:03</created>
		<closed>2018-03-23 15:05:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2811</id>
		<title>Segment flavor not showing in drop down list</title>
		<body>I have two MSH flavors, MSH_TXT and MSH_2.7_TXT. When I tried to assign one of the flavors, the MSH_2.7_TXT is not listed in the drop down flavor list.    ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36216388-acebb3e6-117c-11e8-8658-07dad9c25cb9.png) </body>
		<created>2018-02-14 16:48:17</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 15:07:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2810</id>
		<title>OBX-6 in Co-constraints Table</title>
		<body>Testing in IGAMT dev: OBX-6 in the co-constraint table is not allowing to enter a value set.   IGAMT Dev  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36166664-3f263388-10c1-11e8-988b-a3f4905b5ba8.png)  IGAM Prod ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36166694-56f978a8-10c1-11e8-9b4a-8b942be70d76.png)  </body>
		<created>2018-02-13 18:26:27</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 15:04:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2809</id>
		<title>Un expected text in dT drop down flavor list</title>
		<body>I think this was noticed in yesterday meeting, but I think it was in a different place. It showed up in the  drop down when selecting a DT flavor.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/36161272-372eb61a-10b1-11e8-8958-f804ecc06cb7.png) </body>
		<created>2018-02-13 16:30:53</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 21:29:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2781</id>
		<title>unreferenced segment, datatype , value sets should not be exported in XML</title>
		<body>@Jungyubw  they should not be exported. Any reason why they are being exported ? </body>
		<created>2018-02-05 20:11:18</created>
		<closed>2018-03-26 17:31:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2779</id>
		<title>Fix Add/Removing segment/group in message</title>
		<body>Remove adding group to a message  Enable adding segment everywhere in the message (Already supported)  Do not handle the existing predicates when the segment is removed.  Let the user clean up their mess  Ignore verification for new segment added within the message definition.   Make the new segment colored (green) and add an ? icon where hovered, show message:  Because this is an added segment, it will not be verified.  </body>
		<created>2018-02-05 19:41:21</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 16:20:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2772</id>
		<title>Exporting Guide as Word Document - Co-constraint table not displayed</title>
		<body>Per Dave": When I export the guide to a Word Document, most things look like the HTML, but the OBX co-constraints table doesn't work at all.  There are many pages with only an "IF THEN" at the top and the rest of the page is blank, see below."   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/35696029-2f6f0b7a-0754-11e8-9bf4-6654cf28faaa.png)  @Abdelghani90 find out the following: When I export it as HTML, it works as expected. When I export in Verbose mode for Co-Constraint it works as expected for both word and HTML. When I export as word and my configuration is set to Compact (for Co constraint always). The document is exported but the co-constraint  table is not displayed.  I also checked a different IG and this is not happening.  </body>
		<created>2018-02-01 18:47:54</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 21:22:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2771</id>
		<title>Can't export IG due to special  characters in PhiVads </title>
		<body>![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/35691364-46cadd02-0746-11e8-9cb6-3ce7f590aa59.png)  This particular case the special character was in the pre-text @Jungyubw is there a way to remove special characters when loading the value sets?</body>
		<created>2018-02-01 16:53:36</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 16:14:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2745</id>
		<title>Order of components messed up in some datatypes</title>
		<body>This is in the datatype library.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/34683787-1a94c550-f471-11e7-8919-f7019ae2e482.png) </body>
		<created>2018-01-08 17:40:36</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 21:32:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2742</id>
		<title>New conditional group -- Can't add a predicate</title>
		<body>I can't add a predicate to a conditional group I added. </body>
		<created>2018-01-05 20:51:31</created>
		<closed>2018-01-11 15:43:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2735</id>
		<title>Binding Location in Value set cross reference is sometimes incorrect</title>
		<body>This is not consistent, sometimes I get the right value, sometimes I don't Here's an example. Binding Location should be 4 (not 3) because the value set is assigned to EI_GU.4 ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/34615775-070d4c24-f204-11e7-98ed-cc701e281df3.png)  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/34615808-1e9200ba-f204-11e7-9984-394f053d37f7.png) </body>
		<created>2018-01-05 15:36:55</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 21:30:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2732</id>
		<title>HTML export of my LRI R2 IG fails</title>
		<body>I try to export &gt; As HTML &gt; IG Style  and I get a page with the following error :   {"Errors stack":[],"Location":"[IG Document] 58349b5184ae8eb773924552"}  Export as xml seems to work (I did not check the contents yet, but at least I get a zip file)</body>
		<created>2018-01-05 15:20:31</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 21:31:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2726</id>
		<title>Unable to select data type in Delta </title>
		<body>![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/34577737-3ae7752e-f150-11e7-8a68-d6d2c2760bad.png) </body>
		<created>2018-01-04 18:08:05</created>
		<closed>2018-01-04 18:11:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2725</id>
		<title>Adding field in the midle of a segment</title>
		<body>I was able to add a field to the middle of a segment. I was discussing this with @carolinerosin  and we are wondering If IGAMT is supposed to let user add field in the middle of segments ? It seems wrong. @robnist we think this needs to be discussed.   Per Caroline: "I can see the point for adding fields at the end of a segment, but not messing with an existing segment structure."  It is also messing up the verify, by adding the fields to the middle.   I just added another field and now is doubling up the fields. Take a look.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/34574341-1dd0f1be-f145-11e7-9e6b-90197e4dbb9e.png) </body>
		<created>2018-01-04 16:49:54</created>
		<closed>2018-01-09 15:33:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2723</id>
		<title>Optional Usage drop down</title>
		<body>Notice this drop down: ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/34567712-5d88fffe-f131-11e7-86d9-25b628d3666c.png)  </body>
		<created>2018-01-04 14:27:16</created>
		<closed>2018-01-04 15:27:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2722</id>
		<title>data type user library -- empty after publishing</title>
		<body>I am re-testing this feature, but now it is not working as expected. I created the data type library and published it. Then I tried to use it in my IG, but is empty: ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/34532496-4fd332ec-f084-11e7-86f8-534d7ef13a71.png) Here is the library, I did not added any constraints, just published as it. Could it be that is missing the predicates? but, no errors were generated and the tool allowed me to created like that.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/34532575-95911a56-f084-11e7-9508-c700ffd91752.png) </body>
		<created>2018-01-03 17:50:22</created>
		<closed>2018-01-03 18:02:13</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2720</id>
		<title>Usage Notes</title>
		<body>Per Dave:  Another issue is that there are several places in the HTML export where there is a "Usage note:" but there is no text.  In fact, it is this way throughout the guide, blank usage notes.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/34484189-1dbcc2d0-ef91-11e7-86e3-3a1ab85d008b.png) </body>
		<created>2018-01-02 12:48:07</created>
		<closed>2018-01-11 21:01:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2716</id>
		<title>Datatypes are repeated in export </title>
		<body>Per Dave: When I publish the guide to HTML, many of the datatypes are repeated and out of order, see below ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/34384012-704e1890-eae7-11e7-9ce1-001c67d59faf.png) I checked Mead's IG and only one data type was repeated. </body>
		<created>2017-12-27 14:23:19</created>
		<closed>2018-01-23 18:48:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2711</id>
		<title>[Major blocking Issue] Can not add Segment to Group in Group</title>
		<body>When I try to add a segment to a group (included in another group) in the message structure view, IGAMT fails to do so, the console shows a " ReferenceError: oldPath is not defined" error.  Adding a Group works as expected.  Adding a Segment to a Group not included in another group also works.  ref to #2357   &lt;img width="868" alt="screen shot 2017-12-14 at 10 12 32 am" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14352180/33999084-784dad06-e0b7-11e7-82bc-d58f26327132.png"&gt; </body>
		<created>2017-12-14 15:16:07</created>
		<closed>2018-01-04 19:54:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2706</id>
		<title>Remove default co-constraint table row</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-12-11 18:22:45</created>
		<closed>2018-01-04 15:50:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2705</id>
		<title>Adding data types from a user library</title>
		<body>I created two user libraries.  . MyDTlib is empty . TXT has some datatype I created  1. Right clicked on "MyDTlib" to  "Add User Datatype" 2. Selected "TST" lib, but no data types were displayed in the source column. 3, Did a search on a dt a I know is in TST lib, but the search did not respond  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/33786258-6ac45430-dc36-11e7-8dd4-e63a1d867dfd.png) </body>
		<created>2017-12-08 21:40:18</created>
		<closed>2017-12-08 21:56:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2704</id>
		<title>Unable to save or delete "single code" constraint after modification</title>
		<body>Here's what I did: - create a flavor of a segment (MSH_ACK), based on another flavor (MSH_LRI). My MSH_LRI had some "single code" constraints - in my new flavor, I want to change the values in the single code constraints, so I open the tree element and clic on the little pencil in the valueSet/singleCode column - I change the code value to another value in the editor - the save button stays greyed out, so I cannot save   I thought I could delete (in the tree view) to re-create, but when I clic on the little cross button, nothing happens (it is not deleted). I can only delete in the editor.</body>
		<created>2017-12-08 16:17:36</created>
		<closed>2018-01-11 19:48:30</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2700</id>
		<title>Unable to save profile component</title>
		<body>I added a new item (OBX_LRI segment flavor) to a profile component (NG) I modified the dynamic mapping (added more to the existing table)  The save button to save my profile component stays grey and I am not able to save. If I navigate to another element, I (obviously) lose what I just did  Note that I did the same thing in another profile component (GU) and it worked, I was able to save.</body>
		<created>2017-12-07 21:41:41</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 21:16:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2698</id>
		<title>Adding a user data type from a user library -- datatype is not showing</title>
		<body>Added a data type CWE_USR to "MyDtLib" library:  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/33735062-3b27aefa-db5c-11e7-985b-3380e9a44baf.png)  When go to the IG and try the data type from  from "MyDtLib" the data type I created is not listed:  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/33734969-eb718d90-db5b-11e7-9292-c5528db82bdd.png) @Abdelghani90 I did this before and it was working fine. </body>
		<created>2017-12-07 19:41:08</created>
		<closed>2018-02-09 16:36:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2684</id>
		<title>Predicate Validation</title>
		<body>Mead reported that the tool  is generating incorrect predicate errors. I also tested other predicates, there is definitely something wrong with the evaluation of the predicates.  The message segment seems to be valid.  The message segment: OBX|13|NM|83846-6^MothersHeight^LN||62|in^Inches^UCUM|||||F  Error generated by validation:   The Field OBX-6 (Units) is present whereas it is an unsupported element (Usage = X). The element is not supported based on the condition predicate evaluation: If the value of OBX-6.1 is one of list values: 83846-6,56077-1,8339-4,69461-2,87296-0,11884-4,85724-3,87298-6,87299-4,64794-1,64795-8. --  Here is the XML: &lt;Segment&gt;&lt;ByID ID="OBX_BR_2-6"&gt;&lt;Predicate ID="CP_6[1]_0" Target="6[1]" TrueUsage="R" FalseUsage="X"&gt;&lt;Description&gt;If the value of OBX-6.1 is one of list values: 83846-6,56077-1,8339-4,69461-2,87296-0,11884-4,85724-3,87298-6,87299-4,64794-1,64795-8.&lt;/Description&gt;&lt;Condition&gt;&lt;AND&gt;&lt;Presence Path="6[1].1[1]"/&gt;&lt;StringList Path="6[1].1[1]" CSV="83846-6,56077-1,8339-4,69461-2,87296-0,11884-4,85724-3,87298-6,87299-4,64794-1,64795-8"/&gt;&lt;/AND&gt;&lt;/Condition&gt;&lt;/Predicate&gt;&lt;/ByID&gt;</body>
		<created>2017-11-30 11:46:33</created>
		<closed>2017-11-30 15:21:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2683</id>
		<title>IGAMT - GVT- Profile Viewer</title>
		<body>Is not displaying the elements in the Profile Viewer, nor the Datatypes at all. Only the CS are displayed.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/33393870-95a86a9e-d50e-11e7-9437-9dbbfee80a90.png) </body>
		<created>2017-11-29 19:07:45</created>
		<closed>2017-11-29 19:11:22</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2682</id>
		<title>No validation on user value set </title>
		<body>I am testing V/S with no codes  in the dev server. I imported a PhiVads value set as flavor with no codes. The xml looks like it have the table with the codes, validation is not working.  When I look in the Profile Viewer the co-constraint created using this value set is not there.</body>
		<created>2017-11-29 18:55:26</created>
		<closed>2017-11-30 15:52:45</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2677</id>
		<title>Multiple code system (comma separated) added in value set table</title>
		<body>Step one : import CSV file ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/33330880-0c35b784-d42e-11e7-8b19-4a80b41c7f7d.png)  Step two : create a new code system ("99LAB") ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/33330895-1909f042-d42e-11e7-9a67-f675f8544dc8.png)  Step three: assign "99LAB" to values with no code system ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/33330931-37556aea-d42e-11e7-8a46-9fc0f27ce5d5.png)  Step four: remove the "empty" code system from Source Code System - now the code system of my two firt values changed automatically to wrong values ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/33331005-6af4f190-d42e-11e7-8e8f-b3af28a5c6b6.png)  Step five: remove the second "empty" code system, now the code systems for my two first values changed again and I get multiple code systems (comma separated) in my second value ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/33331087-a58ea4f4-d42e-11e7-9b93-9ff9a9def3c6.png)   [HL70291_USL-2.zip](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/1510709/HL70291_USL-2.zip)   </body>
		<created>2017-11-28 16:27:15</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 21:27:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2676</id>
		<title>Code system changed to (random?) value after CSV import and removing empty code systems</title>
		<body>Step one: import CVS file where some codes do not have code system (this looks good) ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/33330225-4d9da634-d42c-11e7-8342-3f4874630b0a.png)  Step two: remove one of the "empty" code systems from the Source Code Systems on the top  Result: the empty code systems in the table are automatically changed to another value ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/33330372-b1d13c9c-d42c-11e7-817f-85957fd74af7.png)  I would leave the Code System as empty in the table (not randomly pick a value) with the "CodeSystem is required" message </body>
		<created>2017-11-28 16:14:38</created>
		<closed>2018-02-16 21:20:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2671</id>
		<title>Deleting a data type</title>
		<body>I created a data type flavor in a master data type library, made a few changes and then deleted it (right click in the navigation pane on the left side). The data type was deleted, but in the main editing pane, the data persisted (even with the Save button lit up). Saving doesn't do anything, but it's confusing that the data persists  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/33150398-decc1296-cf98-11e7-8f6f-81119c97c293.png)  When I try to navigate away to a different data type, I get the usual pop up.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/33150461-2a32487c-cf99-11e7-9c20-19b47c1886bc.png)  Once a data type has been deleted, the data shouldn't persist.</body>
		<created>2017-11-22 21:24:59</created>
		<closed>2018-01-04 19:32:30</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2650</id>
		<title>Dave - can't delete clone IGs</title>
		<body>From Dave "I have made quite a few intermediate clones of the IG.  I tried to delete one that I no longer need, but it always fails to delete.  "  I tried to delete a clone ant it worked for me. I asked him for screen shot of the error. Here it is:  ![clone](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32788289-d4999bea-c926-11e7-8c7f-e5c8ec521668.png)     </body>
		<created>2017-11-14 15:30:55</created>
		<closed>2017-11-22 17:40:52</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2649</id>
		<title>Dave -- trademarks symbols in IGAMT</title>
		<body> I try to add registered trademarks symbols to IGAMT, but the export is adding weird characters, see yellow.  Thanks, Dave     This material includes SNOMED Clinical Terms® (SNOMED CT®) which is used by permission of the International Health Terminology Standards Development Organization (IHTSDO). All rights reserved. SNOMED CT was originally created by The College of American Pathologists. "SNOMED®" and "SNOMED CT®" are registered trademarks of the IHTSDO.    </body>
		<created>2017-11-14 15:24:54</created>
		<closed>2017-11-14 15:41:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2648</id>
		<title>Dave - The page cannot be displayed because an internal server error has occurred.</title>
		<body>Other links are working. Why this one is not?  Hi Sandra, This seems to be a broken link supplied by IGAMT for this value set, NHSNHealthcareServiceLocationCode - Healthcare Service Location (NHSN)  https://phinvads.cdc.gov/vads/ViewValueSet.action?oid=2.16.840.1.113883.13.19    The page cannot be displayed because an internal server error has occurred.            </body>
		<created>2017-11-13 16:19:08</created>
		<closed>2017-11-14 16:35:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2647</id>
		<title>Mead -- V/S binding broken</title>
		<body>I just tried to update the value set Birth Attendant titles by making it a flavor.  I deleted the prior reference, deleted the value set, and re-added the value set.   However, when I tried to then link it to the observation it belongs to – LOINC 73764-3 – I get the message that the value set binding is broken.  Can you check to see what this is?</body>
		<created>2017-11-13 15:28:05</created>
		<closed>2017-11-22 17:41:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2646</id>
		<title>Deleting and re-adding V/s Issue - Mead</title>
		<body>From Mead: "In order to update my IG, I need to delete many value sets, and re-add them as flavors.  I am hitting a snag with PHVS_BirthAndFetalDeathFinancialClass.  It will not allow the deletion, and says it is referenced in my two PV1 flavors.   But, I see no reference there, and I did remove the reference from the FC_BR data type.  Is this a bug?     </body>
		<created>2017-11-13 15:22:07</created>
		<closed>2017-11-22 17:41:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2634</id>
		<title>Sharing IG error</title>
		<body>I was able to share between my accounts fine, but when I tried to shared with Dave I got this error:  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32452478-a1b26b16-c2e7-11e7-883b-b5d46001f336.png) </body>
		<created>2017-11-06 16:44:20</created>
		<closed>2017-11-22 17:41:03</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2633</id>
		<title>Cardinality error captured while adding the Profiles in GVT</title>
		<body>This error was not captured when trying to push to GVT, but when trying to add the Profiles in GVT  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32377599-9021ae9a-c07e-11e7-9fb7-85f6d016119b.png)  I was told is a carnality issue. The IGAMT "verify" functionality is not reporting this issue.  </body>
		<created>2017-11-03 14:08:00</created>
		<closed>2017-11-03 16:37:04</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2630</id>
		<title>Value Set Delta -- hitdev</title>
		<body>I can't select two value set to compare </body>
		<created>2017-11-01 21:27:58</created>
		<closed>2017-11-14 16:37:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2626</id>
		<title>Share IG is not working</title>
		<body> Tried to share IGs from my old account (CDCvr) to Smartinez (new account). No IG appears in my new account. </body>
		<created>2017-11-01 14:39:48</created>
		<closed>2017-11-01 20:55:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2623</id>
		<title>Value set export -- no working properly</title>
		<body>Using Testing IG. in dev server. Value set configuration setting: ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32233087-f9a8c638-be2f-11e7-896a-5325191c3708.png)  Se "Enable configuration" and selected 3 value sets ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32233130-0e79f82a-be30-11e7-937e-79b127d6c47e.png)  This is the export, notice that 0002_TXT is there twice, and is exporting value set that are not selected and are bounded.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32233145-1d4317ba-be30-11e7-858f-646a849488bb.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-31 15:43:32</created>
		<closed>2017-11-01 20:39:36</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2621</id>
		<title>Manage Accounts -- </title>
		<body>  https://github.com/haffonist/igamt  </body>
		<created>2017-10-31 14:37:38</created>
		<closed>2017-11-01 20:57:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2616</id>
		<title>Syndromic export to GVt failed</title>
		<body>&lt;img width="1147" alt="screen shot 2017-10-30 at 1 28 47 pm" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/32185708-6443798a-bd76-11e7-96e6-d799aa853d8f.png"&gt; </body>
		<created>2017-10-30 17:30:14</created>
		<closed>2017-11-09 19:45:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2615</id>
		<title>Adding PhinVads value sets - duplicate value sets </title>
		<body>The tool is adding a duplicate of every phinVads value set selected, </body>
		<created>2017-10-30 14:45:13</created>
		<closed>2017-10-30 18:00:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2611</id>
		<title>Added value sets are not saved</title>
		<body>Per Dave: I added several PHVS value sets:  PHVS_HeightUnit_UCUM, PHVS_BloodPressureUnit_UCUM, PHVS_DrugProduct_FDA_NDC, PHVS_EmergencyDepartmentAcuity_CDC, and they work fine in the guide, but when I save and come back into the guide later they are no longer in the list of value sets, and when I go into the guide I see a bunch of messages about "Value Set binding is broken", see below.   I tried adding them back and everything was good again.  But then they were gone again next time I came back into the guide.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32172735-08a1cf50-bd53-11e7-83df-ac7408a6ac8a.png)   Thanks, Dave    </body>
		<created>2017-10-30 13:17:09</created>
		<closed>2017-10-30 17:59:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2604</id>
		<title>2.0.0-beta8: Value set Configuration - "Max Number of codes to export" not working</title>
		<body>I set the Max Number of codes to export to 23. In the value set summary I only checked one value set to be exported, this value set had more than 200 codes.   The export shows 0 codes.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32122606-eab75a62-bb2e-11e7-9b79-cb9f9af96214.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-27 19:55:46</created>
		<closed>2017-10-27 21:05:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2602</id>
		<title>GVT export issue</title>
		<body>I get an error when trying to export one of my edos composite profile to GVT ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/32122145-5fa66824-bb2d-11e7-9d54-b91ba85cdfcd.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-27 19:42:34</created>
		<closed>2017-11-09 19:45:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2601</id>
		<title>Co-constraint Export configurantion is not appplied</title>
		<body>I click "Apply" get out and when I go back to configuration. the selection is not there, like it was not applied.   </body>
		<created>2017-10-26 20:45:29</created>
		<closed>2017-10-27 21:19:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2600</id>
		<title>2.0.0-beta8-production: Save is not working in the Conformance Profile section </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-10-26 18:34:04</created>
		<closed>2017-11-15 21:58:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2599</id>
		<title>2.0.0-beta8 -- Issues exporting Value Sets</title>
		<body>Checked the "All HL7 unbounded" and "All custom Unbound"  in the configuration. They were not exported.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32068473-73e97562-ba54-11e7-9af4-ac5df89c9469.png)  Then, I went to the value set "Export Summary" section and clicked on "Export". Exported the IG now all the value sets are exported. ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32068681-dc9e9178-ba54-11e7-9026-a9801f04c031.png)  Then, I unchecked the "Export" box in the value set "Export Summary" section. Left the configuration intact, "All HL7 unbounded" and "All custom Unbound". Now, **NONE** of the value sets were exported at all. </body>
		<created>2017-10-26 17:54:46</created>
		<closed>2017-10-30 18:00:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2598</id>
		<title>Rel. 2.0.0-beta8- Verify generating wrong error</title>
		<body>The usage is "R" and it is saying that the selected usage is "X". See image.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32067517-85801932-ba51-11e7-924d-9fe60778ef2e.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-26 17:28:59</created>
		<closed>2017-10-27 20:58:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2597</id>
		<title>2.0.0-beta8 --- Value Set - All code selection is not working</title>
		<body>All codes selection is not happening when I clicked on the top square to select all codes.    ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/32014708-de50590c-b98c-11e7-805c-de98b08808ff.png)</body>
		<created>2017-10-25 18:04:10</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 18:10:02</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2596</id>
		<title>Testing - Release 20.0.0-beta8 - CS - Drag and drop not working </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-10-25 17:27:04</created>
		<closed>2017-10-27 21:17:53</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2593</id>
		<title>Can't Export Testing_IG (Testing in hitdev) </title>
		<body>![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31951389-f9625df8-b8ab-11e7-9e3a-b67d79c38274.png)  I am able to export other profiles. @maxence-lefort Could you check why I can't export this one? </body>
		<created>2017-10-24 15:11:53</created>
		<closed>2017-10-26 17:56:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2589</id>
		<title>Fix co-constraint export</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-10-23 21:40:14</created>
		<closed>2017-10-30 18:00:41</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2578</id>
		<title>Only specified value sets should be exported</title>
		<body>Only specified value sets should be exported independent of the configuration.</body>
		<created>2017-10-20 18:50:55</created>
		<closed>2017-10-30 17:58:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2577</id>
		<title>Value set Flavor -- missing original code system (2.0.0-beta7)</title>
		<body>The original HL70007 value set had a code system in each code.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31832705-fd8a1bbe-b595-11e7-8515-f0632ae7537a.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-10-20 16:56:12</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 15:09:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2576</id>
		<title>Delete Value set with no Cross Reference - wrong title</title>
		<body>It looks like this issue was also in the previous release.  Look at the message. There is no cross reference in this value set. Delete works.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31830289-c257ebaa-b58d-11e7-9376-f42ef3495725.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-20 15:58:22</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 18:18:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2573</id>
		<title>Data type Library list -- incorrect title f</title>
		<body>Selected a published user data type library. Selected a data type and click a on the "Data Type" column and selected a DT. This is the screen I am getting. The title is incorrect.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31828032-312795aa-b587-11e7-9ad3-61dd489ecd51.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-20 15:11:10</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 19:21:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2570</id>
		<title>Edit Library - did not updated the library Title</title>
		<body>Edited the library to "MyDTlib"  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31826024-e7b9f958-b581-11e7-903f-979fcd5b6248.png)  But, name was not updated in "My Libraries" still showing original title "MyMasterDTlib  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31826081-15080710-b582-11e7-949d-f72f6f52c1b3.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-10-20 14:34:08</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 18:15:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2561</id>
		<title>Filter ON - Data type Info not displayed on right panel</title>
		<body>When I turn the filter "On" and select a data type nothing happens on the right panel. See error in console:  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31778053-a66f82f2-b4bd-11e7-87fd-fa7949f908d5.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-19 15:07:40</created>
		<closed>2017-11-14 20:52:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2555</id>
		<title>I can't delete a Profile component</title>
		<body>![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31620714-f750b97a-b265-11e7-956c-ff0e511dcba6.png)  This PC is not used in any Composite Profile.  </body>
		<created>2017-10-16 15:37:58</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 18:59:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2553</id>
		<title>Release notes are not available</title>
		<body>![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31617899-7613fd6a-b25e-11e7-9b64-46c56c60f6ec.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-16 14:41:06</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 17:02:35</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2552</id>
		<title>Bound DT don't show up correctly in Segment element</title>
		<body>This used to work. -- Rob  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31564324-6a608554-b030-11e7-9d3a-695c2db131fd.png)   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31564330-6f075ac4-b030-11e7-973f-0639cb2d78c3.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-13 20:06:35</created>
		<closed>2017-10-23 19:20:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2551</id>
		<title>Remove date for HL7 Data type, value set and segments</title>
		<body>The tool is assigning the date when the base datatype was imorted in IGAMT. The flavor should be updated to the date it was actually created— Rob</body>
		<created>2017-10-13 20:05:04</created>
		<closed>2017-10-23 19:22:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2550</id>
		<title>Dynamic Mapping</title>
		<body>The tool allowed to create more than one dynamic mapping for the same data type. This should not be allowed. </body>
		<created>2017-10-12 18:37:25</created>
		<closed>2017-10-23 19:05:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2547</id>
		<title>Datatype flavors in co-constraint table are missing from profile viewer, no validation done</title>
		<body>Datatype flavors used only in the co-constraints are missing from the profile viewer and validation is not done against them. Try the Vital Records Death Reporting IG -- XAD_OL  </body>
		<created>2017-10-11 21:25:55</created>
		<closed>2017-10-12 19:40:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2545</id>
		<title>Co-constraint validation on CWE with conditionals</title>
		<body>The co-constraint generated does not take into consideration a presence check, it only check that OBX-5.1 have a code in the value set provided. It fails to perform correct validation when CWE is defined as followed:  Woo is looking into it and will apply a solution after a discussion on Monday.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31458822-36f10f7e-ae8f-11e7-9a38-14076144211b.png)     </body>
		<created>2017-10-11 18:22:22</created>
		<closed>2017-12-13 21:20:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2542</id>
		<title>Validation not ignoring big value sets</title>
		<body>Alaina is validating the Vital Records messages in TCAMT. She is getting ICD-10 errors. This is one of the value sets that are currently highlighted in IGAMT "This table has too many codes (more than 1000), so it will be ignored".    The validation is not ignoring this value set and is generating these errors. They should be excluded from the validation.  OBX_VR_CCOD-CoConstraint-14-2 - [CoConstraint-14-2]If the value of OBX-3[1] (CWE) is '80356-9','then the value of OBX-5[1] (varies) should be one of codes in PHVS_CauseOfDeath_ICD-10_CDC' .</body>
		<created>2017-10-10 16:20:39</created>
		<closed>2017-11-09 14:43:45</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2541</id>
		<title>Single code</title>
		<body>Modify the logic CodedElement Datatype like CWE will have "single code” per Rob’s request.</body>
		<created>2017-10-10 15:18:49</created>
		<closed>2017-10-11 18:48:45</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2536</id>
		<title>Add Value Set form CSV is not working</title>
		<body>I can't save after choosing the CSV file.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31235929-b18c5794-a9c0-11e7-9985-3aa22453c71d.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-05 15:31:40</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:31:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2535</id>
		<title>Fix verification service</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-10-05 14:13:30</created>
		<closed>2017-10-30 18:00:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2534</id>
		<title>Value set Deta not working</title>
		<body>I can't select from any of the tabs.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31230877-500f0bfe-a9b3-11e7-96ac-bd0124a5b3a4.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-05 13:55:48</created>
		<closed>2017-10-20 17:38:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2533</id>
		<title>Value set exported twice</title>
		<body>See image: ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31192884-77d10a96-a910-11e7-83a2-6f33dcd924e1.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-04 18:31:25</created>
		<closed>2017-10-24 15:03:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2531</id>
		<title>New value sets are not been exported</title>
		<body>Created a new value set, binded to PID_TXT-15. The binding is displayed in the export, but the value set does not appear in the value set section.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31190097-1f405704-a908-11e7-8299-617e00832d0c.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-04 17:31:51</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:31:37</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2530</id>
		<title>"Apply Code System for Selected Code" tab not highlighted when a code is selected</title>
		<body>When a code is selected, the "Delete Codes" and the "R P E" tabs are highlighted, but the "Apply Code System for Selected Code" is not, it should also be highlighted.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31188160-050998f6-a902-11e7-9ffa-fc6c1a99d3e0.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-04 16:51:34</created>
		<closed>2017-10-10 17:59:44</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2526</id>
		<title>Export allows errors in the IG if a verify is not performed</title>
		<body>If the user does not run a verify and there are errors, for example carnality errors, the exported IG will include erroneous carnality. Is this the intention or should an automatic verify  be performed during the export and alert the user or don't allow the user to proceed with the export until these errors are fixed? </body>
		<created>2017-10-04 14:18:08</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:42:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2525</id>
		<title>Adding a comment to a segment flavor at the message level</title>
		<body>The comment was intended for MSH_TXT. The comment box indicates that the comment is for the MSH.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31180162-e3ae58d8-a8eb-11e7-9047-f504311ff26d.png)  In the Export there is no indication that the comment is for the MSH_TXT segment.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/31180262-2c20d8f2-a8ec-11e7-8f0b-3ae50ffdaabd.png)    </body>
		<created>2017-10-04 14:10:33</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 18:57:52</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2523</id>
		<title>Export - Configuration</title>
		<body>Not sure what does the "Duplicate OBX datatype value when no flavor has been selected" do. I did not provide a flavor in one of my co-constraints and  I get the same results when this box is checked, in both cases the column is greyed out. </body>
		<created>2017-10-03 19:17:51</created>
		<closed>2017-10-31 14:58:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2515</id>
		<title>Change "Edit" Predicate to "Replace" Predicate </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-10-02 17:53:27</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:31:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2509</id>
		<title>Fix notification popup</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-10-02 15:44:00</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:31:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2507</id>
		<title>Can't change the usage when it's conditional</title>
		<body>I create a data type and set the usage to C and created a predicate. Now I can't change the usage to any other value. The pencil icon allows you to edit the predicate, but the "x" icon doesn't seem to do anything.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/31079645-f1012a5c-a74b-11e7-8c51-50372ed5ca0a.png) </body>
		<created>2017-10-02 13:31:40</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:31:37</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2505</id>
		<title>Value Set Bindings Location needs to use segment name</title>
		<body>When exporting in Word, in the message section, the Value Set Bindings table doesn't use the segment name in the Location column. So rather then seeing the much more useful "MSH", you just see a number representing the segment number (1 in this case). See the red arrow below. The segment name has to be used. I don't think that you need to repeat the message type (ACK^Varies^ACK in this case) but can just go with the segment and field (MSH-15).   As well, the table should be organized by location. MSH-3 should be above MSH-15 and MSH-16.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/31033459-be674d56-a525-11e7-9413-03c3296aca66.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-29 19:55:16</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 19:54:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2488</id>
		<title>"Discard Changes"  and "Save and Continue" not functioning</title>
		<body>See inspection. I can recreate if you like.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30972108-a9dc3278-a437-11e7-8dd9-06627471f46b.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-28 14:28:44</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:24:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2482</id>
		<title>Unable to clone the VRDR IG</title>
		<body>I was able to clone other IGs, but not the "HL7 Version 2.6 Implementation Guide-Vital Records Death Reporting, Release 1 - US Realm". It looks like the issue is with the IG. Could this be also the reason why we can't push the TP to GVT from TCAMT? @Jungyubw I had already shared this IG with you via IGAMT.</body>
		<created>2017-09-27 14:29:25</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:20:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2481</id>
		<title>I can't edit a conformance predicate</title>
		<body>The tool still does not allow to edit a conformance predicate. I will have to delete and then add it, the capability to edit is there, but the predicate is not even displayed to edit it. </body>
		<created>2017-09-26 15:48:34</created>
		<closed>2017-12-01 16:28:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2480</id>
		<title>Verify not generating error when cardinality is incorrect at the CP level</title>
		<body>It is working when I do it at the segment level , but not at the Conformance Profile Level. </body>
		<created>2017-09-25 19:46:01</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:20:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2479</id>
		<title>Create IG - IG Document Meta data</title>
		<body>"Save" button not activated when updating the cover picture.  If I update any other subtitle "save" is activated.  Then and only then I am able to save the image.</body>
		<created>2017-09-25 19:31:10</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:16:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2464</id>
		<title>co-constraints in a Profile Component</title>
		<body>I was unable to save the co-constraint table in the profile component. The "Save" button not activated  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30716573-88b1d66a-9ee8-11e7-9499-bd52e7a2385b.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-21 20:19:15</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:19:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2444</id>
		<title>Login page: Not validation error.</title>
		<body>Also  Add space between forgot password and create new account</body>
		<created>2017-09-18 18:26:12</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:18:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2443</id>
		<title>Cannot logout </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-09-18 18:24:30</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:19:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2437</id>
		<title>Composite Profile - single value selected not displayed in GVT</title>
		<body>I selected a single value from a value set when creating a Profile component.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30498466-dd2058f2-9a24-11e7-82ca-6fd8055ad3e1.png)  But, the GVT is showing the following.    ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30498450-cd0eac66-9a24-11e7-9482-eb301f88f7b3.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-15 18:49:17</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:31:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2434</id>
		<title>DTM flavors are not been exported</title>
		<body>Here a screen shot of IGAMT showing the DTM flavors:  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30490459-037a8aee-9a08-11e7-99af-e415d80806b2.png)   Here a screen shot of the export -- not showing the DTM flavors ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30490424-e1966128-9a07-11e7-81fa-098a176f20dc.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-15 15:25:03</created>
		<closed>2017-09-19 20:36:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2433</id>
		<title>GVT Profile viewer and IGAMT data type  inconsistency</title>
		<body>This is a screen shot from IGAMT -- notice the DT column.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30444696-cc53b934-9951-11e7-92bb-33695d80565c.png)  Screen shot from GVT -- Notice the DT for MSH. What is ST_ForDM21221_2-6?  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30444760-fc79a47a-9951-11e7-99b4-5defcfe5c015.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-14 17:39:29</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 15:47:22</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2432</id>
		<title>Adding Fields -- not showing in GVT profife viewer</title>
		<body>I added a new field and it is not showing in GVT profile viewer. </body>
		<created>2017-09-14 17:16:05</created>
		<closed>2017-09-14 17:32:53</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2430</id>
		<title>Adding Fields - I can't add Constant value nor VS binding</title>
		<body>See image:  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/30439544-1688e80e-9942-11e7-8c9f-ea8617f823d9.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-14 15:47:07</created>
		<closed>2017-09-21 18:38:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2429</id>
		<title>Constant value update - not saved</title>
		<body>I added a constant value, save it and made a modification. The tool is not saving the update, it comes back with the original value after saving it. </body>
		<created>2017-09-14 14:54:20</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:19:03</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2427</id>
		<title>Search Api: No length</title>
		<body>![screen shot 2017-09-13 at 2 38 50 pm](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/30394543-5cd01f50-9891-11e7-9b41-a6ee75848902.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-13 18:39:42</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:49:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2426</id>
		<title>Save button not working - Value set Definition </title>
		<body>I can't save the updates made to the value set definition. I deleted some codes, but could not save the changes. </body>
		<created>2017-09-13 18:37:01</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:17:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2419</id>
		<title>Search not showing results</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-09-11 16:30:58</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:19:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2411</id>
		<title>Value set's Type always display independent of configuration values</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-09-08 19:18:20</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:42:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2406</id>
		<title>Length is exported as NA if not available</title>
		<body>The basic approach of the Immunization IG is that we are silent on Optional fields. I went into IGAMT and removed all the Length and Conformance Length values for optional fields.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/30220023-8962f248-9483-11e7-8741-7485c84b8fdf.png) But when I export it, the export contains NA rather than just being blank for the Length. Note that the Conformance Length seems OK. ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/30220060-abddd090-9483-11e7-979d-42a70daa0420.png)  Unless it's bad practice to remove the lengths in IGAMT, if they are removed, they shouldn't show up in the export.</body>
		<created>2017-09-08 15:52:59</created>
		<closed>2017-09-08 20:48:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2404</id>
		<title>When external is confirmed no redirection</title>
		<body>We should redirect user to the structure tab when user confirm</body>
		<created>2017-09-08 14:20:16</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:41:22</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2403</id>
		<title>Wrong url naming</title>
		<body>This is not a source URL but instead Object URL as we agreed.    &lt;img width="1019" alt="screen shot 2017-09-08 at 10 15 48 am" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/30215672-be4a3f5c-947e-11e7-9b99-bc9f8a286683.png"&gt;   When the external dialog open the URL should be name : "Reference URL" </body>
		<created>2017-09-08 14:17:12</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:41:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2402</id>
		<title>External Value set confirmation dialog </title>
		<body>No validation error provided when email is invalid.  Provide validation message when no or invalid email is provided.   </body>
		<created>2017-09-08 14:15:24</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:41:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2401</id>
		<title>Fix Value set "Apply Code System for Selected" </title>
		<body>The button should always be present but disable when no code is selected. Users need to know that the functionality are present.    When Apply code system all the button disappear and the "Select All" check box is selected.    Please fix ASAP </body>
		<created>2017-09-08 14:10:20</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:16:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2384</id>
		<title>Hot fix export when co constraints model is broken</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-09-06 21:21:32</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:38:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2377</id>
		<title>Constraints.xml unique key violation (ByID)</title>
		<body>There are duplicates in the constraints file that are not allowed. ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/30082436-c748628c-9258-11e7-945a-41d5e3d3a5c1.png)  Files come from my LRI IG, exporting Composite profiles (I selected all of them).  [LRI-R2-CompositeProfile_20170905_160708.zip](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/1278852/LRI-R2-CompositeProfile_20170905_160708.zip)  </body>
		<created>2017-09-05 20:42:02</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:40:41</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2376</id>
		<title>Export to GVT fails</title>
		<body>Working with the LRI R2 IG. I am trying to export the base Conformance profile only (did not try with composite yet). ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/30078488-61b01364-924b-11e7-9df6-b14846fbe516.png) </body>
		<created>2017-09-05 19:04:23</created>
		<closed>2017-09-05 20:37:53</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2362</id>
		<title>Cloning a co-constraint row </title>
		<body>I am trying to change the DT in OBx-2 column after cloning a row in the co-constraint table. The tool adds the DT, does not replaced the existing one.  ![coconstraintclone](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/29879230-8259bfd0-8d72-11e7-988d-0740a944cfad.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-30 15:01:57</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 19:52:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2359</id>
		<title>Profile component predicate dialogs not opening</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-29 15:59:42</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:31:43</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2340</id>
		<title>PHINVADS web service is not populating predef</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-28 16:09:18</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:36:56</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2331</id>
		<title>Unreferenced segment, value sets, data types are being exported in XML </title>
		<body>we should not xml export any unreferenced data object. </body>
		<created>2017-08-25 18:27:04</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:37:03</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2315</id>
		<title>Co-constraints OBX-2 flavors in Export </title>
		<body>Notice that a flavor was not assigned in the co-constraint table and the export is displaying a flavor assignments.  ![co-constraintflavors1](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/29621529-02434146-87ef-11e7-9c25-151c4d3fbb4c.png) ![co-constraintflavors2](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/29621540-0d160c7a-87ef-11e7-8c8b-246b925d2a21.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-23 14:39:33</created>
		<closed>2017-08-24 19:53:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2314</id>
		<title>Importing value set from csv  does not work</title>
		<body>Nothing happens after I select my file in the file system</body>
		<created>2017-08-23 13:59:17</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:37:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2312</id>
		<title>GVT validation on co-constraint dynamic mapping</title>
		<body>Co-constraint dynamic mapping validation is not working at all.  </body>
		<created>2017-08-22 18:48:17</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:37:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2310</id>
		<title>can't delete comments added to the message</title>
		<body>I had a comment on the ERR segment in my ACK message profile. I want to delete it, but the "x" icon doesn't seem to be working. I added a new comment to see if I could delete a different comment, but that one won't delete either. I have been able to delete comments added as part of the segment definition.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29575762-1fc966ba-872b-11e7-8cbb-f762ff62c61b.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-22 16:17:03</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:31:37</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2306</id>
		<title>duplicate value set export</title>
		<body>Sorry if this is a duplicate to a previously reported issue, it seems vaguely familiar.  Some value sets are being exported multiple times. I suspect that it may be because they are listed in co-constraints in multiple OBX segments.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29567890-2daaa2ce-8714-11e7-986b-d6aec4852f76.png)   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29567966-781b6ec4-8714-11e7-8560-0c7e28bb5b99.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-22 13:32:58</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:27:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2305</id>
		<title>Add value set description</title>
		<body>There is room for a Description when selecting a value set to bind but it's not populated. It would be helpful if it was populated with the value set name, especially where there are different flavors of value set based on the same HL7 table.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29567109-d1366944-8711-11e7-8130-95f66d5e3cdd.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-22 13:15:16</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:34:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2303</id>
		<title>Save button doesn't light up when removing DefinitionText</title>
		<body>If all you do is remove existing Definition Text, there is no way to save that change because the Save button doesn't activate nor do you get the "are you sure you want to do this?" popup when navigating away from the page.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29533871-725edcc8-8679-11e7-87f4-a97019fe18b5.png)  see red arrow and green box below  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29533959-c2c4f6b6-8679-11e7-9795-f1ee6fc5dabc.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-21 19:05:54</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:34:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2302</id>
		<title>Conformance Statement ID generation</title>
		<body>I used the new "constant value" option in the segment definition (red box below)  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29533000-7403553a-8675-11e7-8e7d-2532b7a8d8f7.png)  And it generated Conformance Statements, but it auto-generates the Conformance Statement ID which are then different than the format I used elsewhere. I like the idea of specifying it in the segment definition table but I don't want to have different ID formats.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29533155-40a06a10-8676-11e7-8eaa-0829aa9be02b.png)  We should talk about CS ID generation. Should they all be manual or all be automatic? </body>
		<created>2017-08-21 18:41:00</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:39:26</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2294</id>
		<title>Order of segments in IG style export is not alphabetical</title>
		<body>When I export in IG style, the list of segments is not what I expected. I would have expected it to be in alphabetical order. I sort of looks like they are being exported in the order of appearance in profiles, but I think it makes more sense to be alphabetical given that some profiles use the same segments but profiles sometimes use different flavors of segment. For example, I think it makes more sense for the two OBX segment flavors to be groups in the segment section.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29525977-f65b89ce-8659-11e7-92ef-0e01ae93c2ca.png)  I think in profile export mode, it does make sense to export them in the order in which they appear in the message definition.</body>
		<created>2017-08-21 15:23:18</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:35:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2293</id>
		<title>V/S Missing from Export</title>
		<body>Per Mead: " I am looking for the value set PHVS_BirthAndFetalDeathFinancialClass_NCHS.  It is cited multiple times within the IG text, is included within the value set list for the tool, but does not appear within the export.  Can you see the reason why?"  This is on the HL7 Version 2.6 Implementation Guide: Vital Records Birth &amp; Fetal Death Reporting Release 1  IG.</body>
		<created>2017-08-21 14:46:07</created>
		<closed>2017-08-31 18:07:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2290</id>
		<title>Types within Types_ B missing from export</title>
		<body>Per Mead: One thing I am looking for is to be able to define data type flavors for components within a data type.   These do not seem to come through on the export.  I am attaching my most recent.   Look for HD_BR_AA, and SAD_BR.   Both are declared within the tool, used within data types – you can see the references in the export, but not actually exported.   I had thought this was a feature to be included.  Am I mistaken there? [HL7-Version-2.6-Implementation-Guide--Vital-Records-Birth--Fetal-Death-Reporting-Release-1---US-Realm-5898caa884ae9be46ff21abc_20170817_155419.docx](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/1235534/HL7-Version-2.6-Implementation-Guide--Vital-Records-Birth--Fetal-Death-Reporting-Release-1---US-Realm-5898caa884ae9be46ff21abc_20170817_155419.docx) </body>
		<created>2017-08-18 20:01:54</created>
		<closed>2017-08-31 18:08:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2286</id>
		<title>Order of fields scrambled in segment after I hit RESET</title>
		<body>I made some changes, then hit reset here's the result: ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/29463657-72adcd44-8401-11e7-8a15-57e146f291aa.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-18 14:39:44</created>
		<closed>2017-08-18 18:00:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2280</id>
		<title>Another value sete repeating values</title>
		<body>look at PHVS_BirthReportingValueType_NCHS.  It is repeating some, but not all values.</body>
		<created>2017-08-17 19:34:13</created>
		<closed>2017-08-29 19:17:26</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2279</id>
		<title>Word export freezing</title>
		<body>Per Mead, "when  I try to get the document out of protected mode so I can navigate, Word freezes and then refuses to go on.    This may be related to the fact that the document appears to have field values that are linked to other files.  That is something that I urge the IGAMT team to remove"</body>
		<created>2017-08-17 18:46:49</created>
		<closed>2017-08-29 19:18:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2276</id>
		<title>Delete confirmation is missing buttons</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-16 17:02:34</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:32:56</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2256</id>
		<title>Co-constraint data type are repeated in the export </title>
		<body>The export is showing repeated DTs. </body>
		<created>2017-08-16 13:41:10</created>
		<closed>2017-08-16 13:44:18</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2254</id>
		<title>Clicking on "Leave" from the confirmation dialog does not refresh the table definition.</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-16 13:34:58</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:33:13</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2250</id>
		<title>Fix duplicate DT in the export</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-16 13:15:46</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:32:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2244</id>
		<title>Remove varies data type from exported document </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-15 21:54:34</created>
		<closed>2017-08-17 14:44:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2224</id>
		<title>Create predicate should show the creation dialog and not the edit dialog </title>
		<body>When a user click on create predicate. The fist page display the existing predicate. It shouldn't.  </body>
		<created>2017-08-15 19:44:51</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:39:52</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2220</id>
		<title>Missing conformance statements at Group level in the export</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-15 19:11:09</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:29:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2201</id>
		<title>remove date column in comment table for the export </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-15 16:56:58</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:28:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2198</id>
		<title>Fix code export in word and html</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-15 16:36:33</created>
		<closed>2017-08-15 18:28:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2172</id>
		<title>Search is missing columns and rows</title>
		<body>When searching HD, The first component is missing, column length is missing.  @maxence-lefort please fix ASAP. The result should not depend on the configuration.   </body>
		<created>2017-08-14 19:12:58</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:30:30</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2169</id>
		<title>Next button doesn't do anything</title>
		<body>We creating a new IG, the pop-up box includes a "Next" button, but clicking it doesn't do anything. You have to directly click on "Message Events" to switch screens (I assume that is what "Next" should do). I suggest you either enable the button or remove it completely (I don't have a strong preference which one you do although the "Message Events" is pretty easy to miss)  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/29285384-f5893408-80f3-11e7-89f2-ef489342f740.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-14 18:26:52</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:26:48</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2162</id>
		<title>Duplicated Value Sets </title>
		<body>for some versions we have the some hl7 value set duplicated. for the version 2.5.1 we have some hl7 value sets with an extension  </body>
		<created>2017-08-14 15:17:58</created>
		<closed>2017-08-29 14:33:25</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2160</id>
		<title>Export - Comments</title>
		<body>- [x] Why comments are duplicated (in the message table &amp; in the comments table)  - [x] Invalid date in the comments table</body>
		<created>2017-08-14 14:46:44</created>
		<closed>2017-09-01 16:18:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2158</id>
		<title>Export - Conformance statement</title>
		<body>- [x] Remove bullet point before Message/Group  - [x] Replace 'Id' by 'ID' (upper case)  - [x] Order by id  - [x] Discuss MSH conf statements with Craig</body>
		<created>2017-08-14 14:32:36</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:28:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2147</id>
		<title>PHINVADS value sets are changed</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-11 13:20:53</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:33:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2146</id>
		<title>Changing datatype root in segment does not work </title>
		<body>The select button does not become active  ![screen shot 2017-08-11 at 8 45 59 am](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/29213523-9a27778e-7e71-11e7-8db0-a0850de9d93a.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-11 12:47:06</created>
		<closed>2017-08-15 15:02:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2139</id>
		<title>delete value set but I can't save</title>
		<body> How do I know it was saved? How does the user know? In fact, was it?</body>
		<created>2017-08-10 17:48:48</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 14:18:48</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2135</id>
		<title>GVT profile viewer not displaying all the CS</title>
		<body>It looks like the issue is in displaying the CS in the profile viewer. The validation is ok. </body>
		<created>2017-08-10 14:10:59</created>
		<closed>2017-12-13 21:28:29</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2130</id>
		<title>value set check buttons</title>
		<body>What is the purpose of these buttons? When I check them and then click on R, P, or E I expect those to change accordingly but nothing happens? IS it only for deleting? It should be both functions. I seen other users do the same thing I do. Change to support R/P/E.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14874904/29171405-8509b258-7daa-11e7-8950-b74a62bc6c3b.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-10 13:03:36</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 15:13:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2127</id>
		<title>Add Segment/Group/Field</title>
		<body>@Abdelghani90 This functionalities were working fine until you refactored them to use material.   When Adding a new item the position are wrongly set.  Please fix ASAP.      </body>
		<created>2017-08-09 23:41:02</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 14:57:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2113</id>
		<title>CP edit pencil is a delete??</title>
		<body>I clicked on this to edit because it has the "O" and "C" and it wants to delete, I just want to edit. IF I can't edit then this need to be a delete. We need to discuss this workflow....  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14874904/29133742-74866c3a-7d02-11e7-8da5-9a35eb5bd388.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-09 16:59:49</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 15:12:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2112</id>
		<title>Usage GUI sometimes has 2 usages</title>
		<body>I've only seen it happen with C but might occur in other circumstances. If a refresh enough it goes away, but after it is first done you get 2 usages in the cell.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14874904/29133027-207a63c8-7d00-11e7-8cf4-cee4ab75fc37.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-09 16:43:46</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 14:56:56</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2110</id>
		<title>Composite profile co-constraint is wrong</title>
		<body>Created a profile component on OBX from message tab  Created a co-constraint   The generated co-constraint on the composite profile looks like:  ![coconstraint](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/29130164-058efa3c-7cf7-11e7-9c6b-02f3f9e21945.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-09 15:36:53</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 15:08:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2109</id>
		<title>Make default profile component tab to be Message</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-09 15:31:59</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 15:06:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2107</id>
		<title>Cannot change Composite profile description</title>
		<body>I tried changing this, it allows me, but when I save it goes back to what I had…</body>
		<created>2017-08-09 14:55:54</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 15:10:26</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2106</id>
		<title>I can't delete a segment from the profile</title>
		<body>I added a segment for testing purposes. I am not able to remove it. </body>
		<created>2017-08-09 14:42:43</created>
		<closed>2017-08-10 16:33:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2105</id>
		<title>Profile Component- adding OBX segment flavor and modifying co-constraints</title>
		<body>the functionality is there, but I can't make any modifications to the co-constraint table. </body>
		<created>2017-08-09 12:49:43</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:19:35</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2102</id>
		<title>Usage column for segment in profile component</title>
		<body>I don't think the usage for a standalone segment in profile component makes sense ?  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/29086323-35bdab66-7c40-11e7-8fea-859354212fe1.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-08 17:48:49</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:32:03</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2101</id>
		<title>Add Segment - not shown in GVT profile viewer</title>
		<body>I added a segment and connected to GVT. The segment is not in the GVT profile viewer. </body>
		<created>2017-08-08 17:04:26</created>
		<closed>2017-08-09 15:57:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2100</id>
		<title>Fix latency on conformance statements</title>
		<body>@Abdelghani90 this is high</body>
		<created>2017-08-08 14:06:57</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:33:44</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2096</id>
		<title>Discard button not working </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-08-07 18:47:50</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 15:03:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2087</id>
		<title>Fix Delta</title>
		<body>Delta is not comparing the elements of the same position. It seems it is comparing them by index.  </body>
		<created>2017-08-07 17:48:44</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 14:56:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2085</id>
		<title>XML export not working</title>
		<body>I get a page with this:   {"text":"internalError","skip":false,"resourceId":null,"manualHandle":"false","version":null,"scope":null,"date":null,"id":null,"type":"danger"}</body>
		<created>2017-08-07 16:35:45</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:36:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2084</id>
		<title>GVT export not working (null pointer exception)</title>
		<body>![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/29036234-9bdccaa0-7b6c-11e7-93a7-b7f42020dd59.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-07 16:33:47</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:36:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2083</id>
		<title>Cannot find datatype error</title>
		<body>I started to get that error message again today (I didn't for a while, but now it's back) It happens when I try to select the conformance profile in the left menu.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/29032480-82375b2c-7b5f-11e7-9989-fe947869e2a9.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-07 15:01:22</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 14:57:02</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2082</id>
		<title>Duplicate value sets ?</title>
		<body>I am not sure where the duplicates come from ? The cross reference feature does not seem to work, so I can't check if they are all in use in my IG ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/29032233-b52dd458-7b5e-11e7-8d53-b25b49a371a9.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-07 14:54:43</created>
		<closed>2017-10-02 14:17:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2081</id>
		<title>Error on server when trying to work on value sets</title>
		<body>I get the error every time I select a value set from the menu on the left. ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/29032114-509a2bb8-7b5e-11e7-986c-6843d8e81f6c.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-07 14:51:23</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 15:05:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2079</id>
		<title>GVT validation - OBX-3.1 co-constraint errors</title>
		<body>Why is the validation generating all these errors when OBX-3.1 is removed from the message?  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/28975108-d22d2afe-7906-11e7-94b6-9353c725b0f2.png)   @HossamT use the same profile files I e-mailed you on Monday. </body>
		<created>2017-08-04 15:21:24</created>
		<closed>2017-08-29 19:40:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2073</id>
		<title>Delta functionality - </title>
		<body>Notice how the IG title overlays the Data type column  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/28935367-5409ffd0-7852-11e7-9a59-107cf60170cf.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-03 17:52:12</created>
		<closed>2017-08-31 19:35:13</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2072</id>
		<title>Duplicate dataype in "change datatype root" dropdown menu</title>
		<body>Sometimes I see duplicate values ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/28935096-59bf4044-7851-11e7-9513-627805e21f78.png) </body>
		<created>2017-08-03 17:40:58</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 14:56:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2067</id>
		<title>Change registration page</title>
		<body>Change in the tool the "Submit" button to "Register" because it is not an application and there is no approval.  Also change e-mail notice below and maybe what is sent to the user. Otherwise it is confusing. Just state they are register and can begin to use the account.  I know this is different for other tools like IGAMT. </body>
		<created>2017-08-02 14:35:12</created>
		<closed>2017-08-09 14:34:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2065</id>
		<title>GVT - Constraint failure on OBX segments</title>
		<body>The value of OBX-1 is correct.. Why the tool is generation this constraint error?   | IZ-20 - The value of OBX-1 (Set ID - OBX) SHALL be valued sequentially starting with the value '1'. -- | --   OBX|1|CE|64994-7^Vaccine funding program eligibility category^LN|1|V05^VFC eligible - Federally Qualified Health Center Patient (under-insured)^HL70064||||||F|||20120701|||VXC40^Eligibility captured at the immunization level^CDCPHINVS OBX|2|CE|30956-7^vaccine type^LN|2|88^Influenza, unspecified formulation^CVX||||||F OBX|3|TS|29768-9^Date vaccine information statement published^LN|2|20120702||||||F OBX|4|TS|29769-7^Date vaccine information statement presented^LN|2|20120814||||||F</body>
		<created>2017-07-31 18:09:22</created>
		<closed>2017-08-29 19:49:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2064</id>
		<title>GVT - Constraint validation Failure</title>
		<body>I am getting the following constraint falilure, but the value of RXA-2 in the message is correct:     | IZ-29 - The value of RXA-2 (Administration Sub-ID Counter) SHALL be '1'.   RXA|0|1|20120814||33332-0010-01^Influenza, seasonal, injectable, preservative free^NDC|0.5|mL^MilliLiter [SI Volume Units]^UCUM||00^New immunization record^NIP001|7832-1^Lemon^Mike^A^^^^^NIST-AA-1^^^^PRN|^^^X68||||Z0860BB|20121104|CSL^CSL Behring^MVX|||CP|A </body>
		<created>2017-07-31 18:04:57</created>
		<closed>2017-08-08 14:44:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2062</id>
		<title>Composite Profile - IG Style Export </title>
		<body>I created a composite profile using a profile components with an item (MSH_1) selected at the message level. Added a comment to the field. The output is showing the comment in various places in the composite profile definition and it also appears in the MSH-1 field . See image.    ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/28683331-30f68b64-72ce-11e7-897e-9c294193b54c.png) </body>
		<created>2017-07-27 17:22:08</created>
		<closed>2017-10-25 18:28:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2061</id>
		<title>Composite Profile - Definition (NULL text in Export)</title>
		<body>If not definition is provided in the metadata to a Composite Profie, the export show the world "null". It should not display any text.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/28636227-7afedeb4-720b-11e7-8da1-86e6049cd1d3.png) </body>
		<created>2017-07-26 18:06:00</created>
		<closed>2017-08-31 19:46:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2054</id>
		<title>Configuration - Preference (Co-constraint table in Export)</title>
		<body>Currently, the exported Co-constraints table is not showing the OBX-2 value when  a flavor is not assigned in the co-constraint table. But, when a flavor is assigned in the OBX-2 (DM_Flavor) column, the export shows both columns. Rob, will like to see a "Preference" choice to be added to the Export configuration.  See attached figure. Please, discussed with Rob for final approval. For now, when a flavor is not assigned the export could grey out the OBX-2 flavor column.   ![config](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/28543024-6c93313e-708c-11e7-8761-46d341c64e5f.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-07-24 20:26:15</created>
		<closed>2017-09-01 14:26:02</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2051</id>
		<title>Conformance Statement can be lost</title>
		<body>If you add a Conformance Statement in the Data Type library but don't click the "Save" button, it is possible to navigate to another data type without getting a warning that there is unsaved data, and then when you come back, the Conformance Statement has been lost  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/28468978-5f06b156-6dfa-11e7-88df-11601d3ba3ae.png)   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/28469053-9ddc814e-6dfa-11e7-98dc-6c0b6c86bd0e.png) </body>
		<created>2017-07-21 14:54:43</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:54:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2049</id>
		<title>drag and drop in CS editor doesn't work in all cases</title>
		<body>When I work on my laptop, if the node in the context tree is high up in the tree (so high that the whole constructor box isn't visible at the bottom of the window), then it's not possible to drag and drop it into the node section.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/28423420-959de1a0-6d30-11e7-9288-bda1832fe0a6.png)  When I try and to drag and drop the node, nothing fills in at the bottom (I can't reveal the place where I have to drag the node to: ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/17408249/28423215-10ce71f6-6d30-11e7-89fe-e2bccaaa681c.png) </body>
		<created>2017-07-20 14:49:05</created>
		<closed>2017-08-29 14:20:24</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2028</id>
		<title>New tabs data is wrong</title>
		<body> Under conformance statement, there is the CP and I can't see my conformance statement.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14874904/28186557-a12d9c00-67e9-11e7-942a-f240f3170ba7.png) </body>
		<created>2017-07-13 20:38:45</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:54:03</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2024</id>
		<title>profile component dynamic mapping should appear only for obx</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-07-13 18:30:29</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:05:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2020</id>
		<title>wierd undefined in pending requests </title>
		<body>See the data type info on the top  &lt;img width="1356" alt="screen shot 2017-07-12 at 9 07 50 pm" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/28146228-3efd2e9a-6746-11e7-97b7-6b4922dccec9.png"&gt; </body>
		<created>2017-07-13 01:08:28</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:05:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2019</id>
		<title>misleading pending requests under share Elements</title>
		<body>Under share elements, the list of datatypes are under pending requests. This is misleading as there are no pending requests.    &lt;img width="1413" alt="screen shot 2017-07-12 at 9 05 52 pm" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/28146240-53ccb37c-6746-11e7-89b6-0d385d2d5539.png"&gt;      We should have two sections in the order as follow  |&gt; Shared  (Number as badge)      HD_1.....      HD_2.... |&gt; Pending (Number as badge)      ST_1.....      CWE_2....   </body>
		<created>2017-07-13 01:07:32</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:05:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2018</id>
		<title>Clicking on Library list does not display list of library </title>
		<body>When I move from Editing a library and select the list of library, nothing get displayed</body>
		<created>2017-07-13 01:04:38</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:35:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2017</id>
		<title>Hiting Enter Library List open dialog </title>
		<body>When I hit the search input, the following dialog displayed.   &lt;img width="864" alt="screen shot 2017-07-12 at 9 02 42 pm" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/28146131-82c0b4c2-6745-11e7-8a93-851911c3f8d3.png"&gt; </body>
		<created>2017-07-13 01:03:28</created>
		<closed>2017-08-14 14:57:04</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>2016</id>
		<title>Data type Library: editor issue </title>
		<body>&lt;img width="1172" alt="screen shot 2017-07-12 at 9 00 45 pm" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/28146099-496cce5e-6745-11e7-846d-f377dea1d951.png"&gt; </body>
		<created>2017-07-13 01:01:47</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:15:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1945</id>
		<title>Can't add a segment</title>
		<body>This functionality is confusing. I click on "Add Segment" and the "CREATE SEGMENT" pop up looks like only lets the user add a field in an existing segment. But still if I try to add the field,  it does not let me add it.  Am I missing something?  </body>
		<created>2017-06-28 13:09:38</created>
		<closed>2017-07-25 15:27:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1941</id>
		<title>Profile component no applied on certain segments</title>
		<body>I defined several items in my profile component for the "OBR" segment (OBR_LRI flavor) ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/27559605-1a4ed63e-5a8f-11e7-8b8e-8f7ba5536429.png)  Here's what I get in my composite profile: ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/27559686-7a6e4c84-5a8f-11e7-8c3a-926f9a675ac6.png) ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/27559701-8aa9ed92-5a8f-11e7-8255-90c2d8409d8a.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-06-26 20:50:42</created>
		<closed>2017-06-29 15:14:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1940</id>
		<title>XML constraint file issues</title>
		<body>I created a composite profile and exported as XML. I see a few issues: - I have two MSH segment contexts in my constraint file (the one from the composite profile and the one from the original conformance profile) - there is a conformance statement missing from my composite MSH (id = MSH_GU_FRU_1_2-5-1)  IGAMT screenshot of the "original" MSH ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/27559161-8a1a6c96-5a8d-11e7-8a54-d1c97e7e8ffa.png)  The LRI-6 conformance statement is missing from the constraints associated with "MSH_GU_FRU_1_2-5-1"  [LRI-CompositeProfile_20170626_162024.zip](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/1103440/LRI-CompositeProfile_20170626_162024.zip) </body>
		<created>2017-06-26 20:40:48</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:29:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1937</id>
		<title>Adding a Predicate at the message Level</title>
		<body>I can't select a group as a context. Also, when I select the message as the context I get a notice that the message was selected, when I unselect the message this notice is still displayed.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/27556732-bdb55e70-5a84-11e7-8861-9d18bf6a1863.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-26 19:33:04</created>
		<closed>2017-07-13 13:47:02</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1935</id>
		<title>A draggable icon in the wrong element location</title>
		<body>I am adding a CS to a segment. There is a draggable icon next to the segment, but the segment can not be dragged.    ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/27553721-1ab89390-5a7a-11e7-88fc-7f55612e6c56.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-26 18:17:25</created>
		<closed>2017-07-25 15:28:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1926</id>
		<title>Unable to select segment in delta from segment definition </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-23 21:28:24</created>
		<closed>2017-07-07 18:05:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1918</id>
		<title>Search ACK only by message type</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-23 19:25:32</created>
		<closed>2017-06-26 14:31:18</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1914</id>
		<title>Navigating between Data type libraries tab sometime does not show list of libraries</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-23 18:46:45</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:29:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1913</id>
		<title>Export data type library first page issue </title>
		<body>![screen shot 2017-06-23 at 2 40 45 pm](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/27495959-13cec23e-5822-11e7-9d1b-f3d03d40f8de.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-23 18:41:56</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:05:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1911</id>
		<title>Validate create data library inputs </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-23 18:27:43</created>
		<closed>2017-06-23 18:50:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1901</id>
		<title>Fix create new IG Document dialog</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-23 16:34:03</created>
		<closed>2017-07-10 21:41:26</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1900</id>
		<title>Selected Value set in Profile component does not show in the Value Set/Single Code column</title>
		<body>![screen shot 2017-06-23 at 11 44 31 am](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13695248/27489671-676c4146-5809-11e7-9578-bb32ba9723fa.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-23 15:45:29</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:29:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1899</id>
		<title>Can't delete a v/s binding to a field after adding additional value sets </title>
		<body> I was able to delete before adding the additional value sets. </body>
		<created>2017-06-23 14:26:51</created>
		<closed>2017-06-23 18:47:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1898</id>
		<title>Can't save the Definition Text in Segment Panel</title>
		<body>There is no way to save and the text entered is gone when closing the  window.. </body>
		<created>2017-06-23 14:09:42</created>
		<closed>2017-08-18 15:34:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1897</id>
		<title>Can't add a Conformance Statement at the message level in a Composite profile</title>
		<body>The tool does not allow to create a CS  at the message level in a Composite profile.   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/27484247-89e07a16-57f6-11e7-914a-fcf6a05a3c3f.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-23 13:31:26</created>
		<closed>2017-06-23 14:30:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1895</id>
		<title>Check save button in Profile Component panel</title>
		<body>I click the save button, nothing happens. When I move from the panel I get to save it in the "Confirmation" pop up "SAVE AND CONTINUE"</body>
		<created>2017-06-23 11:57:44</created>
		<closed>2017-07-10 14:55:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1893</id>
		<title>Not able read a file in GVT</title>
		<body>I am using GVTdev. Getting "IOError could not read this files" when I try to save from GVT in the "Add Profiles" panel. </body>
		<created>2017-06-23 11:23:31</created>
		<closed>2017-07-10 15:04:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1891</id>
		<title>Co-constraints - wrong list of flavors for CNE</title>
		<body>The flavors listed for CN are not correct.  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/14842422/27479537-4ca72e24-57e2-11e7-9d89-b92d6542261c.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-23 11:05:42</created>
		<closed>2017-06-23 18:47:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1885</id>
		<title>Complex conformance statement id is not what I entered</title>
		<body>I entered "LRI-7" but it was changed into "OR(LRI-7-a, LRI-7-b)"  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/27453260-d20c00aa-5763-11e7-94ac-4543edfbfc70.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-22 20:00:23</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:34:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1884</id>
		<title>Datatypes imported via "upgrade to" do not show up in drop down menu</title>
		<body>The EI_GU v2 datatype was added to my IG via "UPGRADE TO" It does not show up in the dropdown menu if I want to manually change the datatype to EI_GU v2   ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/27452188-b8bde392-575f-11e7-914b-42181e4015d7.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-22 19:32:16</created>
		<closed>2017-06-29 15:14:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1883</id>
		<title>Cross-reference should also check for any reference in profile components</title>
		<body>It would be nice to also check if an element is referenced in a profile component.</body>
		<created>2017-06-22 19:13:01</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:29:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1880</id>
		<title>Composite profie not rendering expected results</title>
		<body>Created a Profile Component, where only segment was added (a flavor of MSH). I also added a conformance statement to that profile component. Created the composite profile using the profile component I just created. When I look at the composite profile definition I do not see the conformance statement I added nor the right MSH flavor. </body>
		<created>2017-06-22 18:54:36</created>
		<closed>2017-06-22 19:07:24</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1859</id>
		<title>Indent a little the right side content of the HTML export</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-19 19:12:26</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:07:13</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1858</id>
		<title>Fix HTML hide and show function</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-19 19:11:45</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:36:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1857</id>
		<title>Add paragraph lines in export </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-19 18:57:37</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:10:41</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1856</id>
		<title>Add NIST to version in IG Document</title>
		<body>NIST IGAMT 2.0.0-RC</body>
		<created>2017-06-19 18:47:20</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:07:16</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1839</id>
		<title>Field order in segment delta is not accurate</title>
		<body>The filed's order of one of the segments in the segment delta is messed up. Because of that, the delta does not compare the right fields and comes back with a lot of "differences".  ![image](https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/13591511/27091068-0d19f23a-502d-11e7-876e-6c8c8d696640.png) </body>
		<created>2017-06-13 15:40:59</created>
		<closed>2017-08-23 17:02:48</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1835</id>
		<title>Change + to edit pencil in profile component value set column </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-12 21:23:03</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:30:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1833</id>
		<title>Remove the integer type for cardmin and length, confLength </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-12 21:22:23</created>
		<closed>2017-07-10 18:31:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1831</id>
		<title>Fix checkbox when already selected in exporting to GVT </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-06-12 21:21:11</created>
		<closed>2017-06-23 17:49:51</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1830</id>
		<title>Fix the header of the table when exporting to GVT</title>
		<body>Headers are misaligned.  </body>
		<created>2017-06-12 21:20:46</created>
		<closed>2017-09-11 16:34:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1813</id>
		<title>complex CS ID is wrong</title>
		<body>Pretty sure we've seen this one before, but when creating a conformance statement, the ID that gets saved and displayed reflects the construction of the CS and not the ID specified by the author  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/26833867/48e454c0-4a99-11e7-83b3-254c188df849.png)  If you open up the editor again and delete the incorrect ID and replace it with a new one, that new one is saved in the editor but the construction is still displayed in the segment activity.</body>
		<created>2017-06-06 14:20:47</created>
		<closed>2017-06-23 18:50:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1803</id>
		<title>"greyCell" in export </title>
		<body>![screen shot 2017-05-31 at 2 42 10 pm](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13695248/26648116/65466eb6-460f-11e7-8194-44300276ae34.png) </body>
		<created>2017-05-31 18:43:03</created>
		<closed>2017-08-03 14:11:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1801</id>
		<title>Fix GVT login auto complete </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-05-31 18:15:18</created>
		<closed>2017-08-28 14:11:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1795</id>
		<title>Profile viewe: OBX-5 Length</title>
		<body>Length needs to be tied to the data type selected. ![obx5](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14842422/26633356/1e06be4e-45e1-11e7-9da1-baba84e8201a.png) </body>
		<created>2017-05-31 13:12:29</created>
		<closed>2017-07-10 15:58:33</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1776</id>
		<title>Issue with verify functionality</title>
		<body>I had a cardinality error on an "X" field. I fixed it, saved and verified again. The error is still showing. See attachment.   ![verify](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14842422/26465300/ace9d80e-4158-11e7-88cc-c07be54cf2a3.png) </body>
		<created>2017-05-25 18:46:07</created>
		<closed>2017-05-30 12:52:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1753</id>
		<title>Duplicate co-constraint errors generated</title>
		<body>The validation is generating two of the same co-constraint errors. Hossam reviewed the issue and cocluded that the constraint file has two constraints.  I am not sure if I reported this error to Woo.</body>
		<created>2017-05-22 18:42:29</created>
		<closed>2017-05-30 14:20:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1752</id>
		<title>Expecting to get an error because when value is excluded.</title>
		<body>I ran a test using the the Immunization ballot profile. In this profile the code 1002-5 in CDCREC-01 is excluded. PID-10 is binded to CDCREC-01 with binding strength “R” and Binding location “1” In the test message I included this code in PID-10.1.   I am expecting to get an error because that value is excluded. But the tool does not generate an error.   In this profile the binding location is in the xml file.    </body>
		<created>2017-05-22 16:31:38</created>
		<closed>2017-07-10 15:45:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1750</id>
		<title>exporting to GVT - Duplicate key value error</title>
		<body>I am getting this error when exporting to GVT: cvc-identity-constraint.4.2.2: Duplicate key value [DTM_S_2-6] declared for identity constraint "DatatypeKey" of element "ConformanceProfile".  In this profile dynamic mapping included mapping to a DT with many flavors. Not, if this is the cause of the problem or how this gets resolved. </body>
		<created>2017-05-22 15:10:56</created>
		<closed>2017-05-30 14:17:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1743</id>
		<title>Save button not lighting up</title>
		<body>I feel like I just saw a Github ticket for this recently, but I can't find one.  In IGAMT Dev, no matter what I do to a data type in the Master Data Type Library activity, the "save" button won't light up. When I navigate away from the data type, I do get the pop up asking if I want to save my changes, so the system knows that changes have been made, it just doesn't active the Save button.</body>
		<created>2017-05-19 18:43:15</created>
		<closed>2017-08-17 15:25:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1742</id>
		<title>Error description not displayed</title>
		<body>The tool is not allowing to see errors description after a verify.</body>
		<created>2017-05-19 17:34:27</created>
		<closed>2017-05-25 18:28:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1739</id>
		<title>Discard Changes is not working</title>
		<body>This happened before, I get no response when I select "DISCARD CHANGES" in the "Confirmation" panel. I had to click "CANCEL" to proceed. </body>
		<created>2017-05-19 12:47:46</created>
		<closed>2017-05-25 18:42:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1734</id>
		<title>Binding Location is missing</title>
		<body>PID-10 has a binding location = 1 but the tool is generating a "binding location is missing" alert.   Per Hossam, I confirm it’s an IGAMT issue, the PID-10 Field is the following :  &lt;Field Name="Race" Usage="R" Datatype="CWE_2-6" MinLength="0" MaxLength="705" ConfLength="NA" Binding="0005_TX_2-6" BindingStrength="R" Min="1" Max="*" ItemNo="00113"/&gt;  “BindingLocation” is missing. </body>
		<created>2017-05-18 18:15:18</created>
		<closed>2017-05-30 14:20:33</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1732</id>
		<title>Profile Component - predicates at MSG and SEG level</title>
		<body>Created a profile component at the segment level. Added a predicate, which IGAMT allowed. Created a Composite profile using the PC mentioned and reviewed the predicate. Description and assertions are incomplete and the panel is labeled CS instead of Predicate. Something is not right.   Also, IGAMT allowed to create a predicate at the message level. </body>
		<created>2017-05-18 12:12:49</created>
		<closed>2017-06-23 11:58:56</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1731</id>
		<title>All coconstraint values sets are gone</title>
		<body>I entered a large number of co-constraints for 3 different OBX segment flavors and now they are all gone.   This is the current screen shot. Note the lack of values anywhere in the OBX-5 or OBX-17 columns ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/26171888/25e0a538-3b0c-11e7-8ad8-a2ee98b881ba.png)   And here is what it looked like last time I exported the document. Note the presence of value sets in those same columns. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/26171943/50802f20-3b0c-11e7-94ea-6f7eb114c80d.png)  Please restore my value sets.   Now that we've produced two documents that have gone for HL7 ballot it's absolutely critical that issues like this don't come up. If I hadn't noticed this, we could have published a final document that was missing significant content relative to the balloted version. </body>
		<created>2017-05-17 19:25:18</created>
		<closed>2017-08-17 15:28:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1730</id>
		<title>Co-constraints validation</title>
		<body>The tool is generating two identical co-constraints errors. Hossam reviewed the constraint files and indicated that the constraints are there twice. </body>
		<created>2017-05-17 18:01:40</created>
		<closed>2017-05-30 14:20:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1680</id>
		<title>Profile Component - IGAMT Dev</title>
		<body>•Created a MSH flavor called MSH_TX –MSH-3 cardinality is [1..1], datatype HD_TX –MSH-5 usage R, dT =  HD •Created a profile component call PC1 –Added the element "MSH-5" from segment level •change the datatype to the "HD_TX" flavor.    **not able to select a data type** •Change usage to “RE”  •Create a composite profile using PC1 –Checked the  “Definition” to see the MSH-5 update.  **MSH-5 usage shows as “R” instead of “RE”** </body>
		<created>2017-05-03 17:38:10</created>
		<closed>2017-05-25 19:22:33</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1666</id>
		<title>Value Set column in Profile component Not exported</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-04-28 21:19:58</created>
		<closed>2017-05-08 14:10:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1665</id>
		<title>Can't export cloned IG to GVT</title>
		<body>Getting the following profile errors. Cloned VRDR IG trying to export the CREI profile to GVT. See attachment.  ![cloningig](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14842422/25544657/6bdb495e-2c29-11e7-9a60-7fe8d0d894e2.png)   </body>
		<created>2017-04-28 19:43:29</created>
		<closed>2017-05-30 14:20:52</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1657</id>
		<title>Export Composite Profile - Weird Description/Comment Column </title>
		<body>When there is no value on a column we should put the background in gray.  There is no row border for the Description/Comment column.   &lt;img width="871" alt="screen shot 2017-04-28 at 9 50 38 am" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13695248/25531587/4ef8f0ce-2bf8-11e7-8c17-18bb5849411f.png"&gt; </body>
		<created>2017-04-28 13:52:11</created>
		<closed>2017-05-01 13:54:18</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1656</id>
		<title>No conformance statement created, still conformance statement section was generated with empty content. </title>
		<body> We should have no section in that case.  &lt;img width="555" alt="screen shot 2017-04-28 at 9 41 34 am" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13695248/25531187/e29e8a34-2bf6-11e7-9b92-c8377950b163.png"&gt;   </body>
		<created>2017-04-28 13:41:59</created>
		<closed>2017-05-01 13:54:35</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1655</id>
		<title>Exported profile component not displaying changed value.</title>
		<body>Exported profile component not displaying changed value. &lt;img width="596" alt="screen shot 2017-04-28 at 9 38 07 am" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13695248/25531125/b1148446-2bf6-11e7-9689-d384f6435b4f.png"&gt; &lt;img width="935" alt="screen shot 2017-04-28 at 9 38 43 am" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13695248/25531126/b122bbce-2bf6-11e7-8530-ffab533df6b3.png"&gt;  </body>
		<created>2017-04-28 13:40:41</created>
		<closed>2017-04-28 14:08:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1648</id>
		<title>wrong list of libraries sometimes showing</title>
		<body>It appears that IGAMT remembers which library I was looking at last time I was logged in. If I am looking at my user data type libraries and then log out, when I log back in and go to the Data Type Libraries activity, it highlights "master data type libraries" (purple arrow) but the library list show is actually the user data type libraries.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/25500446/acdea980-2b54-11e7-8bcb-3b9854a8b1d3.png)  You can confirm this by moving to the user library list and then back to the master library list and you'll see the right list of master libraries (green arrow)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/25500545/069cc146-2b55-11e7-89eb-77dddf9f6892.png) </body>
		<created>2017-04-27 19:23:49</created>
		<closed>2017-06-22 17:31:51</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1646</id>
		<title>Bug in profile components / composite profile</title>
		<body>There is a bug when I create the composite profiles. The composite profile does not seem to be created.. Here's what I did: 1. Create my base profile (ORU_R01), with my segment flavors and my datatype flavors 2. Create my GU profile component 3. Add items to the GU profile component 4. Change the datatype of the items in the GU profile component 5. Create composite profile (ORU + GU), I choose the ORU_R01 as base and the GU profile component.  Now if I have just one composite profile, I am not able to see anything related to my ORU + GU (nothing happens when I select "ORU + GU" in the navigation tree. If I create a second composite profile (can be different from the first one), I have access to my "ORU+GU", but I can see something when wrong because I don't see the GU profile component in the structure tab and the metadata (Name/Description/Identifier) is empty.  ![oru gu](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13591511/25492322/b08e13a4-2b40-11e7-9f3b-249dd5b2badd.JPG)  Other composite profiles work perfectly, so I am not sure what I did to trigger that bug </body>
		<created>2017-04-27 15:58:24</created>
		<closed>2017-06-22 17:32:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1642</id>
		<title>Missing data type in GVT Profile Viewer</title>
		<body>It looks like the data type flavors assigned in the co-constraints table are not accounted as been referenced. </body>
		<created>2017-04-26 20:22:41</created>
		<closed>2017-05-31 15:29:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1639</id>
		<title>IGAMT - GVT Export</title>
		<body>The validation screen in GVT is not expanded. I have to refresh in order to get the full screen.  ![validation](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14842422/25451314/c438a150-2a8f-11e7-9bf4-489ebe183449.png) </body>
		<created>2017-04-26 18:51:16</created>
		<closed>2017-05-23 16:08:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1638</id>
		<title>IGAMT co-constraints and GVT export</title>
		<body>The constraint statement created from the co-constraints in IGAMT  is not expressing the co-constraints correctly.   [CoConstraint-13-2]If the value of OBX-3[1] (CWE) should be '69443-0','then the value of OBX-5[1] (varies) should be one of codes in PHVS_ContributoryTobaccoUse_NCHS' .</body>
		<created>2017-04-26 18:33:44</created>
		<closed>2017-04-28 19:39:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1608</id>
		<title>Export Profile Stype</title>
		<body>In the Vital Records Birth &amp; Fetal Death Reporting IG -- when I click on 3.1.1.1 Segment definition in the Table of Content, it placed me on 3.1.1.2 Segment definitions. It looks like the the section numbers are not matching. </body>
		<created>2017-04-20 16:29:32</created>
		<closed>2017-05-01 14:20:45</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1606</id>
		<title>Data Type Library won't export in Word</title>
		<body>In the dev IGAMT, I tried to export a master data type library in Word format and got the following:  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/25193467/d6835a78-24fc-11e7-8ed7-6cf6ac4484a9.png)  It exports fine in HTML format. I tried restoring the default export configurations for the data type library but it didn't make a difference.</body>
		<created>2017-04-19 17:37:58</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:30:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1591</id>
		<title>too much white space</title>
		<body>The export of Definition Text has too much white space. At max, there should be 1 line break between field descriptions, currently there are 3 line breaks. This is also an issue in the Data Type section.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/25098696/233dadda-236f-11e7-928c-6dc61b3009a9.png) </body>
		<created>2017-04-17 18:11:19</created>
		<closed>2017-05-12 14:07:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1590</id>
		<title>sections numbered incorrectly in Profile Style export</title>
		<body>The numbering of the sections in the Conformance Profile section is wrong. The Conformance Statements and Value Set Binding sections are too high, they should be under the segment that they are part of. For example, for MSH, 3.1.1.3 (Conformance Statements) and 3.1.1.4 (Value Set Bindings) should be under 3.1.1.2.1 or not be a section at all (just be a table). Either way is fine (I think previously they weren't their own section) but the current numbering is not right.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/25098569/b5ea4dec-236e-11e7-944a-2cf9529b96f3.png) </body>
		<created>2017-04-17 18:09:07</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:29:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1578</id>
		<title>Complex CS ID is not displayed</title>
		<body>I created a complex CS with a specific ID (red box below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/25051226/2bc324cc-2111-11e7-8f76-085ac3017711.png)  But when I added it, the ID was replaced by a description of the make up of the complex CS (purple box). ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/25051238/3d0da978-2111-11e7-9fc5-aec87bc499c4.png)  This issue persists even in the data type itself ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/25051250/5053fdf2-2111-11e7-807c-58a39b98ea88.png)  Having the description of the content isn't bad (it may be helpful in the editor (at least until the component CS are deleted)) but the author entered ID needs to used.</body>
		<created>2017-04-14 17:56:01</created>
		<closed>2017-05-30 14:17:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1554</id>
		<title>Errors exporting a Master Data Type Library</title>
		<body>I'm trying to export a master data type library and I'm seeing errors.  When I try to export to Word I see this: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24869330/86f75282-1dd8-11e7-8363-bd90f5f1fd43.png)   When I try to export to HTML I see this: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24869352/971e7e4c-1dd8-11e7-8457-2e57f5a8038b.png) </body>
		<created>2017-04-10 15:29:48</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:28:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1552</id>
		<title>Add Predicate button doesn't seem to work</title>
		<body>It doesn't look like the "Add Predicate" button works in the data type editor. I'm not sure that is wrong as I thought the Predicates were only added in the Data Type Definition. I'm not sure it should even be here. But one way or the other, it should either be removed or it should do something.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24865399/c0b9509e-1dcc-11e7-87d9-182d0d8db044.png) </body>
		<created>2017-04-10 14:05:07</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:25:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1549</id>
		<title>change to a library can be lost</title>
		<body>Make a change in a data type library but then, without saving, go back to the Data Type Library List using the button in the upper left hand corner (green box below) ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24863416/5333d540-1dc6-11e7-8bd0-1706057ce6d6.png)  And then open a different data type library ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24863459/8a28751a-1dc6-11e7-899a-389d604e4c2b.png)  And then go back to the original data type library and the change will not be there. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24863491/acfb3776-1dc6-11e7-807d-52123d73d23f.png)  The easiest solution is probably to add the standard "save changes" pop up that you get other places when you go back to the Data Type Library List ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24863551/e485e380-1dc6-11e7-99b1-695d9152efba.png)  Note that you can do a similar workflow in the IG document activity. The system responses similarly other than when you go to open the second document you get that confirmation popup so that the changes are not lost. that is a good thing, but I think it would be better if that popup showed up as you're changing to the IG document list (so earlier than it is now) and not when going to a new document (at which point there is no context for the author to decided which change is being referred to.</body>
		<created>2017-04-10 13:27:22</created>
		<closed>2017-06-22 17:35:13</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1546</id>
		<title>Meta data missing initially</title>
		<body>When a new data type library is created, the initial screen is the Metadata screen but some key fields (at least Title and Steward and possibly the general text box) are not populated in the display even though the data exists. In the example below, the red arrows indicate the missing data and the purple boxes show that a title and steward where entered when the library was created.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24862694/45ed6cb4-1dc3-11e7-98f4-d0234bc6f8df.png)  Note that if you move to a data type and then back to the Metadata tab (by clicking on the library name in the Table of Contents), then the fields are populated. It seems like it's just that initial display that is affected.</body>
		<created>2017-04-10 13:00:43</created>
		<closed>2017-06-22 17:38:25</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1540</id>
		<title>wonky export order in the value set binding table</title>
		<body>when I bound value sets to multiple locations in a single segment, when I exported them, they showed up in an unexpected order. In the example below, the bindings for ERR-3 (green box) came out below the bindings for ERR-4 and ERR-5 (red box). They should be in the order in which they appear in the segment.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24815038/5eccf8d4-1b99-11e7-89df-ec0d5bf30354.png) </body>
		<created>2017-04-07 18:54:14</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:19:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1535</id>
		<title>can't copy any IG in IGAMT dev</title>
		<body>On the Dev site, when I try to copy an IG, I get an error  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24811741/e98a4998-1b8c-11e7-9963-4fc530828721.png) </body>
		<created>2017-04-07 17:23:10</created>
		<closed>2017-06-01 14:37:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1532</id>
		<title>error during export on the dev site</title>
		<body>I tried to export an IG (both profile style and IG style) in the Dev site and get this error:  {"date":null,"version":null,"text":"internalError","resourceId":null,"manualHandle":"false","skip":false,"scope":null,"id":null,"type":"danger"}</body>
		<created>2017-04-07 17:10:06</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:48:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1454</id>
		<title>Value set missing from Export</title>
		<body>Per Mead: "I note that one of my value sets –birth and fetal death financial class – did not make it into the export.  It is referred to be a field within NK1, not by an observation."  SM: Is reference by FC_BR DT  and the Optional PV1_BR-20 </body>
		<created>2017-03-24 18:18:05</created>
		<closed>2017-04-03 14:00:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1425</id>
		<title>"optional" value sets being exported</title>
		<body>Even when the value set export configurations are as stripped down as the can get (only the default R, RE and C value sets), many extraneous value sets are still in the export (a few are highlighted with the red arrows below). These are just value sets the author will have to manually remove.   ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24054204/6eeda7cc-0b09-11e7-8e5d-c67cae402747.png)  It seems like the value sets are included because they have a usage of R, RE or C somewhere, even if the place they are used are itself optional. For example, value set 0004 is required in PV1-2 even though that segment is in an optional (patient visit) segment group (although PV1 is R within that optional segment group). ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24054363/ebbe0d6e-0b09-11e7-9085-4562ad4c5de4.png)  Similarly, value set 0051 is required in a totally optional segment (DG1)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24054405/10a61c3e-0b0a-11e7-8455-c815c644deb4.png)  I'm assuming table 0113 is included in the export because it is required in one of the places it's used (the DLD data type) ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24054069/f4ac03fa-0b08-11e7-808e-b2bc1e4191ac.png)  Interestingly, the DLD data type is only optional everywhere it's used: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/24054017/c8f1f30a-0b08-11e7-917b-e46f8913f6ec.png)  Overall, the export is still including value sets that are in some way, shape or form optional everywhere they are used. In my IG, I'm letting the document be silent on any element that is ultimately optional (keeps the size of the document manageable) and having these extra value sets is just more manual work that needs to be done.  I'm not sure what the solution here is. It may be to add a configuration to filter out value sets that are only used in data types/fields which are ultimately optional (this could be rather complex given how the building blocks of the HL7 message are put together) or it could be just an option to only export custom data types and filter out all HL7 base value sets (although this only works if we have a best practice to always use a custom value set anywhere that a value set is bound).  This topic probably warrants more discussion on a call.</body>
		<created>2017-03-17 17:09:02</created>
		<closed>2018-01-18 18:25:35</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1408</id>
		<title>Can't assign more than one value set in the co-constraints table</title>
		<body>Per Mead: in the OBX co-constraint section, the way value sets are chosen is totally different than when chosen at the the field level.</body>
		<created>2017-03-16 17:54:25</created>
		<closed>2017-04-03 14:00:36</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1406</id>
		<title>Co-constraints are gone from the IG</title>
		<body>Per Mead Walker: I just went back in to edit a couple of co-constraints within OBX, and it looks like they have disappeared.  I am attaching my most recent export so you can see what was lost.  The IG is: HL7 Version 2.6 Implementation Guide: Vital Records Birth &amp; Fetal Death Reporting Release 1 - US Realm</body>
		<created>2017-03-15 21:32:15</created>
		<closed>2017-04-03 14:00:18</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1372</id>
		<title>Segments and Fields usage for Profile layout</title>
		<body>Usage for fields and segments seems to be reverted in the profile layout</body>
		<created>2017-03-09 21:14:40</created>
		<closed>2017-03-17 14:22:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1357</id>
		<title>Can't Export the Vital Records Death Reporting IG in Word</title>
		<body>I am getting this error: {"text":"internalError","manualHandle":"false","resourceId":null,"skip":false,"date":null,"version":null,"scope":null,"id":null,"type":"danger"}</body>
		<created>2017-03-08 15:38:21</created>
		<closed>2017-03-17 15:36:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1343</id>
		<title>Export -- unexpected character (not pasted)</title>
		<body>Peer Mead: Here is a snip from the latest export: Information for a live birth, including that defined for both the facility and mother???s worksheet, is transmitted.  The interesting part is that this content is not pasted in, I entered it directly from the keyboard.   I think they need to add the special character – ‘ – to the list of supported ASCII characters. </body>
		<created>2017-03-03 17:03:44</created>
		<closed>2017-03-08 21:41:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1341</id>
		<title>Export: Segment Metadata - Comment - missing from export</title>
		<body>The Segment Metadata tab includes a place – Comment – to enter descriptive text for the segment or segment flavor.   However, this does not appear within the Word export.  It should.</body>
		<created>2017-03-02 21:26:50</created>
		<closed>2017-04-10 17:37:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1340</id>
		<title>Export: Diagrams too big</title>
		<body>The diagram is being blown up too big, so it does not fit on the page.    ![diag](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14842422/23526651/d877c312-ff60-11e6-9d4b-3912800a7b1d.png) </body>
		<created>2017-03-02 20:57:09</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:18:35</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1338</id>
		<title>The export is including the word "Subtitle" as part of the subtitle</title>
		<body>"Subtitle" should be removed.  HL7 Version 2.6 Implementation Guide: Vital Records Birth &amp; Fetal Death Reporting Release 1 - US Realm  **Subtitle** Standard for Trial Use 2017/03/02 15:18   HL7 VERSION 2.6 PUBLIC HEALTH AND EMERGENCY RESPONSE WORK GROUP </body>
		<created>2017-03-02 20:50:28</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:18:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1331</id>
		<title>Mechanism for Dynamic Mapping no longer available</title>
		<body>I am looking at the IG Mead Walker is developing and I do no see a mechanism to enter dynamic mapping in OBX-5. It was there before.  ![dyn](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14842422/23481771/a7bfe202-fe9a-11e6-911a-ecf92eea2d22.png) </body>
		<created>2017-03-01 21:18:34</created>
		<closed>2017-03-03 16:36:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1323</id>
		<title>Export - unexpected characters</title>
		<body>From the tool:   Information for a live birth, including that defined for both the facility and mother’s worksheet, is transmitted.  From the export:  Information for a live birth, including that defined for both the facility and mother?s worksheet, is transmitted. </body>
		<created>2017-02-24 19:23:47</created>
		<closed>2017-02-27 20:57:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1322</id>
		<title>Per Mead Walker - Export  is generating errors </title>
		<body>There are three styles, the IG style seems the one for me.    I think it crashed.   Here what I get:  {"text":"internalError","resourceId":null,"manualHandle":"false","skip":false,"version":null,"date":null,"scope":null,"id":null,"type":"danger"}  This sits in the following tab: https://hl7v2.igamt.nist.gov/igamt/api/igdocuments/5898caa884ae9be46ff21abc/export/docx/IgDocument  So I tried profile style – the same.  Table style took longer, and looks like it did download.   I am attaching a copy.  Note, I only put in some of the profiles.  It looks OK, but has none of the introductory text sections.  [Birth-Death-Report-IG-5898caa884ae9be46ff21abc_20170224_140730.docx](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/800273/Birth-Death-Report-IG-5898caa884ae9be46ff21abc_20170224_140730.docx) </body>
		<created>2017-02-24 19:21:12</created>
		<closed>2017-02-28 22:32:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1306</id>
		<title>Export config not working for table style</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2017-02-21 21:01:41</created>
		<closed>2017-02-22 14:47:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1305</id>
		<title>Conformance statement IDs don't appear to update immediately</title>
		<body>In the Data Type library activity, if you edit a conformance statement ID, it doesn't appear to immediately update. This can cause confusion for users as it appears that they changes were lost.  If we start like this: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23184055/cdea506e-f843-11e6-9f06-ff64cb488bf3.png)  And then make this change: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23184090/f7f06ee8-f843-11e6-9dd3-1f2508cff631.png)  After clicking "Save" in the CS editor, it still looks like this: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23184113/145e63e6-f844-11e6-8024-4472331d3b07.png)  But if you go to a different data type (forcing another save of the data type) and come back, the changes are visible: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23184154/43c1e996-f844-11e6-8469-e0ca4bdc6532.png) </body>
		<created>2017-02-21 20:45:23</created>
		<closed>2017-05-30 14:17:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1293</id>
		<title>Possible error in the underlying data base</title>
		<body>When I imported the DR data type from version 2.5.1 into a data type library, the two components has the DTM data type.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23075010/78254ad0-f500-11e6-843c-a7fd0dab90b0.png)  But if you look at the 2.5.1 base document (chapter 02A), the components have the TS data type. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23075051/a18cb782-f500-11e6-8371-05e3f134510b.png)  Because there are limits on how dramatically a user can change the data type, it's not possible to correct this issue in IGAMT manually.</body>
		<created>2017-02-17 17:03:53</created>
		<closed>2017-02-21 21:51:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1274</id>
		<title>duplicate HL7 data types</title>
		<body>If you go to change the data type of a component in a master data type, there are sometimes duplicate entries. For example, even though there is only a single FN HL7 data type in the Table of Contents (blue box), it's present twice in the drop down list twice (red arrow).  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23031258/f06e6786-f435-11e6-8ebb-133535df42fc.png)  I suspect while the Table of Contents is filtered to remove duplicate HL7 data types that are present in multiple MAS data types because if you look at an ST element,the list is much longer (as would be expected given the relatively greater abundance of ST versus FN).  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23031398/7411e82e-f436-11e6-8753-a5b45ee4430b.png) </body>
		<created>2017-02-16 16:55:59</created>
		<closed>2017-03-17 15:11:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1273</id>
		<title>Definition Post-Text doesn't work for master data type libraries</title>
		<body>When you click on the Definition Post-Text, you don't get the box to enter in your text.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/23030965/f9ec0774-f434-11e6-8005-550d7821e184.png) </body>
		<created>2017-02-16 16:46:23</created>
		<closed>2017-02-18 01:24:18</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1269</id>
		<title>Missing Usage Note in master type library</title>
		<body>In the Master Library activity, when defining a new data type, there is a spot for a Usage Note, but the text box to enter a usage note is not there, it's just blank white space.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22994557/f45b71b2-f38c-11e6-88f8-c367a82f9f86.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-02-15 20:44:21</created>
		<closed>2017-02-18 01:25:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1261</id>
		<title>competing text</title>
		<body>In the data type library activity, there is some overlapping text in the Data Type MetaData tab (see red box below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22985147/301c5eca-f36d-11e6-941e-ddaa09c41643.png) </body>
		<created>2017-02-15 16:56:04</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:36:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1231</id>
		<title>Usage changes does not shown in Profile Compoent</title>
		<body>I select and item, change the usage, but nothing appears in the usage column.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14874904/22896219/32f50f6a-f1ed-11e6-9e44-b2347f1c19b7.png) </body>
		<created>2017-02-13 18:07:02</created>
		<closed>2017-04-03 14:37:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1190</id>
		<title>Complex Constraints - deleting a "ForAll" selection</title>
		<body>I am not able to delete one of the constraints from my "ForAll" complex constraint list.  I have to reset and start all over again. </body>
		<created>2017-01-31 19:23:04</created>
		<closed>2017-05-25 19:25:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1184</id>
		<title>CP location for segment contains both "-" and "."</title>
		<body>When exporting segment level conditional predicates, the location contains both a dash and a period. Given that this is segment level, the dash is appropriate and the period should be removed.   Conditional Predicates for data types seem to use the correct delimiter (a period).  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22475723/7d6566e6-e7a5-11e6-95e9-af449a9b6ed6.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-31 17:09:18</created>
		<closed>2017-02-18 01:24:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1182</id>
		<title>Conformance Statement and Conditional Predicate Sections export segment not segment flavor</title>
		<body>When an IG has multiple flavors of a segment, the conformance statement and conditional predicate sections at the very end of the document labels the various tables with the Segment Name without the Extension, so it's not possible to tell which CS or CP goes with a particular segment flavor. The extension needs to be exported  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22475402/7e19fae4-e7a4-11e6-9c06-5ef3c49c0702.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-31 17:03:21</created>
		<closed>2017-02-18 01:23:48</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1181</id>
		<title>Tables in Definition Text isn't exported well</title>
		<body>If an author puts a table in a Definition Text, when it's exported to a Word document, the borders of the table are not included. Nor is the header row formatting. It's a table and the borders can be added manually in Word, but Tables in Definition Text and in the normal text boxes export differently.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22475189/c6e37abc-e7a3-11e6-812d-d1f49fb74c36.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22475271/0dfb693c-e7a4-11e6-8dea-a1bea87ccafd.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-31 16:57:50</created>
		<closed>2017-02-18 01:23:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1178</id>
		<title>Usage of segment groups is not exporting correctly</title>
		<body>The Usage of a segment group in a conformance profile is being exported as "0" (zero) rather than the actual usage.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22473085/2c9d352a-e79d-11e6-972a-c85eebebfe9f.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22473110/426359b6-e79d-11e6-8f9a-4104880cd50a.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-31 16:09:16</created>
		<closed>2017-02-18 01:23:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1175</id>
		<title>apostrophe's still don't export right</title>
		<body>It looks like we still have the issue with apostrophe's not always exporting properly. The original ticket (1102) is closed but I don't see a resolution in it.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22471374/c568432c-e797-11e6-9ba1-884be3036a12.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22471528/35419a4a-e798-11e6-9403-e402da824691.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-31 15:33:09</created>
		<closed>2017-02-15 15:54:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1174</id>
		<title>value sets are not listed in data types</title>
		<body>when a value set is bound to a part of a data type, the value set is not listed in the data type definition screen. It's there (if you click the pencil icon, it shows up in the pop-up) but it doesn't show to the author.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22471034/ca08c27c-e796-11e6-8ffa-e224a6fb2593.png)   Oddly, if you edit the value set bound in the data type, then it does show up. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22470995/aa84fbfa-e796-11e6-9e93-55662051ac6d.png)  ideally, bound value sets should always be displayed as they are for segments.</body>
		<created>2017-01-31 15:22:56</created>
		<closed>2017-06-01 14:36:36</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1173</id>
		<title>value set cross-reference doesn't always work</title>
		<body>Value set cross-referencing seems to work when the value set is linked to a segment, but not when it is linked to a data type.   For example, 0091_01 is linked to RCP-2 and it shows up: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22470717/c6bbc58e-e795-11e6-813f-4fbe3f2b1c40.png)  However 0200_01 doesn't have a cross-reference even though it's part of the XPN_01 data type ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22470760/ed23c05a-e795-11e6-936e-0ef693f0f2d2.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22470830/1a141f06-e796-11e6-8721-74dd60ab95f3.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-31 15:18:06</created>
		<closed>2017-03-03 14:44:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1160</id>
		<title>upon export, some tables have extra white space</title>
		<body>In some tables (but not all of them apparently), upon export to a Word document, there are extra line breaks which adds white space to the table. For example, compare the table in IGAMT to the table in Word. the red arrows indicate places where there are extra line breaks and white space. It's easy enough to remove, but I'm not sure where they are coming from in the first place.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22430824/0cdd254c-e6d5-11e6-8edd-2be4a3914959.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22430758/d1c7949c-e6d4-11e6-9500-50515a2b55f9.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-30 16:16:00</created>
		<closed>2017-04-24 14:30:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1146</id>
		<title>Export - Fix TOC for segments within the profiles</title>
		<body>In Verbose mode, the segments within the conformance profile aren't linked in the TOC</body>
		<created>2017-01-26 15:01:46</created>
		<closed>2017-01-30 12:22:53</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1140</id>
		<title>Segments not being exported</title>
		<body>I'm still seeing that some segments in the message profile definition aren't being exported in verbose mode. In the example below, the OBX_IZ_01, PRT and NTE segments in the Observation_Group are not being exported. This may make sense for PRT and NTE because they occur earlier in the message are exported (sections 3.1.1.2.15 and 3.1.1.2.16) but OBX_IZ_01 is unique from the base OBX segment (section 3.1.1.2.14) and needs to be exported.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22307669/9c62d312-e309-11e6-9ed2-f3a30caa05ff.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-25 20:24:48</created>
		<closed>2017-01-30 12:22:25</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1139</id>
		<title>Export  conformance length and length rules</title>
		<body>For hl7 version &lt;=  2.5.1 - No conformance length column - if data type is complex then no length should appear (Gray background) - If data type is simple then show length  For  hl7version &gt; 2.5.1  - Length and conformance length columns should always appear - if data type is complex then no conformance length and length should appear (Gray background) - If data type is simple then show conformance length and length  For all versions  - For ending group use gray background for usage, cardinality , length etc...    </body>
		<created>2017-01-25 16:51:53</created>
		<closed>2017-01-30 20:54:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1128</id>
		<title>"code" format doesn't export well</title>
		<body>When formatting text as "code" it is possible to use multiple lines in the formatted text, but when the text is exported, the line breaks are just represented by a "?" and the lines run together. It's not easy to enter multiple lines in a code formatted text section, but there are a number of different way to do it, so if authors can do it, the export needs to be able to support it.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22222628/39b179d6-e17d-11e6-9525-ca152e499849.png)   ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22222561/f84cc93c-e17c-11e6-8cef-52a8294130a0.png)   ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22222602/1f98812a-e17d-11e6-8ca7-3de9f2f0e111.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-23 21:06:28</created>
		<closed>2017-04-03 14:18:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1127</id>
		<title>data type name format</title>
		<body>Sorry if this is a duplicate. I feel like we discussed it before.  I think the convention is that data type element identifiers are the data type, a period and then the sequence ID. So the first component of CWE is CWE.1. In the current exports a dash is used rather than a period.  Also note that in the export, there is no space between the data type element name (CWE-1) and the colon separator and the description (Identifier). This makes it a bit difficult to read and Microsoft Word questions it (blue underlining). It would be better if there was more white space (see the second screenshot below to see how it looks in the segment section)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22216478/dd7b2d00-e164-11e6-9cc8-4b863fad8185.png)  The convention for segment elements is the segment name, a dash and then the element number. So the first field in PID is PID-1. The export use the right bits and pieces, but seems to have extra space between them (PID - 1 as opposed to PID-1).  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22216589/495ed63e-e165-11e6-845d-c92c8cc9d073.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-01-23 18:15:50</created>
		<closed>2017-01-25 15:40:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1125</id>
		<title>section number breaks down in the Conformance Profile section</title>
		<body>When exporting the conformance profile section in verbose mode, the number of the sections is off. When Pre-Definition text exists for a segment, it gets moved up in the section hierarchy rather than down. In the example below, the Pre-Definition text for the QPD_IZ segment should be section 3.1.11.3.7.1 rather than 3.1.11.4 (it should not be at the same level as the "Segment Definitions" section. If going down 6 levels deep is too much, it would probably be OK just to have the text above the segment table without any section number. Given that the table and the field Definition Text don't have their own sections, maybe not assigning a subsection to Pre-Definition text is the best way to go  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22211997/a3c391ca-e154-11e6-90a7-0b2107c6d9ae.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-23 16:24:09</created>
		<closed>2017-01-25 15:40:41</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1124</id>
		<title>Cardinality and Usage shouldn't be populated for the END of a segment group</title>
		<body>In the message definition tables, when there is a segment group, it is critical to include a cardinality and usage at the start of the segment group, but there is no need to include the same information at the end of the segment (see red box below). It will just confuse readers.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22211136/bcb46450-e151-11e6-8872-01f0d9a4c1b0.png)  I think it should look like this: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22211309/3f7643a4-e152-11e6-8db9-10e8ac4a8351.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-23 15:57:03</created>
		<closed>2017-01-25 15:40:44</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1118</id>
		<title>Co-constraint table may not be exporting correctly</title>
		<body>Not sure if this still an issue with the latest release (per issue 1117, exports in general don't seem to be working, so I can't confirm one way or another, but as of 1/17, this was an issue).  The co-constraints table is coming out as a jumbled, unformatted mass of text immediately after the conditional predicates for a segment.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22163411/585d2f18-df18-11e6-9535-3c577819e50f.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22163427/69a154a2-df18-11e6-8d33-d9d0eabc6a65.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-01-20 20:00:00</created>
		<closed>2017-01-22 18:36:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1117</id>
		<title>Word export fails</title>
		<body>Can't export in either the standard or verbose Word formats  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/22163262/bfc4f3f8-df17-11e6-8fc0-7ebfa21e5200.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-20 19:53:35</created>
		<closed>2017-01-22 18:23:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1103</id>
		<title>Exporting error</title>
		<body>I am getting this error when I attempt to export the VR IG in word and also HTML  {"text":"internalError","resourceId":null,"manualHandle":"false","skip":false,"date":null,"version":null,"scope":null,"id":null,"type":"danger"}</body>
		<created>2017-01-17 15:33:51</created>
		<closed>2017-01-22 18:35:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1102</id>
		<title>apostrophe's not rendering right in Word export</title>
		<body>I've got some apostrophes in some Definition text that aren't rendering right in the Word export. This wasn't a problem in previous versions of the Word export  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21970649/18891a12-db6e-11e6-816e-ccc115c2d7d9.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21970670/4ed38a26-db6e-11e6-8558-6d2d49a7fad1.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-01-16 04:00:46</created>
		<closed>2017-01-19 21:17:04</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1101</id>
		<title>nested segment groups missing</title>
		<body>The Word export doesn't seem to include segment groups that are nested in other segment groups. Not only are the segment groups (and the segments in them) not in the message definition table, the segments are also not included following the message definition table in the verbose format  For example, in the screen shot below, there are first level segment groups (like insurance (green arrow)) and second level segment groups (timing and observation within the Order segment group (red arrow))  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21970408/95792d26-db6b-11e6-9ba0-57dc846b9fca.png)  The insurance segment group is in the export (green arrow below) but neither Timing nor Observation (red arrows).  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21970460/2d14c668-db6c-11e6-9cc1-0d9f0138de57.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-16 03:48:29</created>
		<closed>2017-01-19 21:17:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1071</id>
		<title>Can't export profiles</title>
		<body>I wanted to export a profile so that I could import it in to the validation tool but when I right click Conformance Profile and select Export, nothing happens.  Long term, will it be the Conformance Profile or the Composite Profiles that should be exportable?</body>
		<created>2017-01-11 13:27:26</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:25</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1052</id>
		<title>Date Updated not updated when creating/editting a profile component</title>
		<body>I can't seem to get the Date Updated element populated (or at least displayed) for s Profile Component  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21822243/07f17982-d73c-11e6-84e0-8bcca8652da4.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 19:53:18</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:20:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1051</id>
		<title>exporting only custom data type flavors?</title>
		<body>In verbose mode, is it intentional that only custom data types are exported? If so, why is that logic also not applied to segments and value sets?  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21821969/136ffcbc-d73b-11e6-8bed-1e66107ad79a.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 19:46:30</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:20:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1050</id>
		<title>Message Infrastructure organization issues for verbose mode</title>
		<body>The organization of the Message Infrastructure section needs a bit of work in Verbose mode. I would expect something like: 3 Message Infrastructure  3.1 Conformance Profiles   3.1.1 QBP^Q11    3.1.1.1 Usage Note    3.1.1.2 Pre-definition    3.1.1.3 Message Definition &lt;including Conditional Predicates and Conformance Statements&gt;    3.1.1.4 Post-defintion    3.1.1.5 Segment definitions     3.1.1.5.1 MSH     3.1.1.5.2 SFT     3.1.1.5.X&lt;remaining segments&gt;   3.1.2 RSP^K11    3.1.2.1 Usage Note    3.1.2.2 Pre-definition    3.1.2.3 Message Definition &lt;including Conditional Predicates and Conformance Statements&gt;    3.1.2.4 Post-defintion    3.1.2.5 Segment definitions     3.1.2.5.1 MSH     3.1.2.5.2 SFT     3.1.2.5.X&lt;remaining segments&gt;  If you think it's too many levels to get down to 3.1.1.5.1 as the MSH segment, rather than having "segment definition" wrapper level, just having the segments be 3.1.1.6 (MSH), 3.1.1.7 (SFT), etc would be fine.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21821655/04139306-d73a-11e6-9404-0e46c98afd34.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 19:44:15</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1048</id>
		<title>odd order of conformance statements at the end of the Word document</title>
		<body>In the final section of the exported Word document, all the conformance statements and conditional predicates are listed. For some reason for the conformance statements for the conformance profiles, the order is reversed from what I would expect. In IGAMT, the QBP is first and the RSP is second but in section 3.5, the order is reversed. It doesn't seem to be the conformance ID as IZ-2 is first.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21821266/8685a4de-d738-11e6-9bac-7737e6779ebc.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 19:29:22</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:22:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1045</id>
		<title>DTM definition not reflected in the Word Export</title>
		<body>I used the Date/Time format editor to define the requirements of several DTM flavors, but those requirements aren't part of the Word export  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21820152/3c9abbba-d734-11e6-98d5-e6a6a81cd0f5.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21820171/4c926d6a-d734-11e6-8be3-ce1e87fb466f.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 18:58:10</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:20:22</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1044</id>
		<title>inconsistent format when referring to a data type element</title>
		<body>you are inconsistent in how you refer to a data type element. In just this small space you use a dash (blue arrow), period (green arrow) and nothing (red arrow) between the data type (CWE) and the element number I believe the accepted convention is to use the period for a data type (eg. CWE.4)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21819838/ee76beb2-d732-11e6-9e7b-7525924ea920.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 18:48:56</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1043</id>
		<title>repeating conditional predicate</title>
		<body>Same issue here as for the conformance statements. The single conditional predicate is repeating multiple times in the  Word export.  As well, the table headers are off (and one short). It seems like they should be "Location", "Usage" and "Description".   Finally, is there a reason by "predicate" is not capitalized (it is in IGAMT)? similarly, in the section before this one "statement" in "Conformance statement" is not capitalized.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21818505/b7c60d5a-d72d-11e6-9104-f67fe5d651d4.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 18:11:50</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:22:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1042</id>
		<title>repeating conformance statements in the Word export</title>
		<body>My MSH segment has only a single conformance statement but in the Word export, it is repeated multiple times. It may be a coincidence, but it seems to be repeated once per field in the segment (25 fields in MSH and 25 occurrences in the CS table)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21818366/26158e1c-d72d-11e6-9c32-986ade9e6c1a.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21818383/36f511b2-d72d-11e6-8b2e-6600890c2933.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 18:09:20</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1040</id>
		<title>multiple value sets are exported with an extra comma</title>
		<body>when a segment field is associated with multiple value sets, in the Word export, the list of value sets seems to be preceded by an extraneous comma (red arrow below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21818119/3bb5df8e-d72c-11e6-9b16-82d5d09bfb2d.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 18:00:19</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1039</id>
		<title>segment groups aren't exported</title>
		<body>Looks like when a conformance profile contains a segment group, that segment group is not part of the message definition table in the Word export  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21817850/45fd7a52-d72b-11e6-9e0b-ca5a885448c9.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21817871/5764548c-d72b-11e6-8d82-1d8ba0694014.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 17:53:31</created>
		<closed>2017-01-10 22:20:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1034</id>
		<title>Conformance Profile missing a "level"</title>
		<body>the Message Infrastructure section goes 3 =&gt; 3.1 =&gt; 3.1.1.1, skipping 3.1.1. I think this case, the element in the red box below should be 3.1.1 so it's clear that the usage note and everything with it is related to the QBP message.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21812756/97911ab6-d719-11e6-81cf-7317c0738a13.png)  As well, even though I have two conformance profiles, in IGAMT, the organization in the Word export is off, the RSP profile doesn't have a section on par with the QBP but above the subsections for each profile (usage note, message definition table, etc)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21812919/1ecd9540-d71a-11e6-997a-951671fb82be.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 15:49:58</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1032</id>
		<title>header indenting is still off</title>
		<body>The indenting of the sections in the Word Export are still off. Each subsection should be indented further to the left.  Now: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21812429/8ab34310-d718-11e6-8b9f-224bcd062899.png)  Should be more like this: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21812504/c794ec3e-d718-11e6-867a-39466b1f3c4f.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 15:40:37</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1031</id>
		<title>Export sometimes misses a space</title>
		<body>If an author applies fomatting to part of a line, after the formatting ends, 1 space is removed between the formatted and unformatted text.  In the examples below, if the first word of a line is either bold or italic, the space after the formatting ends is missing in the Word export. Oddly, underlining is not affected.  If the whole line is formatted, then the spacing is just fine.  If multiple spaces are included in the line, it seems like only a single space is lost (not all of them)  This may see a bit obscure, but I use this format in the immunization guide to call attention to a header.  I'm using the "dev" flag, but this is occurring in the production IGAMT too.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21812041/4fd2b98e-d717-11e6-9076-b846c2538f63.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21812002/33088054-d717-11e6-8f77-8c85ddd083c1.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 15:34:30</created>
		<closed>2017-01-18 20:51:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1029</id>
		<title>Compact Word export has blank pages</title>
		<body>When I exported my IG to the compact Word format, there are two blank pages between the title page and the first page of content. at least one of these should be removed unless they serve a clear purpose (some documents intentionally include a blank page but they label is "intentionally blank").</body>
		<created>2017-01-10 15:12:08</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:20:03</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1028</id>
		<title>export shouldn't include "null" metadata</title>
		<body>When I created my test IG, I didn't enter a lot of metadata, but some authors won't want to include a Sub-Title or Organization. So when you export the document, you shouldn't say that these fields were null or default a value (red arrows below) because they may be purposely blank. Plus, I don't see a MetaData field for document version.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21811147/265f7a18-d714-11e6-88c8-086bb132984a.png)   ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21811126/0d76579c-d714-11e6-98b8-7e840fc86afe.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 15:09:34</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1027</id>
		<title>Cover Picture not included in the Word export</title>
		<body>I added a cover picture but it doesn't seem to be in the Compact Word export format  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21811054/ce749b6c-d713-11e6-9fc1-60c9000dc44a.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21811079/e306370c-d713-11e6-9edb-f0c4c7766ee6.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 15:05:17</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:20:18</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1026</id>
		<title>deleted values aren't immediately removed from the display</title>
		<body>The "delete values" button works in that it deletes the value, but it doesn't refresh the value list so it appears that it didn't work until you save the changes (which still doesn't refresh the value list) and leave the value set and then return to it  button is lit up ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21810505/b996631c-d711-11e6-884b-af3077772193.png)  after clicking the delete values button, the button is no longer lit up, but the value is still visible ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21810530/d3758056-d711-11e6-9fe4-eb519a1e3db4.png)  But after you leave the value set and come back, then the value is gone. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21810615/1ce0d3ee-d712-11e6-81c7-f0d983bd57f8.png)  </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 14:53:04</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:36</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1022</id>
		<title>no way to manually add new values to a value set</title>
		<body>I created a custom value set (I copied the 0361 value set) but when I went to add new values, clicking the "add value" button didn't do anything.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21810132/1b281f50-d710-11e6-94a6-5b55de7de1ba.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 14:38:13</created>
		<closed>2017-01-30 15:27:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1019</id>
		<title>Message STructure label is overwritten</title>
		<body>I created a composite profile (I created it incorrectly if that matters) an on the Metadata tab, the Message Structure label seems to overlap with "ID*" (red box below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21809353/eea889ae-d70c-11e6-95e9-918e93b5ce6f.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 14:15:28</created>
		<closed>2017-06-23 18:52:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1018</id>
		<title>When trying to add a segment, Segment options are limited</title>
		<body>When trying to add a new segment to an existing profile, it looks like the possible values for "Existing Segment" seem to be limited to the segments already in the message profile. When we build out the RSP message for example, we need to be able to add ORC, RXA and RXR, but that doesn't seem possible  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21808777/643e3de2-d70a-11e6-932d-480b6a3af660.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 13:59:00</created>
		<closed>2017-01-10 15:25:15</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1017</id>
		<title>conformance statements bleed across Conformance Profiles</title>
		<body>I added a conformance statement to a QBP profile and then when I move to the RSP profile, the same conformance statement is there too (see below). Other sections (post-test, pre-text, etc) don't seem to be affected)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21808573/7f4042a8-d709-11e6-905a-289fbaffbfb0.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 13:50:58</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>1016</id>
		<title>deleting a section messes up saving other sections</title>
		<body>I deleted the "purpose" section of the Introduction and now anytime I try to add text and save it to any part of chapter 1 I get a saving error (see below).  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21808210/d875023e-d707-11e6-923c-a4eb86ec2a3c.png)  If I go to Chapter 1 (Use Cases), I can edit and save text in those sections.  When I close the document and open it back up, all the sections in Introduction are now gone (red box below) ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21808282/4a9eb9e0-d708-11e6-90c4-40131fd05210.png) </body>
		<created>2017-01-10 13:42:27</created>
		<closed>2017-01-10 21:48:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>973</id>
		<title>Can't add a profile</title>
		<body>when I right click on "conformance profiles" to add a new profile, I can't select an event to add:  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21278513/3f7ad438-c3a1-11e6-8971-3c4a5ba065f9.png)  Combine this with the issue about copying and saving profiles (see issue 972), there is no way to add a new conformance profile in the production IGAMT.</body>
		<created>2016-12-16 21:06:19</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:22:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>972</id>
		<title>copied profiles don't save</title>
		<body>I'm trying to copy an existing profile (the Z34 profile).  I can copy it (and modify it) - see red arrow below  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21278415/ac9cd1b6-c3a0-11e6-89dc-c99fccf97985.png)   But when I close the document and then go back in, it's not there (note that the number of profiles when from 10 to 9): ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21278458/e7f41a30-c3a0-11e6-9e97-370227184275.png) </body>
		<created>2016-12-16 21:04:47</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>950</id>
		<title>complex conformance statement ID is wrong</title>
		<body>When a complex conformance statement is created, the ID is not transferred correctly when the CS is added. When I added the CS in the example below, the default ID was replaced by the "IFTHEN" statement highlighted by the green box. Oddly, the simple conformance statement IDs seem to work.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21027150/34fed0f6-bd55-11e6-8e6a-d438bb0c3e36.png) </body>
		<created>2016-12-08 20:49:58</created>
		<closed>2017-01-09 16:06:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>948</id>
		<title>Can seem to add a condition predicate</title>
		<body>I'm trying to add a Conditional Predicate to a segment. I can add the requirement, but I don't see a way to specify the true/false usages and the "save" button (green box below) doesn't light up. Am I missing something?  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/21026566/d4e88c90-bd52-11e6-99fc-e22596646708.png) </body>
		<created>2016-12-08 20:31:31</created>
		<closed>2017-01-09 15:55:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>947</id>
		<title>co-constraints table isn't exporting</title>
		<body>Looks like the co-constraints table defined in a segment is not being exported.</body>
		<created>2016-12-08 20:22:46</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:20:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>946</id>
		<title>Deleting a Conformance Statement doesn't light up the "save" button</title>
		<body>I'm trying to delete a Conformance Statement associated with the MSA segment: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20973510/6da35820-bc5e-11e6-821f-ef51b97d6f2f.png)  But when I click the delete button, the CS goes away, but there is no way to save the change as the "save" button doesn't light up: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20973550/9d333524-bc5e-11e6-99c6-7167823ab264.png)  And if you move away from the segment, there is no pop up asking to save changes.  And then when you go back to the MSA segment, the deleted CS is still there: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20973599/d3138036-bc5e-11e6-97ad-0b332bf759c2.png) </body>
		<created>2016-12-07 15:23:35</created>
		<closed>2017-01-09 16:06:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>945</id>
		<title>Uniqueness of Conformance Statement IDs is no longer checked</title>
		<body>There used to be a check on the conformance statement ID to make sure it wasn't already in use. That doesn't seem to happen anymore.  This CS existed: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20973380/0aa94d1a-bc5e-11e6-9f46-e6683cd94987.png)  But I was still able to create this in another part of the IG: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20973412/25b82d92-bc5e-11e6-878e-d8037a80558e.png) </body>
		<created>2016-12-07 15:19:22</created>
		<closed>2017-01-09 16:19:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>922</id>
		<title>Conformance statements and predicates are not showing in word export</title>
		<body>Conformance statements and predicates are not showing in word export, due to the use of inline constraints</body>
		<created>2016-11-28 22:05:30</created>
		<closed>2016-12-02 22:15:24</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>916</id>
		<title>Global Conformance Statements missing from the Export</title>
		<body>The Word Export doesn't seem to include any of the Global Conformance statements. For example, the ADT conformance profile below has a number of CS, but when I search the Word export, I don't find them.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20568892/97eaaf26-b163-11e6-930e-a55a2708937e.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20568910/b19d5608-b163-11e6-8d10-921cc501bccc.png) </body>
		<created>2016-11-23 16:00:53</created>
		<closed>2016-12-02 22:15:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>914</id>
		<title>Images aren't exporting again</title>
		<body>The Word document exports have reverted to a previous issue where images in IGAMT are not being included in the export document.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20567898/09d59b68-b160-11e6-85f9-d3d8565240bf.png) </body>
		<created>2016-11-23 15:34:52</created>
		<closed>2016-11-28 22:04:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>913</id>
		<title>export gets truncated</title>
		<body>Even though the text in IGAMT looks OK, there are two places in my IG where the export gets truncated.  The first spot is in section 1.4.5 which looks like this in IGAMT: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20566994/b1f6c334-b15c-11e6-9ed4-b19525b7b5cc.png) And the export ends here: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20567035/dcb13a3c-b15c-11e6-8883-b6b3ff5d1e0b.png)  If you go into IGAMT and replace the current text between the tables with an identical copy, then the export works: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20567238/a0b51700-b15d-11e6-97c3-523b5afce13c.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20567258/afff5acc-b15d-11e6-81a2-70b016c37fde.png)  The second place where the export truncates is in section 2.3.7.11 in the middle of the word "Local". In IGAMT it looks like this: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20567359/fcabff7e-b15d-11e6-9ad5-d2978b93ab90.png) And the export looks like this: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20567385/17eefb24-b15e-11e6-92ae-c079339299eb.png)   If you go into IGAMT and replace the word "Local" the issue is fixed: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20567474/6ed348a0-b15e-11e6-99a4-505bd1091d9d.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20567456/62214a76-b15e-11e6-8273-3243d12846d0.png)  My guess is that there are unprintable characters in there that are causing the export to truncate without an error but I sure can't find them.  I've created copies of my IG so that the development team can take a look and will share them with Harold. They will be labeled "before" and "after". "before" has the truncating issue, the "after" has been fixed and successfully exported.</body>
		<created>2016-11-23 15:25:49</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:22:04</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>912</id>
		<title>Issues with Date Updated</title>
		<body>There seems to be some trouble with the individual Date Updated field of the IG components.  On the Metadata tab, the Date Updated value has a couple of issues: 1) it doesn't update, even when data is changed (see example below) 2) the field doesn't seem to be editable (which makes sense), but it isn't greyed out (like HL7 Version is), so it seems like an author should be able to update it.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20564396/ba4c365e-b152-11e6-8443-890e2c959587.png)  In other tabs, the Date Updated field starts out OK (in the example below, it starts out as the date/time when I copied the IG), but when I update the Contents, the Date Updated reverts to an earlier date (the one on the Metadata tab presumably) rather than updating to the current date/time Before the change: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20564455/07f837ae-b153-11e6-9e12-ac2ac49c8787.png)  After the change: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20564488/234537dc-b153-11e6-80a5-890a43cf4468.png)  </body>
		<created>2016-11-23 14:02:43</created>
		<closed>2016-11-25 19:14:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>911</id>
		<title>updating the "Date Updated" value doesn't seem to work</title>
		<body>When copying a whole IG, I would expect the "date updated" column for the new IG to be updated with the current date, but it doesn't seem to be. Before the copy: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20564211/cec8cd0a-b151-11e6-85ab-2b67b1fb6ca6.png) After the copy: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20564232/e2fb36e6-b151-11e6-950f-29d82b961959.png)  And then when the document is actually updated (note the new title in the example below), the Date Updated isn't updated either. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20564280/264bf516-b152-11e6-876c-64254780644a.png) </body>
		<created>2016-11-23 13:55:50</created>
		<closed>2016-11-25 19:13:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>906</id>
		<title>Conformance profile level constraints are not displayed</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-11-22 19:30:16</created>
		<closed>2016-12-02 22:15:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>899</id>
		<title>Segment constraints</title>
		<body>When a segments has multiple fields that have constraints, there is a table for each field, where we should only have one table with all the constraints</body>
		<created>2016-11-22 16:12:41</created>
		<closed>2016-11-22 16:13:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>897</id>
		<title>Message content not showing in the new export</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-11-22 15:13:54</created>
		<closed>2016-11-22 15:29:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>893</id>
		<title>images won't load</title>
		<body>I'm having trouble getting images integrated into IGAMT. A few of the images I've tried will load, but most of them give the error seen below. There is no indication of what went wrong.  Note that in this example, I'm trying to load the same file as what is above it (so I know this file has been OK before). The image file type, doesn't seem to consistently predict success or failure ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20492070/fd5279d4-afd8-11e6-85e0-bb5aefb79289.png) </body>
		<created>2016-11-21 16:56:28</created>
		<closed>2016-11-22 16:51:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>892</id>
		<title>HTML export doesn't work at all</title>
		<body>The HMTL export seems to produce a completely empty file. As of right now, none of the exports work</body>
		<created>2016-11-21 15:26:03</created>
		<closed>2016-11-22 16:51:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>884</id>
		<title>unable to change datatype for element in segment</title>
		<body>Unable to edit a datatype where needed.  The choice box does not offer any choices and since we "pre-adopt" other datatype from futre version the can change.  For example,  CE --&gt; CWE.  </body>
		<created>2016-11-18 23:30:35</created>
		<closed>2017-01-13 22:19:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>882</id>
		<title>files won't open</title>
		<body>We're having another problem with exporting to a Word file. When I try to do this, I get the following errors when i try to open the Word document:  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/20435253/089de5fe-ad71-11e6-815b-2cba63d16e31.png)  This is the case not only for my newer versions of the IG, but also for a copy saved on 10/19 before I exported document to add the manual formatting and circulate for review, so I know versions of the IG have exported successfully in the past.</body>
		<created>2016-11-18 15:27:58</created>
		<closed>2016-11-22 16:53:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>847</id>
		<title>Content from Value Set section not in the export</title>
		<body>I added content to the Value Set section to explain value sets in general, but when I exported the document, it wasn't present.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19819573/f9111478-9d1a-11e6-852c-b6361c2a1d42.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19819596/0d53e3e8-9d1b-11e6-943e-b7b52ec1e107.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-28 19:37:48</created>
		<closed>2016-11-22 16:56:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>838</id>
		<title>Impossible to create new IG document</title>
		<body>I tried to create a new IG, but there is no event when I expend the message type ![igamt impossible create](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13591511/19694391/238e2d64-9aad-11e6-9532-01e7e9eefeff.JPG)  This is on the production tool. </body>
		<created>2016-10-25 16:19:14</created>
		<closed>2016-10-25 19:48:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>836</id>
		<title>Exported Word document has trouble opening</title>
		<body>I exported my IG to Word but when I tried to open it, I got warning errors (see below). Ultimately, it did open and look OK, but I'm assuming there is an error in there somewhere.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19686707/02e7d7c4-9a88-11e6-83a6-4c8bccf1e8d0.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19686712/082806b4-9a88-11e6-9467-dd4c33cc65e2.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19686741/26ae032c-9a88-11e6-8f25-feff65055f6d.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-25 12:54:52</created>
		<closed>2016-11-22 16:56:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>835</id>
		<title>Segment Pre and Post-Text don't work</title>
		<body>It is no longer possible to enter a Definition Pre-Text or Definition Post-Text for a segment. The sections just don't expand to allow text editing.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19686174/b110219c-9a85-11e6-815b-243f6aae97c8.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-25 12:37:11</created>
		<closed>2016-10-25 17:03:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>827</id>
		<title>Comment editor header is quirky</title>
		<body>I went to edit a comment associated with the ERR segment in a message profile (see green arrow below). The editor itself worked fine (I could update and save a comment) but the header to the editor popup was strange (see red box below). I suspect something is not displaying as you expect  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19536417/7b55ba3a-9611-11e6-88a5-a6566a329023.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-19 20:36:14</created>
		<closed>2017-10-16 19:46:45</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>821</id>
		<title>Don't publish Cardinality and Usage for End of Segment Group</title>
		<body>When outputting the conformance profile, it makes sense to publish the segment group usage and cardinality at the beginning of the segment group (green boxes below) but not at the end of the segment group (red boxes below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19491164/8a0175a4-9537-11e6-9f0e-8b3776076435.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-18 18:35:50</created>
		<closed>2016-12-02 22:15:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>813</id>
		<title>Label is wrong</title>
		<body>On the IG Document Metadata page the date label is not displaying correctly (red box below).  On a related note, I thought we were going to update this date/time every time we saved the IG so that it represented the currently date of the document.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19439202/dddbda98-9442-11e6-90c2-b9ee1999351b.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-17 13:24:20</created>
		<closed>2016-10-25 17:08:53</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>807</id>
		<title>Assertion XML DOM issue</title>
		<body>&lt;Description&gt;The value of MSH-2(Encoding Characters) SHALL be '^~&amp;amp;'.&lt;/Description&gt;                     &lt;Assertion&gt;                         &lt;PlainText Path="2[1]" Text="^~\&amp;amp;" IgnoreCase="false"/&gt;                     &lt;/Assertion&gt;  Assertion is not populated correctly </body>
		<created>2016-10-12 15:54:50</created>
		<closed>2016-10-19 13:51:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>803</id>
		<title>Word export is running words together</title>
		<body>When I export my IG to Word, some of the words are running together even though there are spaces in IGAMT.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19270557/3df3b14c-8f86-11e6-9e0e-3898811faa18.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19270625/8e875686-8f86-11e6-9585-88dfc1f9ba48.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19270650/b5150fbe-8f86-11e6-9124-cfbdd3a3ed66.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19270696/e6c05b9a-8f86-11e6-8009-34c53aad43de.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-11 12:47:28</created>
		<closed>2017-01-09 16:04:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>797</id>
		<title>Co-constraints table sorting doesn't seem to work</title>
		<body>I'm assuming you should be able to sort the co-constraints table by a column, but it doesn't seem to be working. The order doesn't change regardless of whether or not the arrow is up (red circle below) or down (green circle below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19197649/9581f062-8c80-11e6-8edc-7ca2ced67b6c.png) ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19197666/aa48195e-8c80-11e6-9a08-90d72a4690b3.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-07 16:26:34</created>
		<closed>2017-04-03 14:18:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>793</id>
		<title>show only published datatypes for igdocument and dtLib</title>
		<body>the issue is that we don't have the status in the children of the datatypeLibrary I am wondering if i should add it to the model !!  @haffo  </body>
		<created>2016-10-07 01:58:51</created>
		<closed>2016-10-17 14:53:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>789</id>
		<title>Usage  not outputting correctly</title>
		<body>The Usage in the Word output of a profile is not being populated correctly  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/19167996/b5a5a95e-8bd3-11e6-8e40-0f8306741f17.png) </body>
		<created>2016-10-06 19:46:57</created>
		<closed>2016-10-07 19:27:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>788</id>
		<title>Saving issue for datatype</title>
		<body>if you are available, please stop by @haffo @IsmailMellouli @Jungyubw  </body>
		<created>2016-10-06 15:52:26</created>
		<closed>2016-10-06 20:44:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>755</id>
		<title>Saving the first time don't work correctly for the datatype Library </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-10-04 13:44:20</created>
		<closed>2016-10-07 19:34:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>754</id>
		<title>Non clickable TOC in datatype library HTML export</title>
		<body>Fix the href for the anchors </body>
		<created>2016-10-04 04:41:46</created>
		<closed>2016-10-05 18:31:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>688</id>
		<title>MISSING predicates and conformance statements in word export</title>
		<body>This is what shows in WORD:  Conditional predicates Location    Usage   Description HD.1    C(R/RE) If HD.2(Universal ID) is not valued HD.2    C(R/O)  If HD.1(Namespace ID) is not valued  Note that HD.3 is missing here but not in igamt.  Also note that there is no conformance statement in word, but one in igamt.  [0 PREDICATE MISSING.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/493166/0.PREDICATE.MISSING.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-09-26 13:20:54</created>
		<closed>2016-09-26 19:57:41</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>661</id>
		<title>data types missing in word export</title>
		<body>Seq Element name    Data type   Usage   Cardinality Length  Value Set   Comment 1   Set ID - OBX           X    [ 0 .. 0 ]  [ 1 .. 4 ]   2   Value Type      R   [ 1 .. 1 ]  [ 2 .. 3 ]   3   Observation Identifier      R   [ 1 .. 1 ]  [ 0 .. 0 ]   4   Observation Sub-ID      R   [ 1 .. 1 ]  [ 0 .. 0 ]   5   Observation Value   ED_7106662  R   [ 1 .. 1 ]  [ 1 .. 29999 ]        NOTE THAT DATA TYPES ARE MISSING EXCEPT IN OBX-5.   </body>
		<created>2016-09-20 15:45:28</created>
		<closed>2016-09-20 21:40:24</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>660</id>
		<title>can't change data type in segment flavor</title>
		<body>I tried to change the data type in a flavored OBX to a flavored CWE. Save button is inactive. [1 update data type.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/482714/1.update.data.type.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-09-20 13:52:12</created>
		<closed>2016-09-20 19:24:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>657</id>
		<title>Can't seem to add new complex CS</title>
		<body>I've created complex CS in the past (see IZ-31 below) but I can't seem to know. I wanted to replace the IZ-31 that exists now because it references the wrong value set. I can create the necessary simple CS and I can build the complex CS, but clicking the "add" button to add the new complex CS doesn't seem to do anything.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18595971/b45f1688-7c0c-11e6-8159-86174b1d138b.png) </body>
		<created>2016-09-16 17:55:52</created>
		<closed>2016-10-12 16:25:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>656</id>
		<title>Can't remove Conformance Statements added at the profile level</title>
		<body>I added a conformance statement to an RCP field in the profile editor. I realized I should add it in the segment editor instead. I tried to delete the CS (green arrow) but the 'save" button didn't light up (red box) and when I closed the CS editor, the CS was still there (blue box)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18590480/96dc6808-7bf4-11e6-98b3-ec2c6b9f02ca.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18590500/b10c9bbc-7bf4-11e6-8c6a-d481058de1dd.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18590517/c4cbbdd6-7bf4-11e6-8a6c-846d4ba0ab1f.png) </body>
		<created>2016-09-16 15:05:17</created>
		<closed>2016-09-19 19:51:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>655</id>
		<title>Profile order is not reflected in the Word export</title>
		<body>When exporting into a Word document, the order of the conformance profiles in IGAMT (red box below) is not reflected in the Word document (green box below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18588829/b0dbd90c-7bed-11e6-9b6c-c5707b70be40.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18588759/69d7ee7e-7bed-11e6-950c-d9ec5a300ae2.png) </body>
		<created>2016-09-16 14:12:59</created>
		<closed>2016-09-26 21:54:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>653</id>
		<title>Profile level CS not published</title>
		<body>It is possible (and sometimes desirable) to add conformance statements at the profile level. However, it doesn't look like these conformance statements are published as part of the Word document export. Note the existence of CS (red box) but they don't show up in the profile definition (green box) or anywhere in the document (blue box)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18588398/e65e5a2a-7beb-11e6-9c02-4498b614c82b.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18588443/153fbb86-7bec-11e6-9999-446ab4bc4a85.png) </body>
		<created>2016-09-16 14:03:52</created>
		<closed>2016-09-23 13:32:22</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>652</id>
		<title>new problem adding segment</title>
		<body>[22 add seg.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/474852/22.add.seg.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-09-15 14:19:15</created>
		<closed>2016-09-20 19:21:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>651</id>
		<title>Deleting Conf Profile Issue</title>
		<body>- User deleted conf profile - User drag another conf profile - Deleted conf profile came back </body>
		<created>2016-09-14 16:55:37</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 13:43:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>646</id>
		<title>Changes to a newly added profile don't stick</title>
		<body>If you add a new profile and edit the MetaData, save the profile and then close the IG, when you open the IG back up, none of the changes are saved:  For example, I added an RSP and changed the ID and the description: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18478596/73535626-7997-11e6-96d7-99be4c2944eb.png)  I then closed the IG and reopened it but none of my changes had been saved: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18478689/c0e3e2c0-7997-11e6-9859-e166a2b44b92.png) </body>
		<created>2016-09-13 14:52:33</created>
		<closed>2016-09-26 21:55:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>644</id>
		<title>Can't add segment to profile</title>
		<body>I tried to add a segment to RSP. (OBX) The search does not find the existing OBX segment. I had added that segment to the list of segments earlier.  [11 ADD OBX.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/467336/11.ADD.OBX.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-09-12 13:00:00</created>
		<closed>2016-09-20 15:50:25</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>643</id>
		<title>Add Profile Issue</title>
		<body>When Clicking on Add Profile while an exiting ig is open with unsaved changes, the user is redirect to the list of ig docs </body>
		<created>2016-09-08 23:26:33</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 13:43:38</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>642</id>
		<title>Validate Imported ValueSet File</title>
		<body>We need to make sure the file is CSV file and that the structure is correct.  May be a duplicate.  </body>
		<created>2016-09-08 22:53:24</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 16:56:54</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>640</id>
		<title>Value sets missing</title>
		<body>I'm pretty sure I created separate Race and Ethnic Group value sets from CDCREC (CDCREC_01 and CDCREC_02 respectively). CDCREC_01 seems to be missing (purple box below) and PID-10 doesn't list the CDCREC_01 value set until you click on the pencil icon (red box) (which exists even though there is no value set listed in the table) at which point CDCREC_01 is now listed in the pop up (green box).   I'm less concerned about losing the CDCREC_01 value set (although losing value sets is never good), but it's not good that the reference to CDCREC_01 wasn't cleaned up when the value set disappeared.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18359805/23f7ac96-75c1-11e6-84d0-88e7aaf152f4.png) </body>
		<created>2016-09-08 17:38:52</created>
		<closed>2016-09-29 20:07:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>639</id>
		<title>still seeing an error when searching for a PHINVADS value set</title>
		<body>![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18358748/40c6cbea-75bc-11e6-9b9f-ed29efe1842e.png) </body>
		<created>2016-09-08 17:03:39</created>
		<closed>2017-01-30 15:32:52</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>637</id>
		<title>display has some quirks</title>
		<body>I opened up the RXA segment and the display is all wonky. The "definition pre-text" is off, there are no column headers and the gridlines aren't synced up with the content.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18352634/c9e9ff90-75a4-11e6-8fce-48285398dde2.png) </body>
		<created>2016-09-08 14:17:03</created>
		<closed>2016-09-19 20:33:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>635</id>
		<title>table import from .csv has some issues</title>
		<body>When I loaded a value set from a .csv file, it shows up in the value set list (red box below), but when I click on it I get an error saying "Cannot find the table specified" (black arrow below). Plus the CodeSystem values are not populated. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18350931/c315f3ec-759d-11e6-8333-8816f3eaaf4f.png)  The codeSystem not being populated probably has to do with code system not populated on the MetaData tab.   I updated the MetaData (coding system, open/closed, etc) but when I clicked on "save" nothing happened. When I tried to navigate away from the table I go the usual warning about unsaved data. Even when I said to save and move away, nothing seemed to happen.   Plus, it doesn't seem to be possible to delete the table. When I try, I get the same "cannot find the table specified" error.  So in general, the table appears to load but doesn't behave like it is a real table </body>
		<created>2016-09-08 13:29:34</created>
		<closed>2016-09-08 22:56:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>624</id>
		<title>add value set process causes lockup</title>
		<body>I was trying to add a value set.  selected import. selected version 2.7.1.  Locked application with spinning ball.  I had been working in QPD segment, right clicked the value sets to add value set.  I am pretty sure I had saved before I did this.  I got Server Error message. [1 add table.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/452363/1.add.table.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-09-02 15:33:46</created>
		<closed>2016-09-27 14:22:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>614</id>
		<title>SAD data type missing from XAD=1</title>
		<body>I am using 2.7.1 I added XAD data type.  there is no data type shown for XAD-1.  Once I added SAD data type to the list of data types, it showed up. </body>
		<created>2016-09-02 14:05:16</created>
		<closed>2016-09-08 23:19:02</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>613</id>
		<title>profile contents don't show</title>
		<body>I have added some data types, made flavors of data types and segments.  I have been adding fields to QPD query parameters. After making a flavor of XTN, I went back to QPD_xxx and got a blank edit box and spinning circle of dots.  [6 empty edit area.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/450359/6.empty.edit.area.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-09-01 17:41:01</created>
		<closed>2016-09-14 22:01:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>611</id>
		<title>create field in segment has no save button</title>
		<body>the save button never shows when creating a new field. [4 create field.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/450050/4.create.field.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-09-01 15:20:36</created>
		<closed>2016-09-01 15:58:44</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>610</id>
		<title>another issue with sections</title>
		<body>See attached.  [2 missing section.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/449916/2.missing.section.pdf)  I tried copying the same block into a different section without problem saving. </body>
		<created>2016-09-01 14:29:46</created>
		<closed>2016-09-29 16:48:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>607</id>
		<title>problems with sections continue</title>
		<body>I opened the recovered IG and found the duplication of sections. I deleted duplicate sections and closed.  When I reopened, the duplicates were back.  Also note that the sections are misnumbered in both attached screen shots. [2 duplicate sections.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/449654/2.duplicate.sections.pdf) [1 duplicate sections.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/449655/1.duplicate.sections.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-09-01 12:47:12</created>
		<closed>2016-09-09 12:51:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>582</id>
		<title>Inappropriate value set association possibilities</title>
		<body>When creating custom fields for a segment (such as QPD), the segment editor will allow the author to associate value sets with some inappropriate data types. In the example below, you can add a value set to NM_01 and DTM_01 (purple box) but not DTM (red box). The latter is appropriate, the former are inappropriate. The tool should only allow value sets to be associated with logical data types (and their related flavors).  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18062672/6f32258c-6ded-11e6-825a-ca1f0c5b1629.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-29 18:37:38</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 20:47:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>581</id>
		<title>Can't add value sets to all data types for custom fields</title>
		<body>I created a number of custom fields for the QPD segment. one (QPD-10) of them uses the ID data type which should be OK to add a value set to. The field has the pencil icon in the Value Set column for QPD-10 but I can't successfully add a value set even though I can add value sets for a number of other fields with different data types. One thing I notice is that for the the ID data type (but not other data types I tried), once you type in a value set into the search box (0136 in the example below) and select a value set (0136_01 in the example below, the search term persists (red box below). I don't think this causes the problem (if you delete the search term manually and then click Select, it still doesn't work), but it correlated with it.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18062468/9d66dba6-6dec-11e6-8a12-8085efe8d0b7.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-29 18:34:19</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 20:47:36</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>579</id>
		<title>Create Field editor has value set issues</title>
		<body>When creating a custom field for a segment, the editor has a couple issues with selecting a value set.  1) it seems like the ValueSet entry field accepts just text and doesn't actually constrain it to a discrete value set (at least it doesn't seem to offer up suggestions of discrete value sets based on what the author enters as other value set selection activities do. 2) even if a value is entered to ValueSet, it doesn't make to the segment editor (kind of like the comment in a previous ticket). See red box below  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18061588/e22f47a4-6de8-11e6-8113-4a50a71057a0.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18061673/396782d4-6de9-11e6-9215-93e7965b12ca.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-29 18:05:39</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 20:47:26</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>578</id>
		<title>When Creating a Field, comments are not stored</title>
		<body>When creating a custom field for a segment, the Create Field editor includes a spot to add a comment. But if you add text there (red box below), it doesn't make it into the segment table (blue box below).   ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18061392/2da5b156-6de8-11e6-93f0-154a912720ed.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18061470/6e34c54a-6de8-11e6-8d25-7d2be045b24f.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-29 18:02:16</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 20:47:30</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>577</id>
		<title>Section move not being saved</title>
		<body>I'm trying to move the Dynamic Definition section of the Use Case so that it follows the Interaction Definition but every time I move it, it just winds up back at the bottom again next time I open the IG.   Move and saved (note that the number (2.3.6) didn't seem to change when I moved it): ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18058316/659a8956-6dd9-11e6-99d6-b910b8ec79ca.png)  And then the next time.... ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/18058338/786256cc-6dd9-11e6-9eb3-040d108fe052.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-29 16:13:26</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 13:43:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>574</id>
		<title>section is misnomered</title>
		<body>The section #11 is misnumbered and has a different font. [1 section missnumbered.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/437100/1.section.missnumbered.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-08-25 13:21:14</created>
		<closed>2016-08-31 21:24:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>573</id>
		<title>duplication of document sections</title>
		<body>I was reviewing the document and found that sections that I had added as subsections we duplicated as sections below with the same name.  When I click on the subsection, the section is also highlighted.  [3 duplication of sections.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/436982/3.duplication.of.sections.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-08-25 13:19:27</created>
		<closed>2016-08-31 21:24:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>571</id>
		<title>add segment fails, position list nonsensical</title>
		<body>I started a clean IG (2.5.1) and clone of MSH, deleted the row def segment from RSP. I added CX data type. I exported each time with no problem.  Attempted to add OBX to RSP. The first attempt failed for no apparent reason. Save button inactive. Cancelled and then retried. This time, the position list was weird. only position 13 showed.  [1 add segment fail.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/430511/1.add.segment.fail.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-08-22 15:30:46</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 22:09:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>570</id>
		<title>Possible Encoding issue on Conformance Statement</title>
		<body>I am getting an error coming from a CS, VR-29 - The value of MSH-9(Message Type) SHALL be 'ADT^A04^ATD_A01'. I have the exact value in the message, an error should not be generated. Hossam indicated that this might be due to an encoding issue, coming from TCAMT or IGAMT. </body>
		<created>2016-08-22 15:21:39</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 21:00:33</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>569</id>
		<title>Delta Result persists</title>
		<body>If you do a segment delta for one segment (NK1 for example) and then move to a different segment (MSH for example) and edit the Delta Configuration but don't click the "Segment Delta" button before you move to Delta Result, the delta report from the previous segment (NK1 in this example) shows up. In the example below the segment was MSH (red box) but the result was from the previous segment (blue box). Either the delta should update when going to the Delta Result activity or it should be cleared out when the user changes segments.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17860092/cc101de6-6851-11e6-8469-5d87052a5ac0.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-22 15:19:53</created>
		<closed>2016-09-21 20:47:16</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>568</id>
		<title>The "Binding Location" attribute missing from IGAMT XML profile</title>
		<body>I am getting a “The binding location is missing” in the Viral Records validation.  The IGAMT profile is not specifying the correct binding.  This is happening in all the segments using the HD data type.   It looks like the VR profiles are missing the a Binding Location.  VR profile: &lt;Field Name="Sending Application" Usage="R" Datatype="HD_VR" MinLength="1"                 MaxLength="227" ConfLength="1" Binding="0361" Min="1" Max="1" ItemNo="00003"/&gt;  IZ-Profile: &lt;Field Name="Sending Application" Usage="RE" Min="0" Max="1" Datatype="HD_IZ" MinLength="1" MaxLength="227" Binding="HL70361_IZ" BindingStrength="R" BindingLocation="1" ItemNo="00003"/&gt; </body>
		<created>2016-08-19 18:18:13</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 21:38:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>567</id>
		<title>DTM_S format</title>
		<body>IGAMT is not supporting this format: "YYYYMMDDHHMMSS[.S[S[S[S]]]][+/-ZZZZ]"  </body>
		<created>2016-08-19 17:31:42</created>
		<closed>2016-08-24 04:09:30</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>565</id>
		<title>data type creation error</title>
		<body>I added data type to new IG, CX. clicked save and got the attached screen.  note weird thing in list. [9 data type.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/425691/9.data.type.pdf)  Note I am in an empty add box. </body>
		<created>2016-08-18 19:13:33</created>
		<closed>2016-08-31 21:26:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>562</id>
		<title>description text truncated</title>
		<body>One of the description texts is being truncated in the Word export  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17749184/4069fabe-6482-11e6-9b89-248bd1afb25f.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17749167/32e59826-6482-11e6-975c-428c77fee95d.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-17 18:56:04</created>
		<closed>2016-10-25 16:37:22</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>561</id>
		<title>Changes to value sets are not being kept</title>
		<body>I know for a fact, that I deleted a bunch of value sets for optional fields (blue box below) and updated a bunch of value sets to user defined ones (red box below). Yet, they are now back to the original default value sets. Bad IGAMT, bad.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17748412/e329cf58-647e-11e6-8ffc-975298554bd4.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-17 18:33:05</created>
		<closed>2016-10-11 14:17:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>554</id>
		<title>export to WORD says [MISSING IMAGE]</title>
		<body>Working on an IG that exports to WORD. I added a jpeg image. Exporting to WORD has message [MISSING IMAGE]. Export to html brings the image.  Also, import into word takes a long time and occasionally hangs. It has a popup that indicates that fields in document point elsewhere and asks to update from links. </body>
		<created>2016-08-17 14:28:33</created>
		<closed>2016-10-17 15:24:13</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>553</id>
		<title>sections not all being exported</title>
		<body>I'm working on the Use Case section of my IG. I've moved a few sections around and deleted a couple, but now, not all of the sections that in IGAMT are in the exported documents (Word or HTML). For example, the red arrow below highlights the "scenarios" section (I think that was an original section that came with the template) but it's not in the HTML output.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17676315/a27bd352-62f3-11e6-9842-0cd4f10181dd.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17676378/e3d61d3a-62f3-11e6-8eff-e16dac18cd96.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-15 19:24:18</created>
		<closed>2016-09-26 21:55:03</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>552</id>
		<title>Images cannot be resized</title>
		<body>I've inserted a couple of images into a text box and I can't resize them either within IGAMT itself or by resizing them in another program and saving the larger image. Plus when I export to a Word document the images are missing. </body>
		<created>2016-08-15 19:20:46</created>
		<closed>2016-09-08 22:44:24</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>551</id>
		<title>MSH delete prevented</title>
		<body>I cloned an MSH and renamed. I linked that MSH to a cloned segment (one that did not allow rename when cloned and edited). tried to delete the old MSH and got the can't delete because still linked.  [delete old msh.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/418308/delete.old.msh.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-08-15 15:16:32</created>
		<closed>2016-08-17 16:29:51</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>550</id>
		<title>name change on cloned segment fails</title>
		<body>I created a clone of Z42, renamed, saved, got successful save message, but title in left hand box does not change.  Repeated 4 times [profile name change.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/418277/profile.name.change.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-08-15 15:06:18</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 22:14:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>548</id>
		<title>Definition Text tables don't represent well in the Word document</title>
		<body>Tables built in the Definition Text doesn't seem to be exported the same. In the example below, the Component Name column seems too narrow in the Word document and none of the table borders are there making it tough to read.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17633166/8fd93780-6091-11e6-827f-6a6806926429.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17633142/7a4697b4-6091-11e6-9b6c-2b80153a2d6c.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-12 18:36:25</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 22:28:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>547</id>
		<title>triggering of the "save" button is inconsistent</title>
		<body>If you open an existing user defined segment and just update an existing Definition Text, it doesn't activate the "save" button. You have to go and edit something else to be able to save the change. However, if you try to move away from the segment to a new one, you do get the "confirmation" pop up to save or discard the changes so it's not clear if you need to save the change to get it to persist. Either way, either the Save button needs to light up or the confirmation box needs to go away so it consistently reflects what has to happen for the text change to persist </body>
		<created>2016-08-12 18:23:57</created>
		<closed>2016-09-14 16:58:16</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>542</id>
		<title>Export of Data Types</title>
		<body>It appears the only data types exported in the Word document are the user defined data types. In the examples below there are examples of: - custom data types (red box) - standard complex data type (purple box) - "varies" data type (blue box) - standard atomic data type (black box)  Of these only the custom data type seems to make it into the exported IG. The purple box is my fault (it should have a custom data type), but the blue and black boxes are scenarios where the data type needs to be in the IG. In general, is there any reason not to export the data type regardless of whether or not it's custom or standard?  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17631223/d61cbf04-6088-11e6-846b-416a7aff03d2.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17631201/af0c1dce-6088-11e6-8e2e-675c4b1891f6.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-12 17:35:55</created>
		<closed>2016-09-27 13:30:04</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>539</id>
		<title>Conformance Statement at the profile level not published</title>
		<body>When exporting to a Word document, it appears that the profile level Conformance Statements are not included in the document anywhere.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17630849/db85e968-6086-11e6-9818-0b3465c962f1.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-12 17:19:10</created>
		<closed>2016-12-02 22:15:14</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>538</id>
		<title>Value sets in the Word document after they've been removed from IGAMT segments</title>
		<body>I've removed the default value sets from all optional elements in segment records (reader should refer back to the base standard, the IG is silent on optional elements). But even though the value sets are removed in IGAMT (green box below), they still show up in the exported Word Document (red box below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17630145/a58722d0-6083-11e6-989c-6c8f17814eb3.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-12 16:57:00</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 22:29:24</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>535</id>
		<title>Firefox script warning</title>
		<body>I've been getting this error periodically (once per hour of IGAMT use or so) when I use IGAMT in Firefox. I've never seen it when using Chrome. I haven't noticed a pattern as to when it appears. Most recently it was when going from a table to a user segment. It doesn't seem to keep me from doing anything.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17625800/00be31ca-6070-11e6-8d96-5a9d0443c43d.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-12 14:35:51</created>
		<closed>2016-10-03 15:24:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>534</id>
		<title>Search for PHINVADS value set doesn't seem to work</title>
		<body>I can't figure out how to find PHINVADS value sets. No matter what I search for, I can't find any value sets. For example, I need to create a value set for these values:  Value Set Name – Funding Eligibility Observation Method (IIS)  Value Set OID - 2.16.840.1.114222.4.11.6039 Value Set Code: PHVS_FundingEligibilityObsMethod_IIS Value set definition: The Funding Eligibility Observation Method identifies the method for capturing funding program eligibility. Note that it is always reported at the immunization level. Used in OBX- 17  Concept Names   Concept code    Code System Identifier – HL7 Table 0396 Eligibility captured at the immunization level  VXC40   CDCPHINVS Eligibility captured at the visit level VXC41   CDCPHINVS  But no matter what I search, I can't find anything. Am I doing something wrong?  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17625660/6acf4028-606f-11e6-87b6-e943c6cb2e52.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-12 14:31:51</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 21:55:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>532</id>
		<title>adding multiple values in a value set causes focus issues</title>
		<body>This one is a bit odd.  Create a value set and click the "Add Value" several times so that you get multiple blank values: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17625053/c0bc3b88-606c-11e6-8d21-d9762f1ec865.png)  If you click in one of the fields, and start typing, only the first character is recorded (no matter how many you enter) and you have to reclick in the field to restore the cursor and keep typing ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17625095/eee21014-606c-11e6-883e-315c5c45382f.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-12 14:14:13</created>
		<closed>2016-09-26 21:55:25</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>528</id>
		<title>Missing tables</title>
		<body>Table 0396 missing from 2.8.2 (and probably others) as a default.  Always need to get this table from the HL7 site. This applies to all versions, not just 2.8.2.  Also, table 360 and 361 also seem to be missing.  Need sort option to help better find tables. </body>
		<created>2016-08-11 22:23:36</created>
		<closed>2016-10-03 16:40:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>527</id>
		<title>Value Sets in 2.8.2 have multiple copies </title>
		<body>![capture](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14874904/17606897/09df0246-5ff0-11e6-98c8-ab835e77690c.PNG)  I just created a new 2.8.2 IG and there are a number of USR value sets. Also, some are CDCREC, which I know Craig created but how did they end up in mind? </body>
		<created>2016-08-11 22:20:37</created>
		<closed>2016-08-31 21:26:05</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>519</id>
		<title>ACK message Structure Id "typo"</title>
		<body>The ACK message Structure Id has an extra underscore (probably due to it's "varies" option). Might want to remove that.  &lt;img width="962" alt="screen shot 2016-08-11 at 11 43 41 am" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14352180/17594947/14f74e5e-5fb9-11e6-9cd1-c27407b4435d.png"&gt; </body>
		<created>2016-08-11 15:45:22</created>
		<closed>2017-02-22 14:52:43</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>514</id>
		<title>Value set IDs don't sort nicely for numbers</title>
		<body>When the value set code is a number, they don't seem to sort properly. In the example below the values in the blue boxes interrupt the normal sequence of codes (9, 10, 11, 12, etc)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17591934/e03ea74c-5fa5-11e6-9b93-cc98f3d85a61.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-11 14:29:12</created>
		<closed>2017-03-03 15:23:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>513</id>
		<title>server error on save</title>
		<body>I copied use case section, deleted interaction section from one, clicked on the cloned interaction section. A popup asked to save before leaving. I saved and got a popup stating save failed due to error on server. </body>
		<created>2016-08-11 13:57:03</created>
		<closed>2016-08-17 14:55:56</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>483</id>
		<title>clicking link of segment in message does not work</title>
		<body>Working in my profile, I click on the name(link) of segment. I get the "do you want to leave" message. I click yes. The pop-up disappears and I remain on the message page. </body>
		<created>2016-08-09 14:20:54</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 21:58:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>478</id>
		<title>Cardinality is wrong for a few fields</title>
		<body>In v2.8.2 base, the PID-13 and -14 fields are allowed to repeat (even though they have a usage of B) - see blue box below. but in the base segment definition, the cardinality is 0..1 (green box below). I think it should be 0..*  Other fields may be similarly affected (in fact all of the repeating fields in the screen shot below have this issue)..   ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17445863/43274a06-5b0c-11e6-8f01-657acda27dd1.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17445815/16789b4a-5b0c-11e6-8543-baa5a2fe6bb1.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-05 18:00:01</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 16:48:35</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>470</id>
		<title>can't add value sets</title>
		<body>All of a sudden, I can't add any value sets. I've tried 3 or 4 different ones (alone and in pairs) and while I get a "table is successfully save" announcement, the tables don't show up in the Value Set list. Maybe the get added but not displayed? At the very bottom of the value set list there is a funny looking "bbb" (see red arrow below)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17415123/01ad8c70-5a4e-11e6-8f3f-1d536d1516f7.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-04 19:19:01</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 22:00:24</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>469</id>
		<title>can't add conformance statement to a data type</title>
		<body>I created a user data type for XPN and need to add a conformance statement to the name type (XPN.7) but when I click on the the add icon, nothing happens </body>
		<created>2016-08-04 18:47:34</created>
		<closed>2016-08-17 14:21:36</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>468</id>
		<title>can't add predicate to a data type</title>
		<body>I've created a couple of user specific data types and set the Usage of one component to C. I get the little indicator that a predicate is needed, but when I click on it nothing happens. I can't find any way to add a predicate. </body>
		<created>2016-08-04 17:51:25</created>
		<closed>2016-08-17 14:21:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>464</id>
		<title>value set cross referencing is not working</title>
		<body>Even when a value set is bound to a data type which is used in a custom segment which is used in a profile, the cross reference tab in the value set still says it's not being used. Cross referencing at the segment and data type level seems to work fine.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17407630/9b431c54-5a2d-11e6-8a1e-4f8785ccd3bd.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17407662/cba02b4e-5a2d-11e6-82db-f8114b06eef1.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-04 15:34:19</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 22:02:12</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>463</id>
		<title>can't add new data type</title>
		<body>I have created a clone of the data type table with ED data type in it. I tried to add to the data type list and don't see it in the pull down list. [ed datatype.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/401965/ed.datatype.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-08-04 15:23:25</created>
		<closed>2016-09-22 15:28:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>462</id>
		<title>value set name doesn't update</title>
		<body>When a custom value set is created it is assigned an ID suffix (red arrow below) which is part of the value set record but also used as the ID in the data type it is bound to:  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17407369/9cb19562-5a2c-11e6-9e77-e99ad1858b26.png)  but if you doing the binding and then update the ID suffix, the name of the value set in the data type is not updated (see difference between red and blue arrows below). If a value set ID is updated, it needs to be updated in places that use it. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17407495/1b2144f6-5a2d-11e6-94a4-3dc1b6b8c55f.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-04 15:23:24</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 22:27:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>460</id>
		<title>Extensibility of "close" won't save</title>
		<body>When updating a custom value set, if the Extensibility is set to "close", it is not possible to save the value set. If you set any other attribute or set Extensibility to "open" and click the save button, you get a popup in the upper right corner saying the value set was saved, but if Extensibility is set to "close", you don't get that popup and if you try to migrate to a different section of the IG, you get the "unsaved data" warning. If you click "save and continue" in this popup, nothing happens. If you "discard changes", you do move away and the changes are lost.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17406805/97f521b2-5a2a-11e6-9252-7e9ccf2684ae.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-04 15:03:03</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 22:00:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>459</id>
		<title>get O to X question when trying to save a newly associated segment</title>
		<body>[o2x.pdf](https://github.com/haffonist/igamt/files/399836/o2x.pdf) </body>
		<created>2016-08-03 15:55:45</created>
		<closed>2016-08-19 14:48:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>458</id>
		<title>Cross reference statement is inaccurate</title>
		<body>if a table (or data type or anything) is not cross referenced, the text statement says "segment" rather than table (or whatever is appropriate. This will confuse people  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17370231/e5153a92-5960-11e6-8515-914f4b97d96b.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-03 14:59:49</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 21:55:59</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>457</id>
		<title>Value set search doesn't always work</title>
		<body>I tried to add a value set to elements in a custom MSG data type. When I tried to search for the "event type" value set by entering "e" into the search box, no results were returned even though there were clearly multiple value sets starting with "e".  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17305377/ca155500-57ef-11e6-8a1b-4fece8d96189.png)  "m" works fine as a search value and even brings up things like "admission type (0007)" which is probably too permissive  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17305482/24b00ea6-57f0-11e6-9afa-9771e331dbc8.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-01 18:59:45</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 21:58:09</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>456</id>
		<title>hitting "enter" while searching for a value set does the unexpected</title>
		<body>I tried to search for a value set to associate with an element in a custom MSG data type. I typed in a few characters and hit "enter". As soon as I hit enter, I got a popup box that asked if I wanted to Change Usage from O to X. This doesn't seem like the right behavior  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17305143/c0d0d20e-57ee-11e6-97ca-0df84d4a72bd.png) </body>
		<created>2016-08-01 18:51:27</created>
		<closed>2016-08-18 21:59:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>451</id>
		<title>autosave locks pull down </title>
		<body>When editing a cloned segment, I tried to create a new conformance statement. If I had a pull down open (in process of selecting) and autosave occurred, that drop down was locked and empty. I cancelled and recreated the CF, without problem. Went to create a second CF and encountered same problem. </body>
		<created>2016-08-01 18:20:53</created>
		<closed>2017-03-03 18:56:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>450</id>
		<title>export in Word produces blank document</title>
		<body>I tried to export in Word. I get a blank document with the following text:  {"text":"internalError","resourceId":null,"skip":false,"manualHandle":"false","scope":null,"version":null,"date":null,"id":null,"type":"danger"} </body>
		<created>2016-08-01 18:01:04</created>
		<closed>2016-09-09 12:52:41</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>442</id>
		<title>Value Set City Places (NCHS) is too big causing system to hang</title>
		<body>Per Harold request, it needs to be paginated.  </body>
		<created>2016-07-29 13:32:12</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 22:26:37</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>441</id>
		<title>IGAMT Login issue</title>
		<body>My IG is not displayed, when I first log in. It takes a second login to see it.  </body>
		<created>2016-07-29 12:31:55</created>
		<closed>2016-09-08 22:44:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>439</id>
		<title>Definition text doesn't show up in the Word document</title>
		<body>Even though I added Definition Text for the first two elements in a user defined EI data type, this text doesn't show up in the Word Document.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17224176/8038bd5a-54c5-11e6-8999-1811f9a92f8b.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17224238/b38006d2-54c5-11e6-93d4-c73b6b7c401b.png) </body>
		<created>2016-07-28 18:18:05</created>
		<closed>2016-09-07 21:10:34</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>438</id>
		<title>value set names don't render correctly</title>
		<body>In the Word Document export, user defined value sets don't render correctly. In the example below, the value set is named 0126_01 but in the word document it retains it's original (random?) identifier  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17224065/f5f52836-54c4-11e6-934c-ec012b55ac89.png) ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17224070/fc140ad4-54c4-11e6-92fd-a5bfefccb0c6.png) ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17224109/1e69c2cc-54c5-11e6-9522-5e3d5028d87c.png) </body>
		<created>2016-07-28 18:14:10</created>
		<closed>2016-08-31 20:12:56</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>437</id>
		<title>User defined data types not named right</title>
		<body>In the Word document export, user defined data types (ones copied from the basic data type) have bad name. Rather than using the data type extension (01 in the example below), it just seems to repeat the data type name.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17224018/bd5e538a-54c4-11e6-94ab-099491e0e3a8.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/17223975/8f880c58-54c4-11e6-9e7a-a6825d5366bf.png) </body>
		<created>2016-07-28 18:11:50</created>
		<closed>2016-09-20 15:50:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>435</id>
		<title>no table 0396</title>
		<body>the coding system HL7 table 0396 doesn't seem to be in version 2.8.2 </body>
		<created>2016-07-28 17:03:02</created>
		<closed>2016-10-03 16:40:19</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>432</id>
		<title>No ACK in message list for 2.8.1</title>
		<body>Creating a new IG from standard. ACK not in list of messages. </body>
		<created>2016-07-27 18:08:32</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 16:49:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>427</id>
		<title>Check the format Pattern verbiage </title>
		<body>The tool is generating the following formatted CS:   The value of HD.2(Universal ID) SHALL be valid in format: 'ISO-compliant OID'.  It should be something like this (per IZ tool):   The value of HD.2 (Universal ID) SHALL be formatted with ISO-compliant OID. </body>
		<created>2016-07-25 21:34:12</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 21:01:07</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>408</id>
		<title>Unable to delete a segment</title>
		<body>A "segment Not Found" message is generated when trying to delete a segment from the table of contents. </body>
		<created>2016-07-22 14:52:26</created>
		<closed>2016-08-02 17:05:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>399</id>
		<title>Value set binding not working</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-06-24 12:47:23</created>
		<closed>2016-10-03 15:31:42</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>385</id>
		<title>no Table of Contents</title>
		<body>when I create a brand new IG, there is no table of contents  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15894792/8376fb7a-2d4d-11e6-8815-1741af044d36.png) </body>
		<created>2016-06-08 12:49:33</created>
		<closed>2016-07-26 14:56:00</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>384</id>
		<title>Adding a value set doesn't seem to work</title>
		<body>When I'm in a custom data type, if I remove the original (base) value set and try to bind a new value set, it doesn't work. I can select a value set but clicking the save button doesn't seem to do anything.   If I don't remove the original value set, but rather just select the pencil icon, it does allow me to save the new value set. </body>
		<created>2016-06-07 20:03:20</created>
		<closed>2016-06-17 18:22:58</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>378</id>
		<title>variation in "document date"</title>
		<body>I've got different formats for the "document date" column in the list of my IGs (see arrows below). Oddly, event though I've edited both documents # 1 and 3 today, the date continues to be in the past? Is the Document Date intended to the the last edited date or the document creation date? (assuming the May 24 date is related to the fact that documents 2 and 3 existed before the most recent update of the tool)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15684873/ca0a1600-272e-11e6-96b5-ce155091932c.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 17:56:40</created>
		<closed>2016-10-03 15:21:44</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>377</id>
		<title>value set search persists between value sets</title>
		<body>If you do a search in a value set and then leave the value set to go to another one, the search persists. For example, if i search for the letter O in the race value set and then go to the patient class value set, only those patient classes containing an O will display.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15684241/d630d7f0-272b-11e6-9a22-399eb764e5f0.png)  It is possible to clear the search, but it may be misleading if people don't realize the search is still in force. Ideally, the search would be cleared when moving between value sets.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15684253/e8080d36-272b-11e6-9b36-24da48c66e01.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 17:35:45</created>
		<closed>2016-08-19 01:47:44</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>374</id>
		<title>duplicate Description in value sets</title>
		<body>The value set activity shows the description twice. Interestingly, if you put the cursor in one of the boxes and edit the text, it immediately shows up in the other box. Is there an intention that these should be different or is this a duplication?  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15683651/06bcf208-2729-11e6-8eff-3eadf88db4dc.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 17:14:31</created>
		<closed>2016-08-19 01:51:23</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>373</id>
		<title>User created value sets won't save</title>
		<body>I copied a data type and modified the MetaData. I clicked the save button but nothing apparently happened because when I go to navigate away from the new value set, I get the warning confirmation box.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15683561/acda36f6-2728-11e6-8a4c-1fb166ad8a9f.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 17:11:51</created>
		<closed>2016-07-29 15:48:21</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>372</id>
		<title>Data Type Purpose and Use doesn't seem to save</title>
		<body>I copied a data type and entered a Purpose and Use, Comment and Definition Text. When I saved the record it seemed to save (see green banner below). But when I navigate away from the data type and come back, only the Comment and Definition Text are there. The Purpose and Use doesn't seem to be saved.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15683391/b97bb1ec-2727-11e6-85a0-3a69851adf75.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 17:05:08</created>
		<closed>2016-08-02 23:57:02</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>371</id>
		<title>getting mixed messages...</title>
		<body>When adding text to the Conformance Profile MetaData and then hitting save, you get a message of "Message Saved" but the red header suggests there was an error. Did it save or not? It's hard to tell.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15683104/5d3b4ace-2726-11e6-8659-ae74df72509d.png)  Then, if you try to leave, you get the usual conformation box: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15683171/9e32a9aa-2726-11e6-950e-a0b8179776f9.png)  In general, if you move to a profile section and then try to leave (without making any changes). you sill get this pop up asking about discarding changes. ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15683216/d6db51e4-2726-11e6-9105-235085f09ecd.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 16:57:54</created>
		<closed>2016-08-02 23:56:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>370</id>
		<title>Link editor cuts off</title>
		<body>When trying to insert a link when the text editor is empty, the last of the link editor is cut off. You can access it by tabbing through the fields (URL -&gt; Text -&gt; Open in new window) but you can't go straight to the check box.   ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15682571/f42639a6-2723-11e6-88df-26733f13703e.png)  This is not a problem when there is significant text already in the box ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15682638/442e3ade-2724-11e6-9888-d6598645037d.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 16:53:48</created>
		<closed>2016-08-31 21:29:20</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>369</id>
		<title>No way to insert a file</title>
		<body>It's not possible to insert a file. I am trying this with a simple .txt file. It doesn't matter if I drag and drop or browse for the file.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15682473/776b392a-2723-11e6-993a-6722fa71c192.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 16:33:44</created>
		<closed>2016-08-17 16:46:26</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>368</id>
		<title>no way to insert an image</title>
		<body>When I try to drag and drop an image, there is an error and it doesn't take.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15682324/bc798b12-2722-11e6-9388-ece0773f8df0.png)  Browsing for the image results in the same thing. </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 16:29:41</created>
		<closed>2016-08-02 23:56:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>367</id>
		<title>copied sections don't persist</title>
		<body>In a test document, I created a new section (red arrow below) and then copied a couple of sections (blue arrows) including the section with a new section (green arrow). I then closed the document and re-opened it. When I did that, the only thing that was retained was the newly created section. None of the duplicated sections were retained.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15681635/96f14d24-271f-11e6-8949-a1bc0d63084c.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 16:07:50</created>
		<closed>2016-08-17 16:42:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>366</id>
		<title>Copied sections can't be saved</title>
		<body>I've tried to copy both the Actor and Use Case sections and in both cases, it's not possible to change the Title or Content and save the section. It is possible to save the original section.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15681217/0e11c4e4-271e-11e6-96c2-1ccb59b5ee96.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-31 15:55:10</created>
		<closed>2016-06-17 18:19:04</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>365</id>
		<title>PDF ToC pages are not granular enough</title>
		<body>The PDF table of contents lists page number that are inaccurate. In the example below sections 3.2.1 and 3.2.2 are on page 13 but the table of contents show page 10 (presumably because that is where section 3 starts)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15588239/7bfad0ce-2352-11e6-9900-cad48a5ff50a.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-26 20:01:09</created>
		<closed>2016-08-31 21:23:22</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>364</id>
		<title>spurious underscore</title>
		<body>there is a spurious _ in the table of contents of the PDF document when segments are listed. I'm not sure if this related to expect a flavor suffix or something else, but it looks odd and will confuse people. It is also there for data types when there isn't a data type flavor.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15588063/c665cd86-2351-11e6-9a7b-fb2c6c72429d.png)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15588124/0b2632da-2352-11e6-924b-6daead6f9860.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-26 19:56:43</created>
		<closed>2016-06-20 17:19:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>363</id>
		<title>Update bar is hidden</title>
		<body>A while back you added a notification bar at the top of the screen when an action was taken (or couldn't be taken) like the document is save. It seems like that bar is hidden behind the NIST-IGAMT header. See arrow below for what I mean. This screen shot was immediately after saving a section.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15587973/55089826-2351-11e6-9a82-804e33b4a028.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-26 19:52:46</created>
		<closed>2016-06-02 20:36:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>362</id>
		<title>lack of notification when data is missing</title>
		<body>If required fields (highlighted in red) are required before a section can be saved, then it would be nice to have a notification to that effect. the button changes color when saving is possible but it's pretty subtle (see image below) and when you click on the "greyed out" save button, it does nothing, but there's clear indication that nothing is happening (but it doesn't really do a whole lot that is obvious to a user, when you are allowed to save)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15587869/e6591d92-2350-11e6-9d67-9f15f5ebbf4c.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-26 19:49:07</created>
		<closed>2016-09-08 23:02:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>361</id>
		<title>blank sections retain previous text</title>
		<body>When you move from one section of the IG to another, if the new section is empty (no text in the Contents section), the text from the previous section is show. For example below, Actors has legitimate text but when I move from Actors to General Assumptions (which has no text), the Actors text persists.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/15586522/755cc7de-234a-11e6-83f7-f2ab543b758c.png) </body>
		<created>2016-05-26 19:04:12</created>
		<closed>2016-06-02 20:37:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>354</id>
		<title>Display of T/F</title>
		<body>Per Rob: "Created flavor but doesn’t display T/F" </body>
		<created>2016-04-27 18:13:36</created>
		<closed>2016-06-01 17:22:06</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>353</id>
		<title>No value set at primitive level</title>
		<body>From Rob: I accidentally hit the X for value set now I can’t get it back. I should be able to. See attachment.  Also, if the DT is not for coded elements at the primitive level then there should be no option to add a value set. ![vs](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14842422/14861004/4b4cd958-0c79-11e6-94d9-737906057c2e.png) </body>
		<created>2016-04-27 17:11:26</created>
		<closed>2016-06-01 18:07:40</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>352</id>
		<title>Can't edit edit a code system.</title>
		<body>When a new code is added,  I can’t edit it to add a different code system. See attachment. ![codesys](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/14842422/14860893/d9a10c5c-0c78-11e6-8c7c-33edc7e07654.png) </body>
		<created>2016-04-27 17:08:03</created>
		<closed>2016-06-17 18:22:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>349</id>
		<title>value set value delete is behaving erratically</title>
		<body>I'm seeing odd behavior when I delete values from a value set. I started out by copying value set 0203. I then set about deleting some extraneous values that weren't relevant to the context i was going to use the value set in.  (1) the purple boxes highlight some key value to keep an eye on. I then deleted "Health Care Number" (2) that resulted in the blue boxes. The top value of "Patient Internal Identifier" remained at the top of the list, and "License Number" and "Local Registry ID" moved up. I then deleted "License Number" and that's when things got odd (3) as shown by the green boxes, not only was "License Number" removed and "Local Registry ID" moved up, but "Patient internal identifier" also seemed to have disappeared, to be replaced by "Person number"  If you continue the deleting values, you see the pattern that every other time, the top value in the list if replaced by a new value.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/14827071/4181d096-0ba6-11e6-9cde-82a8faadd2a9.png) </body>
		<created>2016-04-26 17:04:35</created>
		<closed>2016-06-20 17:19:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>348</id>
		<title>data type flavor data doesn't all show up when part of a different data type</title>
		<body>I created a new data type (CE_1 in red below) and then used it as the data type fro CQ.2 but when I expanded CQ.2, while the Usages were accurate for the first 4 elements, the Conditional Usages didn't have the True/False usages nor did the condition predicates show up as documented in the CE_1 data type (purple boxes)  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/14824928/5f9a782a-0b9d-11e6-86c1-97b45c46be53.png) </body>
		<created>2016-04-26 15:57:38</created>
		<closed>2016-06-20 17:17:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>345</id>
		<title>creating a new data type adversely affects the table of contents order</title>
		<body>If you create a new data type flavor, the nicely alphabetical Table of Contents list of data types goes out the window and you're left with a seemingly randomly sorted list which makes it tough to find the data type you want.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/14824394/6bde9726-0b9b-11e6-8aa2-436ca78aea9e.png) </body>
		<created>2016-04-26 15:42:34</created>
		<closed>2016-06-02 20:39:26</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>341</id>
		<title>No support to provide binding to two separate value sets.</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-04-13 14:13:34</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 21:30:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>340</id>
		<title>No support for the assigment of data type when the field's data type varies</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-04-13 13:51:20</created>
		<closed>2016-08-17 16:46:41</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>339</id>
		<title>No support for adding a segment flavor</title>
		<body>IGAMT is not supporting adding a segment flavor list to a profile. </body>
		<created>2016-04-13 13:47:30</created>
		<closed>2016-06-01 17:56:30</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>334</id>
		<title>Context menu latency</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-04-08 18:21:44</created>
		<closed>2016-06-01 17:46:45</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>330</id>
		<title>Segments missing Data Types</title>
		<body>I just noticed that some segments are missing data type and I can't assign a DT flavor to them. </body>
		<created>2016-04-07 14:07:24</created>
		<closed>2016-06-01 17:52:51</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>328</id>
		<title>Can't load Value Sets </title>
		<body>I can't load the following value sets, it might be related to the size.  Cause of Death (ICD-10) 2 -.16.840.1.114222.4.11.3593  County, Coding System HL7 2x (HL70396) - 2.16.840.1.114222.4.11.7162 </body>
		<created>2016-04-06 15:29:49</created>
		<closed>2016-07-22 19:21:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>319</id>
		<title>Word doesn't respect the "quote" format for tables</title>
		<body>When a table is embedded in text that is formatted with the "Quote" format in the text editor, the formatting (the purple color of the text) is not applied to the table.  Also, if Paragraph Format (Heading 4) is applied to the table title, then Word creates a new sub-section for the table. This seems problematic (see previous comment #316 for a previous noting of this)  Also note that the alternate line shading applied in IGAMT is not present in the Word export.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/14251544/27f04a9a-fa49-11e5-979a-0412b3e7b13c.png) </body>
		<created>2016-04-04 14:47:15</created>
		<closed>2016-10-25 15:22:43</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>310</id>
		<title>Issue with copying "Use Case"</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-04-01 04:19:59</created>
		<closed>2016-06-01 17:46:31</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>309</id>
		<title>added sections don't stick around</title>
		<body>I've added new segments in the Use Case section. I've saved the changes, but when I close the guide, log out and log back in, the sections are gone.  Before (blue arrows note the new sections) ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/14110351/a1ff9128-f58b-11e5-9a84-46a8f74568aa.png)  After: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/14110371/b44edb9a-f58b-11e5-8fd3-8a7fcc2a6d64.png) </body>
		<created>2016-03-29 13:54:58</created>
		<closed>2016-06-02 20:32:39</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>304</id>
		<title>Title edits don't always show up in the TOC</title>
		<body>If the name of a section is edited, the change isn't always displayed in the table of contents. It appears that the TOC does not display the name if the TOC node has sub nodes (see red arrows in the example below).   In this example, the name of Use Case -- 66 was changed to Use Case 1, but that change isn't apparent (even after saving the document) in the TOC. The name of the next 3 nodes had "xx" appended onto the end. But only changes to the Actors and Preconditions nodes appear in the TOC.  ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/14028179/3a723256-f1c9-11e5-8aa5-e23b36232afb.png) </body>
		<created>2016-03-24 19:06:45</created>
		<closed>2016-06-02 20:32:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>289</id>
		<title>exports failling</title>
		<body>All exports are failing with this message:  {"text":"internalError","resourceId":null,"skip":false,"manualHandle":"false","type":"danger"} </body>
		<created>2016-03-21 19:57:00</created>
		<closed>2016-04-06 21:14:28</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>287</id>
		<title>adding a new profile may result in the profile not being editable</title>
		<body>When adding a profile by right clicking "Conformance Profile" in an existing IG, if you add a new message type one not already listed as a profile, the new profile isn't actually accessible. If you select the conformance profile, the workspace doesn't update to allow you to work on the profile. Oddly, if you add a new profile this way where the message type is already part of the IG, this problem does not manifest itself (the new profile can be opened and edited). </body>
		<created>2016-03-21 19:40:25</created>
		<closed>2016-07-25 14:05:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>285</id>
		<title>Can't add Code Systems</title>
		<body>Something seems to have broken with the functionality to add Code Systems to a value set. The icons changed but I can't figure out how to add a new code system. When I hit the pencil (edit I assume) icon, a new plus (add?) icon appears, but clicking it does nothing. I was able to delete an existing code system but I can't add new ones </body>
		<created>2016-03-21 19:27:04</created>
		<closed>2016-03-22 14:51:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>265</id>
		<title>Data type "varies" - not suppported</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-03-16 16:17:59</created>
		<closed>2016-09-14 21:49:04</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>264</id>
		<title>Creating a predicate for a list of values</title>
		<body>The tool does not indicate which separator to use. </body>
		<created>2016-03-16 16:12:39</created>
		<closed>2016-03-22 15:03:37</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>262</id>
		<title>Constraints Path is incorrect </title>
		<body>PID-2.1 instead of PID.2.1 </body>
		<created>2016-03-16 15:51:34</created>
		<closed>2016-03-22 15:01:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>261</id>
		<title>Update Constraints Path</title>
		<body>For ex. Should be MSH.2.1 instead of 2[1].1[1] </body>
		<created>2016-03-16 15:19:20</created>
		<closed>2016-03-22 15:00:10</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>259</id>
		<title>Toc Context menu hangs there</title>
		<body>On every second attempt to edit copy/delete a datatype, the context menu seems not responding.  Harold </body>
		<created>2016-03-15 16:23:56</created>
		<closed>2016-04-07 19:07:24</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>258</id>
		<title>Segments flavor -- system halting</title>
		<body>I can't create a segment flavor, system halts when trying to save the new segment.  </body>
		<created>2016-03-14 14:34:18</created>
		<closed>2016-03-16 22:31:57</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>257</id>
		<title>Having issues deleting Data types</title>
		<body>Created a copy of a DT and can’t remove it. </body>
		<created>2016-03-11 21:16:13</created>
		<closed>2016-03-16 22:32:49</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>251</id>
		<title>output of comments has issues</title>
		<body>The treatment of comments seems a little off.  I entered a Metadata comment for the IDS data type and it showed up in the PDF in a couple of places (purple boxes) ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13710414/fba93c44-e77e-11e5-89cc-67994c5460d0.png)  I then added a Metadata comment, and a Defin.Text and Comment for JCC.1 but only two of them show up in the PDF ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13710552/c03d01b2-e77f-11e5-9adc-5bae810fdaa7.png)  PDF output: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13710211/b127053a-e77d-11e5-8b2b-db438a6203ec.png) </body>
		<created>2016-03-11 17:58:40</created>
		<closed>2016-04-06 21:14:37</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>247</id>
		<title>table render has some issues</title>
		<body>Some of the fancier table formatting options don't render well.  From IGAMT: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13709744/211c484e-e77b-11e5-82b1-9d37ba191033.png)  From the PDF: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13709767/38339eba-e77b-11e5-8e60-139434d42b57.png)  From the HTML: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13709789/5487e56c-e77b-11e5-8099-f81e3268424d.png)  From the Word document: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13709826/89304264-e77b-11e5-86eb-001105bf05d5.png) </body>
		<created>2016-03-11 17:23:02</created>
		<closed>2016-10-24 15:58:56</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>244</id>
		<title>publication issues with fancy text</title>
		<body>The text editor includes a lot of different formatting options, some of which don't render correctly in all publication formats. From the editor: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13708593/20a171c4-e775-11e5-8e2a-c6ae777df64d.png)  From the PDF format: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13708605/30130f78-e775-11e5-9d27-71a74c601534.png)  From the HTML format: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13708682/97e328ea-e775-11e5-827d-25af1fd3ad6d.png)  From the Word format: ![image](https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/17408249/13708809/292eb9cc-e776-11e5-8418-91e56190d98b.png) </body>
		<created>2016-03-11 16:44:33</created>
		<closed>2016-10-24 17:47:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>239</id>
		<title>Data type flavors replacing base DT in optional elements</title>
		<body>Added HD_VR_AA flavor, the tool changed all the HD data types to this flavors including the HD_VR that I created and also the the DT in the Optional fields. </body>
		<created>2016-03-11 15:14:28</created>
		<closed>2016-03-15 16:16:32</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>238</id>
		<title>IMPORT HL7 DB 2.7.1 and 2.8 Received from Rob</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-03-09 21:47:31</created>
		<closed>2016-08-29 16:48:52</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>236</id>
		<title>Collapsing Conformance Profiles node does not hide the conformance profiles sometimes</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-03-09 16:57:21</created>
		<closed>2016-04-08 18:21:17</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>216</id>
		<title>text editor closes unexpectedly</title>
		<body>The editor window will close unexpectedly. Type some text and then use the mouse to highlight some text. Without releasing the left mouse button, drag the cursor so that it is outside of the text box. When you release the mouse button, the editor window closes. It seems to save any changes, but it's odd behavior. </body>
		<created>2016-02-25 18:48:23</created>
		<closed>2016-06-02 20:29:27</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>135</id>
		<title>ToC open/close icons have stopped displaying properly with the change to IGDocument structure.</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-01-27 14:40:17</created>
		<closed>2016-02-16 22:44:55</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>128</id>
		<title>Fix delete message (conformance profile)</title>
		<body>- Need to remove dead segment, datatype, valueSets etc... </body>
		<created>2016-01-08 21:30:54</created>
		<closed>2016-02-29 16:34:29</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>120</id>
		<title>Fix Create IG</title>
		<body>- Set the User Creating the IG in the newly created IG. </body>
		<created>2016-01-08 20:50:03</created>
		<closed>2016-01-27 14:35:47</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>117</id>
		<title>Delete IG from user list: if current IG delete from edit area. </title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2016-01-08 19:56:38</created>
		<closed>2016-02-16 22:43:08</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>116</id>
		<title>When items are selected int he ToC, highlighting does not extend the full with of the item's text.</title>
		<body>Fixed.  Highlighting now extends for 400px, which should be sufficient. </body>
		<created>2016-01-08 18:56:19</created>
		<closed>2016-02-16 22:45:01</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>115</id>
		<title>The IG list is not being populated from the db. Suspect the newly created IG is not being saved.</title>
		<body>Done IG was indeed being saved, but sans an accountId.   The REST method for save was throwing an error when the accountId was null. ProfileController.save... was calling findProfile(id);  the return value was not being used.  Call has been removed. We now set the accountId in the js during the save function.  </body>
		<created>2016-01-08 17:21:28</created>
		<closed>2016-02-16 22:44:46</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>114</id>
		<title>IG edit form fields are not all synching with the visible fields in the IG list.</title>
		<body>Done IG list fields were bound to the wrong fields in the model. </body>
		<created>2016-01-08 17:11:55</created>
		<closed>2016-02-16 22:44:50</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>77</id>
		<title>Create IG from DB  11/23</title>
		<body>Fix the create IG feature. This will involve updating the client and server and adding unit tests. </body>
		<created>2015-11-17 20:51:16</created>
		<closed>2015-12-08 17:07:36</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>72</id>
		<title>Value Set bug fix</title>
		<body>Fixed bug to show eror when the user create new value </body>
		<created>2015-11-12 15:04:38</created>
		<closed>2015-11-17 16:13:43</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>66</id>
		<title>Export as Zip Not Working</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2015-10-23 15:37:09</created>
		<closed>2015-10-23 15:37:11</closed>
	</bug>
	<bug>
		<id>65</id>
		<title>Export as PDF Not working</title>
		<body></body>
		<created>2015-10-23 15:36:46</created>
		<closed>2015-10-23 15:37:22</closed>
	</bug>
</bugs>
